<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><airline_id>2</airline_id><name>Lufthansa</name><title>Cheap First Class Tickets &#38; Discounted Business Class Fare on Lufthansa </title><alias>Business-Flights-First-Class-Lufthansa</alias><summary>&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Lufthansa. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Lufthansa, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Lufthansa. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;With FlyFirst.com and Lufthansa, you&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on luxury airfare and enjoy all of Lufthansa&#38;#39;s extensive and much-lauded services.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Lufthansa&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;As the fourth largest air carrier in the world, Lufthansa is a titan in the airline industry. The privately owned airline maintains the world&#38;#39;s largest aircraft fleet, operates its hub at Frankfurt Airport and houses its headquarters in Cologne, Germany. With more than 116,000 employees, Lufthansa flies to 197 international destinations. The company holds 14 subsidiaries, including Austrian Airlines, Swiss European Air Lines and Tyrolean Airways, offering flexibility and choice for passengers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Lufthansa&#38;#39;s services are legendary. Airline reviewer SkyTrax recently evaluated Lufthansa&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;first class services&#60;/strong&#62; and awarded the company with the top five-star designation. In the ratings, SkyTrax noted Lufthansa&#38;#39;s comfortable seats that recline to a fully flat position, its variety of in-flight entertainment and its outstanding on-board staff service.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;As if a five-star rating isn&#38;#39;t enough, Lufthansa recently upgraded its already-extravagant first and business class services. The company opened five new premium lounges in its Frankfurt First Class Terminal devoted entirely to its top-tier passengers. Here, passengers enjoy high-end toiletries, daybeds in quiet rooms, a cigar lounge, hot and cold meals and an extensive wine list. Passengers are delivered directly to their aircraft in sumptuous limousines after passing through special customs and security queues.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In addition to the special first class terminal, Lufthansa operates several first class lounges in the Frankfurt Airport, as well as in airports in &#60;strong&#62;Munich, Dusseldorf, New York, Geneva and Zurich&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class In The Air at Discounted Price&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;n first class, passengers flying out of Germany and other European cities enjoy exclusive caviar service, a &#38;quot;Culinary Delights&#38;quot; menu that changes bi-monthly, appetizers with a wide range of canap&#38;eacute;s and table service featuring top-of-the-line linens and glassware.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class Flights Very Cheap&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In business class, passengers boarding flights in Europe delight in fresh meals served on quality china. On flights lasting more than 76 minutes, travelers enjoy a delectable dessert with choices of fresh fruit, sweet treats or ice cream. Seats on newer aircraft lie completely flat for restful sleeping and contain expanded seat-back entertainment screens. On long-haul flights, passengers can adjust seat angles with their own smart phones and extend the seat to a full six and-a-half feet flat bed.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Lufthansa and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you choose to travel in Lufthansa&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;first or business class options&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com ensures that you enjoy all of the lavish amenities and services at a fraction of the regular rates. Together, Lufthansa and FlyFirst.com offer you tremendous value on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discounted First Class Tickets Lufthansa, Cheap Business Class Flights , last minute flights LUfthansa</description><keywords>Cheap Business class flight with Lufthansa, discounted business class tickets, first class flight Lufthansa</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5d5be27b53ae421e9442a5848b32b4ce.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>First class flights to Europe </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d1b93f46ffad4b6d8de79bf5bbbef83e.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Last minute business class cheap</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>13d93f9ad00d4ca0834252e2051af885.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>cheap tickets to Europe </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>3</airline_id><name>United</name><title>Last Minute Business Class &#38; Cheap First Class Fare on United</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-Tickets-United</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on United, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on United. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on United. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel around the &#60;strong&#62;world in affordable style&#60;/strong&#62; and convenience with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar discounts on first class tickets and last minute business class deals aboard United Airlines. With FlyFirst.com and United, you&#38;#39;ll pay a small fraction of the regular fares on &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62;, yet enjoy all of the full-price services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About United Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The largest airline in the world, United travels to more than 1,000 cities in 170-plus countries across all six inhabited continents. United employs more than 88,000 people, serving more than 140 million passengers annually. Headquartered in Chicago, Ill., United&#38;#39;s other operating brands include p.s., United Express&#38;reg; and United Services.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As a company continuously renewing its commitment to its passengers, the company was designated the &#38;quot;Best Airline for North American Travel&#38;quot; by&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Business Traveler&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;magazine in 2012. In spite of already earning high marks on a variety of its services and amenities, United recently launched extensive upgrade and expansion programs. United is now the only U.S. airline to offer seats that recline to a 180-degree flat position and personal on-demand entertainment systems on first class and business class international long-haul flights from all three New York airports. It also provides live television viewing on 200 of its airplanes.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The company maintains more than 50 United Clubs at 38 airports around the world, featuring complimentary cocktails, snacks and beverages, business services and personal workstations.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class In The Air&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In addition to full-flat beds and personal entertainment systems, domestic first class passengers enjoy adjustable headrests, an iPod adapter, a power outlet, over-sized leather seats and expedited check-in, boarding and security queues.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Additional services for international first class flights include premium personal care kits, comfortable duvets and pillows, exclusive bed turn-down service, lumbar support and back stimulation with United&#38;#39;s BackCycler&#38;reg; motion system and a customized dining experience.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class In The Air &#38;amp; Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In addition to more spacious seating, multi-course meals and a variety of entertainment options, business class passengers enjoy priority security screening. Aboard United BusinessFirst&#38;reg; international flights, &#60;strong&#62;business travelers&#60;/strong&#62; are treated to complimentary toiletry kits, individual seat controls for lie-flat seats and snuggle-worthy duvets and pillows. Ergonomic tray tables, USB ports and a power outlet provide comfortable in-air work spaces.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    United Airlines and FlyFirst.com&#60;br /&#62;
    United&#38;#39;s breadth of travel connections, choice of itineraries and frequently upgraded first and business class services provide the highest &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; and flexibility for all of its passengers. FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s tremendously &#60;strong&#62;reduced first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62; &#60;strong&#62;business class deals&#60;/strong&#62; ensure that you receive the ultimate in service for less than half of United&#38;#39;s published fares.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Fly Comfortably in United's New Business Class Seats with FlyFirst.com Discounts, Last Minute First Class, Cheap Business Class fares</description><keywords>Fly Comfortably in United's New Business Class Seats with FlyFirst.com Discounts</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4c9cf403a6db4e93b225cb37d9a60128.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class United</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>55704a599abd4191883c21a62f190ba5.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class on United</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>6666f675aa174bad989a188fbca1f3a5.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>First Class Cheap United</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>4</airline_id><name>Delta</name><title>First Class Tickets &#38; Discounted Business Class Fare , Save Thousands on Delta, Book with FlyFirst</title><alias>Business-First-Class-Cheap-Delta</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights On Delta, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Delta. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Delta, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Delta. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Relish the phenomenal savings FlyFirst.com provides on Delta Air Lines&#38;#39; award-winning first class fares and business class flights. As a luxury traveler, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to complimentary world-class dining, exclusive airport lounges and pampering services while paying up to 70 percent less than your fellow passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Delta Air Lines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Delta. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Delta delivers more than 160 million passengers a year to 318 destinations across 59 countries. Based in Atlanta, Ga., Delta maintains one of the largest aircraft fleets in the world with 722 airplanes. Dedicated to improving its fleet and customer experiences, Delta is conducting a $3 billion improvement plan. Currently, the airline operates the world&#38;#39;s largest fleet of wireless Internet-equipped aircraft. Delta earned more than 30 airline industry awards for its services and received the Secretary of Defense Freedom Award for supporting its National Guard and reserve employees. The company operates with 80,000 employees around the world.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Delta At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class and international business class passengers receive complimentary access to Delta&#38;#39;s welcoming Sky Club airport lounges. There, travelers delight in a wide variety of complimentary snacks, beverages and cocktails as well as refreshing showers, comfortable armchairs and a variety of other services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class, Affordable Fares&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Delta&#38;#39;s first class is available on all domestic and &#60;strong&#62;international flights&#60;/strong&#62;, offering in-flight wireless high-speed Internet, power outlets, USB ports, live satellite television, hundreds of movies and thousands of music selections. Passengers on lengthy flights dine on entrees created by Delta&#38;#39;s team of celebrity chefs; on shorter flights, passengers enjoy a variety of snacks and beverages. First class passengers appreciate expedited check-in, security and boarding queues that eliminate unnecessary wait times.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Discounted Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Delta Elite is Delta&#38;#39;s international business class also available on transcontinental routes between New York and San Francisco or Los Angeles. Delta Elite travelers savor extensive entertainment options, a delectable wine menu created by a master sommelier and Westin Heavenly&#38;reg; bedding of large, luscious comforters and full-size down-alternative pillows. Transcontinental passengers savor cuisine designed by famed chef Michael Chiarello, while intercontinental travelers dine on seasonal, five-course meals created by renowned chefs. Seat types depend on the type of aircraft involved, but range in recline angles from 150 degrees to full-flat 180 degrees; all offer from 55 to 60 inches of spacious legroom.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Delta And FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel in the lap of luxury with Delta&#38;#39;s distinctive style and service while enjoying FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;amazing discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;first class fares and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Tickets cheap, Business Class Air, Last Minute First Class Tickets</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class Flights, First Class Airline, Last Minute Business Class Deals, Cheap Fare , Cheap Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>d91dcd2fbf654cff8e151f0f3dd19502.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare on Delta</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cad10aa65f134019b33e92319b29387a.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>Business Class Flights </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>de193d7261d643fd82af4660b02783a7.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>First Class Tickets , Last Minute Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>5</airline_id><name>Air France</name><title>Last Minute First Class Ticket, Discounted Business Class Flights on Air Fance</title><alias>Business-Class-Flights-Air-France</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Air France, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Air France. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Air France. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Journey in Air France&#38;#39;s cosmopolitan comfort with dramatic &#60;strong&#62;discounts on first class seats and last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll luxuriate in all of the newly re-designed &#60;strong&#62;premium services&#60;/strong&#62; and amenities while paying as little as 30 percent of published fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Air France&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Air France, a subsidiary of Air France/KLM Group, transports more than 59 million passengers each year to 163 destinations in 92 countries. The company maintains its global hub at Charles de Gaulle Airport in Paris and operates secondary hubs at five other French airports. The company is currently engaged in an extensive enhancement project aimed at improving its long-haul first class and &#60;strong&#62;business class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. The project, budgeted at several hundred millions of Euros, includes the re-design of its La Premi&#38;egrave;re class and its new &#38;quot;feel at home&#38;quot; focus. With the re-design, Air France now offers La Premi&#38;egrave;re class on its long=haul flights only, while &#60;strong&#62;Business Class&#60;/strong&#62; is the highest cabin level on remaining flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Air France At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Air France and its partners operate more than 300 special lounges, &#60;strong&#62;offering business services&#60;/strong&#62;, tranquil lounging areas, Internet access, snacks and meals and a host of other treats. The airline recently inaugurated its new SkyPriority program that offers identical services at all airports so passengers always know what to expect. The new program features special check-in, priority baggage drop-off and expedited immigration and security queues.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;L&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;a Premi&#38;egrave;re Class&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;La Premi&#38;egrave;re passengers enjoy privileged welcome services, luxurious lounges, direct access to aisles on board the flight and seats that convert to flat beds topped with a mattress, duvet and feather pillow. Travelers dine on meals created by world-renowned chefs and sip wines from a menu chosen by one of the world&#38;#39;s most respected sommeliers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business Class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers on all flights delight in Air France&#38;#39;s completely re-designed meals that begin with an oshibori and an aperitif. On medium-haul flights, passengers also savor a full meal, including a starter, main course and dessert. &#60;strong&#62;Business class travelers&#60;/strong&#62; enjoy security checkpoints with fast-track lanes and dedicated check-in and baggage drop-off.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Air France and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the most of your travel time aboard the exceptional luxury of Air France. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll delight in Air France&#38;#39;s distinctive services on &#60;strong&#62;first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; at remarkable savings of up to 70 percent off.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class Tickets on Air France. </description><keywords>Cheap Business Class Fare,Discount Business Class Fares, First Class Tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6842d1864dc442079404bdfb6e47feb8.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Air France </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>afb657ea2dc74f5db59a48a0ed687e0d.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>First Class Tickets </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>fe3cc0dea80a4370bf8c3399f25e45b9.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>last minute business class first class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>6</airline_id><name>Singapore Air</name><title>Last Minute First Class Tickets, Cheap Business Class to Singapore. Best Deals on Business and First Class Fares.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Singapore-Air</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Singapore, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Singapore. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Luxuriate in the gracious amenities of Singapore Air with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s extraordinary deals on first class tickets and business class fares. We&#38;#39;ll save you as much as 70 percent so you can jaunt around the world in one of the best-rated airlines around.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Singapore Air&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Singapore Air served 18 million passengers each year and earned the top five-star rating from SkyTrax. Noting the air carrier&#38;#39;s first and business class lounges, outstanding cuisine, Internet offerings and staff attitude, SkyTrax also honored Singapore at its 2012 World Airline Awards. The air carrier travels to 62 destinations in 35 countries and operates several subsidiaries, including SilkAir and Scoot.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Singapore Air At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;First class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers and travelers with &#60;strong&#62;Singapore Air business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; are invited to enjoy the plush services at any of the airline&#38;#39;s 16 SilverKris Lounges. The lounges offer scrumptious buffets, private workstations, refreshing showers and comfortable arm chairs in a peaceful setting.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Disconted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Singapore Air offers a variety of first class seat types. Its newest seats are some of the widest in the industry at 35 inches across. Fine skin care products; bed turn-down service that includes pajamas, fine linens, duvets and pillows; fine cuisine and an all-in-one electronics panel are just a few of the airline&#38;#39;s first class luxuries. Passengers can choose from dozens of luscious meals at reservation time with the exclusive Book the Cook service.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Singapore Air offers three types of business class, and Singapore Air&#38;#39;s Book the Cook program is available on all of them. On board its all-business class flights between Los Angeles and New York, passengers enjoy wide seats in a 1-2-1 layout which gives every passenger access to the aisle. They also can visit the cabin&#38;#39;s snack corner at any time during the flight.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    On long-haul business class flights, passengers sink into wide leather seats that life fully flat and are arranged in the 1-2-1 format. In-seat power outlets, in-flight entertainment and USB ports are just a few of the amenities.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    On medium-haul flights, seats lies nearly flat and a control panel allows passengers to adjust the seat recline to fit personal preference. Passengers have access to personal entertainment systems featuring television shows, movies, music and 3D games.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Singapore Air and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With Singapore Air&#38;#39;s signature services, it&#38;#39;s easy to enjoy your many travels, and FlyFirst.com makes it more economical with cheap &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class to Asia, Cheap First Class Airline Tickets, Discounted Flights Business Class</description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets, Cheap Business class to Asia , LAst minute Singapore air </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>2c0bd9f87242455c804ad8209e3be0a6.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Singapore Air </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>a3743ae786224cc09daeda06e608f6f3.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Last Minute Singapore Air </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>114f40d88075470d92a49ae9279d3fdb.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets Singapore Air</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>7</airline_id><name>Japan Air</name><title>Discounted Business Class on Japan Air , Cheap First Class Travel</title><alias>Cheap-First-Business-Class-Japan-Air</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Japan Air, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Japan Air . Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Japan Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With headquarters in Tokyo, Japan Airlines (JAL) and its subsidiaries transport 52 million passengers each year to 220 destinations across 35 countries. Founded in 1951, the air carrier maintains five subsidiaries, including J-Air, JAL Express and JALways. Combined, the air carriers make up the world&#38;#39;s sixth largest airline.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Japan Airlines At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;JAL services are flavored with gracious Japanese hospitality, as evidenced by the company&#38;#39;s welcoming airport lounges. The signature Sakura Lounge is comfortable, peaceful and beautiful, offering passengers complimentary drinks, refreshments and a chance to relax and unwind. Internationally, the airline operates first class lounges and JAL lounges. All provide tranquil settings for passengers to refresh before, between and after flights with various amenities and &#60;strong&#62;luxury services&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class passengers delight in the range of food options aboard JAL. Full seasonal meals are available from Japanese menus and Western menus, and offer all of the fresh fare one expects from world-renowned chef Fumiko Kono. A la carte menu items are available at any time during the flight. Premium travelers also enjoy the airline&#38;#39;s MAGIC in-flight entertainment system, complimentary cosmetic gift bags and pajamas.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;JAL recently unveiled its new JAL Suite on its Tokyo to New York and London routes. The suites feature Tempur&#38;reg; bedding, Symphony pillows, privacy partitions and a 23-inch electronics screen. They will soon be available on flights from Tokyo to Paris, Chicago and Los Angeles as well.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Discounted Last Minute&#38;#160;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;JAL also extends its attention to upgraded business class seats. The company recently announced it will install new full-flat seats on more international flights in a 1-2-1 configuration so that all passengers have access to the aisle. The new seats will be used on flights between Tokyo and Vancouver and select Southeast Asia and Hawaii flights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In addition to newer, more plush seating, &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers delight in Japanese and Western menus of seasonal fare, and a choice of designer chocolates, Japanese cheeses and freshly steamed Minami-Uonuma rice.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;JAL and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make the most of your travel time by flying in JAL&#38;#39;s distinctive &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62;. With FlyFirst.com, JAL&#38;#39;s high-end &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; are well within reach.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Japan Air Business Class Fares, Cheap First Class Tickets , Last Minute Business Class</description><keywords>Business class trip, First Class Tickets, Cheap Business class fare, last minute business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f0bcb6f9bcf34375b0840b1f36e10e0a.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flights to Asia </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>74cd388727d94bfc81d24fd9e0258044.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class on Japan Air</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>455d95fca0484980a875c17eec3a636c.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Fares</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>8</airline_id><name>American Airlines</name><title>Discounted First Class Airline Flights, Last Minute Business Class on American Airlines </title><alias>Business-Class-Tickets-American-Airlines</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on American Airlines, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on American Airlines. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on American Airlines. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll enjoy discounts as high as 70 percent on the airline&#38;#39;s first and business class tickets, and you&#38;#39;ll receive FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s signature personalized service in the process.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About American Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;American Airlines recently announced its impending merger with US Airways Group, which will finalize by the end of 2013. The merger will create the largest airline in the world and will retain the American Airlines name. Currently, American offers flights to 260 destinations in 50 countries using its fleet of nearly 900 aircraft. Dedicated to renewing its fleet, the company will add another 500 new aircraft in the coming year, creating one of the newest and most updated fleets in the country.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;American At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;International first class travelers are invited to American&#38;#39;s Flagship Lounges at London Heathrow, New York/JFK, Los Angeles and Chicago. The lounges offer meals, premium liquor, business facilities and restful lounge areas. All first class and business class passengers may use the Arrivals Lounge at London Heathrow.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;On international flights, first class passengers enjoy a pampering bed turn-down service that includes a quilted bed topper, duvet, pillows, pajamas and an amenity kit outfitted with Dermalogica&#38;reg; skincare products. On most first class flights, passengers also have the use of a tablet computer for in-flight entertainment holding 70 movies. Many of American&#38;#39;s first class seats swivel 90 degrees to face a work station and 30 degrees to use a dining area. All of these seats extend to a full-flat position and have aisle access. During most flights, savory meals are offered, designed by renowned Chef Richard Sandoval.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;International business class flights receive the same bed turn-down service as on first class, including the Dermologica&#38;reg; skin care amenity kit. Most of American&#38;#39;s business class seats recline and offer foot and leg rests and delightful refreshments. Fresh, inventive meals are provided on international flights and long domestic flights, complemented by fresh-baked cookies and warm, premium nuts.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;American Airlines and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Flying in luxury aboard American Airlines doesn&#38;#39;t have to be expensive when you take advantage of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s remarkable discounts. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy all of the choice amenities of first class seats at a fraction of the regular cost and business class tickets that won&#38;#39;t break the bank&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Last Minute Business Class, First Class Tickets, Business Class Cheap, Discounted Business Class Airfare, America Airlines </description><keywords>Cheap First Class Airline , Last Minute Business, Business class American Airlines , First Class Discounts </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f8ff9f9310db47c3ae0aa5ae81e1c270.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ccd6ac8cffa14662bc214859c075d260.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>Best Deals on First Class Tickets </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>5d282532e87a4aa2aab02c749e5a3cce.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>9</airline_id><name>China Eastern</name><title>Discounted Business Class, Best Deals in First Class on China Eastern Airlines </title><alias>Business-Class-Flights-First-Class-China-Eastern</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on China Eastern , we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on China Eastern. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;We&#38;#39;ll save you up to 70 percent on your China Eastern premium flights so you can find adventure and enlightenment across the globe.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About China Eastern Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;China Eastern Airlines transports the second highest numbers of passengers of all Chinese airlines, carrying more than 65 million travelers each year. With 983 domestic and international destinations, China Eastern operates several subsidiaries, including China United Airlines, Shanghai Airlines, China Cargo Airlines and Joy Air. It holds Jetstar Hong Kong jointly with Qantas Airlines. The company maintains its headquarters in Shanghai and employs more than 63,000 people. Named the world&#38;#39;s most improved airline in 2012 at SkyTrax World Airlines Awards ceremony, the airline is owned in the majority by the Chinese government.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;China Eastern At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Lounges are available at most of China Eastern&#38;#39;s larger destination airports, including Shanghai. Accessible to both first class and &#60;strong&#62;business class passengers&#60;/strong&#62;, the lounges offer drinks, snacks, entertainment options and beer.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Discounted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Privacy and comfort are the hallmarks of China Eastern&#38;#39;s first class cabins. Supple leather seats are over-sized for maximum comfort and recline to your preferred angle. Your seat will recline to a completely flat position for restful sleeping, and you&#38;#39;ll savor the full bed turn-down service that includes a warm duvet, fluffy pillows and pajamas. The unique China Eastern Media Panel offers a wealth of entertainment options, from movies and television shows to games and language courses.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Last Minute&#38;#160;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;China Eastern offers the Business Class Kingbed to its passengers, the largest business class seat in the industry. Be entertained with more than 150 movies, music and games, or make your travel time productive on roomy workstations. With optimum comfort in mind, the custom seats include arms that fold down for extra sleeping and working space and retractable privacy screens that create extra shoulder space. A variety of dining options are made available through the airline&#38;#39;s World Gourmet Cuisine program.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;China Eastern Airlines and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Luxury and service are on tap for premium travelers using the expanding China Eastern Airlines. These prime amenities can be affordable and accessible when you book your &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; with the full-service travel experts at FlyFirst.com.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Tickets, Business Class Cheap , Discounted Airlines Tickets, First Class Fares</description><keywords>Business Class Tickets, Cheap First Class, Last Minute , Discounted Flights in Business Class, Best Deals Business Class.</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f7d274284e24414ebfc80767f3263fdc.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3724cf4bdf144ea69ddc07bef193efdc.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>Best Business Class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>4ca5ab99e6094099a505c5965acd4940.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>Save money Business Class Tickets </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>10</airline_id><name>Air China</name><title>Discounted Business Class &#38; Best Deals in First Class on Air China</title><alias>Business-Class-Flight-Air-China</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Air China, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on regular premium airfares and still enjoy all of Air China&#38;#39;s superior services.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Air China&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Headquartered in Beijing, Air China carries the flag of the People&#38;#39;s Republic of China and operates the 10th largest airline fleet in the world. Annually, the air carrier transports 60 million passengers to 185 international and domestic destinations. Air China maintains seven subsidiaries, including Beijing Airlines, Air Macau, Tibet Airlines, Air China Cargo and Shandong Airlines. The air carrier was established in 1988 and consolidated with China Southwest Airlines and China National Aviation Company in 2002. It was the official airline for the 2008 Beijing Olympic Games.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Air China At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First and business class passengers have access to Air China&#38;#39;s airport lounges around the world. Most of the exclusive airport lounges offer local dishes, snacks, beverages, premium liquor, entertainment and comfortable seating. Some of Air China&#38;#39;s airport lounges include luxury shower facilities, playrooms, large-screen televisions, napping rooms, VIP rooms, private workstations and live musical entertainment.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Disocunted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class seats offer three angled positions: standard, executive and rest. Passengers can swivel the seat to change positions and also enjoy adjustable headrests, power outlets and a spacious, folding work table. Personal on-demand entertainment systems at each seat provide hundreds of options, from movies and music to games. The first class seven-course meal begins with caviar and includes choices of lobster medallion or balic salmon and roasted duck or beef tenderloin. The smaller first class meal offers a choice of shrimp wonton or Quiche Lorraine and a variety of other courses.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Last Minute Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Business class seats aboard Air China recline to 180 degrees for comfortable rest throughout the flight. Passengers appreciate the adjustable headrest, interactive entertainment system, power outlets and either a four-course meal or a two-course meal offering Chinese or Western menu options.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Air China and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Air China can transport you to beautiful and exciting destinations in style and comfort. FlyFirst.com can give you access to dramatically reduced first class seats and last minute business class fares so that you can better enjoy your Air China experience&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Tickets, Discounted First Class Flights, Cheap Last Minute First Class</description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets, Best Deals , Discounted Fares Business Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cc5bc083f37a45029bf4c79d42f06b3e.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Best Deals Business Class Flights</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>f95de6b1f5274df6acffde8c7318a1bd.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute First Class Fares </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>05ef83fdf7da4bb196e9b508b8d395a5.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>First Class Cheap Deals </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>11</airline_id><name>Qatar Airways</name><title>Save Thousands in Business Class and Discounted First Class on Qatar Airways  </title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Business-Qatar-Airways</alias><summary>
    FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Qatar, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Qatar Airway. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.

</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Qatar Airways. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Qatar Airways&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Owned by the Qatar government, Qatar Airways is based in Doha and was named the best airline in the world by SkyTrax in 2011 and 2012. The air carrier operates several subsidiaries, including Qatar Airways Holidays, United Media Int., Qatar Executive and The Qatar Aircraft Catering Company. Serving 124 commercial and cargo destinations, Qatar Airways maintains an aircraft fleet of 122 airplanes. The company employs 20,000 people around the world.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Qatar Airways At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First and business class passengers at Doha International Airport enjoy extensive access to Qatar Airways&#38;#39; Premium Terminal. At the special terminal, personal chauffeurs transport passengers to and from their aircraft in deluxe vehicles. Travelers re-energize with casual dining, delicatessen, hand-rolled sushi and fine dining options and sip wines from a choice vintage selection. Spa services, massages high tea service and first class privacy rooms induce relaxation while kids can draw, color and play with games in the children&#38;#39;s area. A fully equipped business center helps passengers take care of last minute work duties.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Best Deals on First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class travelers settle into comfortable, spacious seats that convert to flat beds equipped with fine Italian Frette linens and a warm duvet. Culinary masterpieces served to first class passengers are a result of a collaboration between four celebrity chefs. An on-demand menu is also available, as is a broad selection of wines. In-air mobile services, Christian Dior amenity kits and fresh pajamas pamper passengers with even more luxury.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Save up to 70% on Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business class&#60;/strong&#62; amenities are just as sumptuous as first class offerings, from personal on-demand entertainment systems, meals designed by celebrity chefs, a selection of on-demand meals, in-air mobile service, high-end wines and Ferragamo Attimo amenities. Seats recline to a flat position and are draped in Italian Frette linen for extra comfort.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Qatar Airways and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With all the pampering and exquisitely designed services provided by Qatar Airways, it&#38;#39;s easy to see why the airline was named the best airline in the world for two consecutive years. FlyFirst.com partners with Qatar Airways to provide you with &#60;strong&#62;dramatic savings&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares and first class tickets,&#60;/strong&#62; ensuring that you &#60;strong&#62;pay far less&#60;/strong&#62; than published rates.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Tickets Deals, Discounted Business, Cheap Business, Cheap First Class</description><keywords>Best Business Class Deals, last minute first class airfare, cheap airline first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c07d3eba54db4c51aa6aece705cd88cd.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Airline Qatar</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>91e89d163fb7469d82343edd002b744c.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Discounted Fare First Class Qatar </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>3a8e6d9d23b84b60ae5038103c4ea2d1.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Save on Business Flight with Qatar Airline</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>12</airline_id><name>Korean Air</name><title>Discounted Business Class on Korean Air , Cheap First Class Tickets, Save up to 70% </title><alias>Business-First-Cheap-Flight-Korean-Air</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Korean Air , we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Korean Air. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Korean Air. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Jet around the world in Korean Air&#38;#39;s prime cabins for less with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s outstanding discounts on &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class seats and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 id=&#34;textpreview&#34;&#62;About Korean Air&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Based in Seoul, South Korea, Korean Air operates its main hub at Incheon International Airport. Named by&#60;em&#62;Business Traveler&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;as Asia&#38;#39;s best airline in 2012, the airline offers a robust international passenger service as well as a vibrant cargo business. The two segments transport 24.2 million travelers and 1.5 million tons of freight to 125 cities in 45 countries in all six inhabited continents. Korean Air is the largest airline in South Korea and employs nearly 21,000 staff members.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Korean Air At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class travelers are treated to exclusive first class check-in counters and personal assistance from KAL Premium Service. Baggage wrapping, overcoat storage and premium lounge areas are also made available to first class passengers. Business/Prestige Class passengers enjoy exclusive check-in desks, snack and beverage service, priority boarding and baggage handling and premium lounge services.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Korean Air offers its first class passengers three types of seating, depending on the aircraft in use: &#60;strong&#62;First Class Kosmo Suites&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;First Class Kosmo Sleeper Seats&#60;/strong&#62; and&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;strong&#62;First Class Sleeper Seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Both Kosmo configurations offer private cubicles with over-sized ergonomically designed seats that recline to a full-flat position for easy sleeping. The Sleeper seat also reclines completely flat and includes a personal entertainment system.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Disocunted Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers travel in Korean Air&#38;#39;s equivalent, Prestige Class. This travel class offers two seating types: the full-flat Prestige Sleeper Suite and the reclining Prestige Plus seat. Both seating types offer personal on-demand entertainment systems, storage and individual reading lamps. Passengers dine on a blend of Korean, Chinese, Japanese and Western cuisines prepared by a first-class chef.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Korean Air and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Korean Air provides stellar f&#60;strong&#62;irst and business class services&#60;/strong&#62; around the world, from Asia and Oceania to Europe and North America. FlyFirst.com specializes in offering Korean Air&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;spectacular luxury&#60;/strong&#62; while saving you as much as 70 percent off published fares. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll pay a fraction of the price on Korean Air&#38;#39;s choice business class fares and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class seats&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description> first class flights Korean Air, Business Class Cheap , Best Deals on Airlines </description><keywords>Last minute Business Fare First Class, Cheap Flights, last Minute Business class, save thousands, cheap airline tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>268316d9bfca4c198b418a201f9fc4d4.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Air </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>42522fb5f40743d4984cd20fcb13af50.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Air </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>0ed0ec277dec42b5a82fb3b0b1c01ee1.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>13</airline_id><name>Asiana Airline</name><title>Discounted First Class &#38; Cheap Business Class on Asiana Airline</title><alias>Business-First-Class-Tickets-Asiana-Airline</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Asiana Airlines, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Asiana Airlines. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel in the luxury of one of the world&#38;#39;s top airlines with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discount first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on Asiana Airline&#38;#39;s deluxe accommodations and enjoy all of its full-price amenities and services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Asiana Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Based in Seoul, South Korea, Asiana Airlines is a top-rated airline serving 105 domestic and international routes. The air carrier often earns the highest marks for service and facilities, earning the coveted &#38;quot;World&#38;#39;s Best Airline&#38;quot; by SkyTrax in 2010 and other &#38;quot;airline of the year&#38;quot; awards over the past five years from publications such as&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Business Traveller&#60;/em&#62;,&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Global Traveler&#60;/em&#62;,&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Premier Traveler&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Air Transport World&#60;/em&#62;. The air carrier employs more than 9,000 workers and is Korea&#38;#39;s second largest airline.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Asiana At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;International first and business class passengers may use the Asiana Lounge at Incheon Airport in Seoul, where refreshments, Internet desks, showers and various other services are provided. Asiana operates two additional international flight lounges in South Korea airports, Gimhae and Gimpo, and several other lounges around the world.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Last Minute First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Asiana&#38;#39;s first class is divided into two categories: First Suite Class and &#60;strong&#62;First Class&#60;/strong&#62;. Suites offer completely private accommodations, mini bars, full-flat beds, 32-inch monitors, on-demand entertainment systems and side seats for companions. First Class offers extra-wide seats that are reclined using high-end electronic controls. Both categories of first class seats include top-of-the-line in-flight snacks developed by Asiana&#38;#39;s chefs in partnership with restaurant La Cucina; superior champagne, cognac, whiskey and other beverages; amenity kits featuring Bulgari cosmetics; pajamas and satellite phones.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Disocunted Business Class Tickets&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Business class options aboard Asiana are also divided into two categories: Business Smartium and &#60;strong&#62;Business Class&#60;/strong&#62;. Smartium offers seats ensconced in shell pods configured in a staggered layout to promote privacy. Each seat has direct aisle access and reclines to a fully horizontal position for sleeping. USB and power ports, personal on-demand entertainment systems, retractable armrests, adjustable headrests, ample storage and over-sized cocktail trays are just a few of Smartium&#38;#39;s amenities. The airline&#38;#39;s Business Class features extra-wide aisles, seats that recline to 167 degrees, personal entertainment systems, top quality in-flight snacks, satellite phones and laptop power ports.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Asiana Airlines and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you choose &#60;strong&#62;first class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, or &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, countless luxuries await your flight aboard Asiana Airlines when you book with FlyFirst.com.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Affordable First Class, Cheap Business Class to Asia, Last Minute Business Class</description><keywords>Cheap Affordable First Class Seats on First-rate Asiana Airlines, First class airlines, cheap business class flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>456e0a1d92bc482cb401a3f5598e519c.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Air</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0580e0e1d2e9475e823faf9658bf3b8e.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flights</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>5282654906cf4eafa1969a4a030d5981.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Last MInute Business Class Flight</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>14</airline_id><name>Thai Airways</name><title>Discounted First Class Tickets on Thai Airways , Cheap Business Class Flights</title><alias>First-Class-Business-Tickets-Thai-Airways</alias><summary>FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Thai Airways. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.d first class fares and business class tickets from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on your travel while appreciating all of the lush full-rate services.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Thai Airways . Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70&#60;/strong&#62;%&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Relish the colorful comfort of Thai Airways with dramatically &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class fares and business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on your travel while appreciating all of the lush full-rate services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Thai Airways&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Based in Bangkok, Thai Airways is the national flag carrier for Thailand and transports passengers to 75 destinations in 35 countries. With 24,000 employees worldwide, Thai Airways frequently wins industry service awards for its catering, service and publications. The air carrier serves nearly 21 million passengers annually.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Thai Airways At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Thai Airways operates its signature lounges at its home base of Suvarnabhumi Airport. The Royal First Lounge at Suvarnabhumi offers two VIP lounges, a la carte dining, business facilities and shower suites. The Royal Silk Lounge features comfortable sofas, a lobby bar, a buffet, kid&#38;#39;s room and computer workstations. The Royal Orchid Lounge is available to both first and business class travelers and offers additional buffet dishes, sleep rooms and private rooms. Spa services at Suvarnabhumi Airport are available for first and business class passengers at the Royal Orchid Spa.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Royal First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class passenger luxuriate in private, over-sized seats with lumbar support. With the touch of a button, the seat reclines to a fully horizontal position for comfortable sleeping. In the flat position, the seats stretch to nearly seven and-a-half feet. Each private seating pod is equipped with an on-demand entertainment system that responds to a touch screen. Thai Airways&#38;#39; award-winning culinary service begins as you enter the first class cabin, and you are presented with a glass of first-rate vintage champagne. Finely crafted meals on fine porcelain and exquisite table linens ensure a fine dining experience.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class/Royal Silk Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Aboard Thai Airways, business class is called Royal Silk Class. Situated in individual shell pods, Royal Silk Class seats offer lumbar support, comfortable recline angles and laptop power outlets. Each seat holds a personal touch-screen on-demand entertainment system offering hundreds of channels, games, music and movies. Delightful dishes offer nourishment and entertainment with menu items ranging from beef steak in peppercorn sauce to stir-fried chicken with garlic. Passengers can pre-order from a menu of eight meals.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Thai Airways and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Traveling abroad in style doesn&#38;#39;t have to be expensive. FlyFirst.com partners with Thai Airways to bring you first class fares and &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; that won&#38;#39;t break your budget.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discounted Business Class on Thai Airways, Best Deals On first Class Fare, Cheap Business Class Airline </description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets ,Last Minute Business Class, Business Discounted Fare on Thai Airways </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0ab30ad9089c4729905c34491c00f6bf.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Thai Airways Airbus A340</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d83dbdc86597412db9b45c831b94fe9a.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title> Unidentified airline staff work</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cb19265b21ce410e9605f796f8c49d16.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Thai Airways aircraft docking</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>15</airline_id><name>All Nippon Airline</name><title>Last Minute First Class Tickets, Discounted Business Class Flights on All Nippon Airline</title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-Discount-All-Nippon-Airline</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About All Nippon Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With more than 14,000 employees, Tokyo-based All Nippon Airlines (ANA) serves 81 domestic and international cities with a fleet of 226 aircraft. The largest airline in Japan, ANA provided transport for more than 47 million passengers in 2012. In 2013, the airline was awarded SkyTrax&#38;#39; top five-star rating for its broad range of services and amenities. FlightStats ranked the airline No. 1 for its on-time performance, and&#60;em&#62;Air Transport World&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;recognized the air carrier with the &#38;quot;2012 Airline of the Year Award.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;ANA At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;All Nippon operates ANA Lounges at various Japanese and international airports. First and business class passengers can dine on light meals, refresh in a shower suite or a massage chair, relax in supple arm chairs or catch up on work at Internet connection sites.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class seats offer exclusive privacy in individual shell or cubicle configurations. Both offer over-sized seats that convert to flat beds, large dining trays, storage areas, international telephones, large-screen monitors and power ports. Light meals are offered throughout the flight to supplement scheduled meals of fresh, seasonal gourmet cuisine. Personal on-demand entertainment systems are installed at each seat, offering movies, music and games. A variety of sleeping accessories are provided for first class passengers, including a feather mattress, fluffy pillow and pajamas. Ginza Cosmetics provides skincare products for the first class amenity kits.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With ANA&#38;#39;s large fleet, it&#38;#39;s unsurprising that there are several business class seating configurations available depending on the individual aircraft. The newer business class seats are ensconced by private shell pods, providing excellent privacy and security. They also feature large sliding trays for work and dining, power ports, ample storage space, seats that recline to a fully horizontal position and large touch=screen monitors. Business class passengers dine on delectable dishes, light fare and, on routes to Asia, Pierre Herm&#38;eacute; Paris desserts. Sleeping accessories, amenity kits, slippers and aroma cards are also available.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;ANA and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With savings up to 70 percent, you can&#38;#39;t afford not to check out FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;amazing deals&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;luxurious first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; on award-winning ANA.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Airfares, Business Class Airfares, Cheap Last Minute First Class Airline Cheap</description><keywords>First class airfares, business class airfares, class airfares cheap business</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f7c226cbea244ee6a9bea57cead8849f.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Boeing 787-881 Dreamliner JA805A</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3b3a14579b5a4f8cadbf7a840fc94f61.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>KAGOSHIMA, JAPAN - FEBRUARY 18</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a44b470f5e404edebddf6387dd78f8b3.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Check in counter at Tokyo</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>16</airline_id><name>Emirates</name><title>Best Deals Business Class Seats, Cheap First Class on Emirates</title><alias>Buisness-First-Cheap-flight-Emirates</alias><summary>Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Emirates. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Emirates, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Emirates. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Experience warm and gracious Middle Eastern hospitality for yourself aboard the lavish aircraft of Emirates airline. Even better, you can enjoy the sumptuous &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; for less with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unbeatable savings. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy discounts of up to 70 percent on regular, published fares, while reveling in the full-price Emirates&#38;#39; treatment.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Emirates&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The largest Middle Eastern airline, Emirates is based in the United Arab Emirates&#38;#39; Dubai. The air carrier transports travelers to 133 destinations in 77 countries across all six inhabited continents. By the number of international passengers it serves, the airline is the fourth largest airline in the world. A subsidiary of The Emirates Group, Emirates is owned by the Dubai government. In 2011, it was named the Airline of the Year by&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Air Transport World&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;and in 2012, SkyTrax named it the world&#38;#39;s eighth &#60;strong&#62;best airline&#60;/strong&#62; at its World Airline Awards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Emirates At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At its main hub at Dubai International Airport, Emirates offers the Emirates Lounge, available to both first class and business class passengers. It also operates 32 additional Emirates Lounges in 28 destination airports around the world. The lounges feature fresh meals, beverages, comfortable seating, large screen televisions, fully equipped &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; centers, complimentary wireless Internet and refreshing shower facilities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Emirates&#38;#39; new Airbus A380 aircraft provide first class passengers with completely private suites. Inside the suites, passengers revel in the personal mini-bar, wardrobe, vanity table and fine cuisine such as lobster and glazed duck. Passengers can refresh in one of two on-board shower spas or mingle with other passengers and nosh on hors d&#38;#39;oeuvres in the on-board lounge.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Discounted Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Stretch out and enjoy the flight on Emirates&#38;#39; business class seats. Electronically controlled seats recline at various comfortable angles and extend to a completely flat 79 inches for sleeping. Delectable meals are served on fine bone china by Royal Doulton and include free-flowing champagne, delicious wines, crisp cocktails and other beverages. Personal in-flight entertainment systems enable you to enjoy movies, television channels, music and games.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Emirates and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Emirates offers the &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; amenities and services, and FlyFirst.com offers the tremendous savings. Together, the partnership proves that you don&#38;#39;t have to break the bank to enjoy &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Last Minuet Business Class To Dubai, Cheap Business First Class Tickets, cheap business class emirates</description><keywords>First Class, Business class, Cheap Flights , Cheap Business Class Flight, Cheap Flights, last minute business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>80c65ed5b2644668bf7ecb344452c0fb.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class To Dubai, last minute flight</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5789c12a22724c2692e2c45e38c7d4c1.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class To Dubai, last minute flight</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>fab06115d7684086bff6447823e7102c.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class To Dubai, last minute flight</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>17</airline_id><name>British Airways</name><title>Cheap First Class Tickets &#38; Discounted Business Class Fare on British Airways </title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-British-Airways</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on British Airways, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on British Airways. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;From world-class airport lounges to spacious, sumptuous premium cabins, flying aboard British Airways is a luxury experience. FlyFirst.com makes it affordable to fly in British Airway&#38;#39;s lavish comfort with outstanding discounts on first class flights, business class seats and last minute tickets.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About British Airways&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;British Airways is a leading world airline, operating more than 300,000 flights each year. Roughly half of those flights originate from or fly into London&#38;#39;s Heathrow Airport. After its 2011 merger with Iberia Air, British Airways (BA) began operating under the umbrella company, International Airlines Group. The air carrier transports passengers to more than 160 destinations and employs about 40,000 workers, pilots and attendants. It was the official airline for the 2012 London Summer Olympic Games.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;BA At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Both first and business class travelers are invited to BA&#38;#39;s Galleries Lounges around the world and may receive complimentary treatments at the airline&#38;#39;s Elemis Travel Spa at Heathrow. First class passengers find exclusive pampering at the Galleries First lounges, complete with ample champagne, wine, coffee, dining, entertainment areas, a kid&#38;#39;s zone and business facilities. Relaxation and refreshments are abundant at the airline&#38;#39;s Terrace and Executive Club lounges, open to both first and business class passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;BA&#38;#39;s first class tier is simply called &#38;quot;First,&#38;quot; where fine dining, on-demand entertainment systems and personal concierges to guide you through Heathrow Airport offer the utmost in pampering service. BA is installing new sophisticated and deluxe First cabins on all of its long-haul aircraft, creating an oasis that first class travelers won&#38;#39;t soon forget. The new cabins offer personal wardrobes, seats with 60 percent more shoulder room, bed turn-down service featuring 400-thread count Egyptian cotton duvets, in-seat power supply and amenity kits stocked with D.R. Harris &#38;amp; Co. products.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Last Minute&#38;#160;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business class&#60;/strong&#62; at BA is referred to as &#38;quot;Club World&#38;quot; and includes world-class cuisine and Elemis amenity bags. Most of Club World&#38;#39;s seats are fully equipped with every imaginable comfort, from laptop lockers and touch-button privacy screens to beds that recline to four pre-set positions. The seats also include memory foam headrests, on-demand entertainment, power supply and a large fold-out table.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;British Airways and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you choose to fly &#60;strong&#62;First or Club World&#60;/strong&#62;, BA has plenty of &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; and service in store for you. FlyFirst.com helps you attain all that splendor for 70 percent off &#60;strong&#62;business class seats and first class flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Exclusive Deals on British Airways' First Class Flights, cheap airline flights, first class , business class cheap, last minute</description><keywords>Exclusive Deals on British Airways' First Class Flights, cheap business class airline, last minute flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ba52fd75cd0a43c7becf2a324e7ea147.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to London</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c66d4fde1d7e4938a62489b6355f9b3c.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>f62245de02de44c6ad5c2b9602cc21d8.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Cheap Airline Tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>18</airline_id><name>Swiss Air</name><title>Best Deals on First Class Tickets on Swiss Air, Save Thousands on Cheap Business Class</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Swiss-Air</alias><summary>&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%

    &#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights Swiss Air , we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Enjoy SWISS hospitality and quality for less with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s discounts of up to 70 percent on first class seats and business class fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Swiss&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Award-winning Swiss International Air Lines (SWISS) is based in Basel, Switzerland, and was formerly known as Swiss Air. Purchased by Lufthansa in 2005, SWISS transports passengers to 74 destinations in 38 countries and is known for its high-quality service. In 2012, the air carrier earned &#38;quot;World&#38;#39;s Best Business Class On-board Catering Award&#38;quot; at the World Airline Awards and previously was recognized as the best airline in Western Europe and for its excellent airline staff service. With a fleet of 92 aircraft, the airline serves nearly 16 million passengers and employs more than 8,000 people.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Swiss At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;First class passengers can relax, dine and work in the spacious luxury of SWISS First Lounges around the world. Its Zurich lounge offers an a la carte restaurant, a fully stocked library, a business center, shower facilities, sleeping rooms and a direct limousine shuttle to the terminal. Business class passengers enjoy the SWISS Business Lounge, where a full buffet offers hot and cold snacks, showers and business facilities in a serene, restful setting.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Tranquil cabins, gracious service and extensive gourmet cuisine are the hallmarks of SWISS first class flights. SWISS&#38;#39; newest first class seat, available on many long-haul routes, offers a comfortable and unique air-cushion technology that adjusts the seat firmness to your personal preference and reclines to a fully flat position for sleeping. All seats directly access the aisle for greater comfort and ease of moving about the cabin. Delightful refreshments and meals are served on board, featuring some of the most treasured tastes of Switzerland, including Balik salmon, traditional Swiss cheese and Nespresso coffee. La Prairie skin care products, an on-demand entertainment system, an amenity kit and sleeping accessories cater to every need and make the trip more enjoyable.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Spacious seats, time-saving services and the world&#38;#39;s best in-class on-board cuisine make traveling in SWISS business class a treat. Intercontinental passengers enjoy over-sized seats that convert to flat beds, delectable five-course meals, power ports, extensive in-flight entertainment systems and Valmont of Switzerland personal care products.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;SWISS and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Let SWISS pamper you with the luxury you deserve, and let FlyFirst.com save you thousands of dollars on those high-end treats aboard SWISS first class flights and business class fares.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Deals on SWISS Business Class Fares, First Class Fares, Discounted Business </description><keywords>Deals on SWISS Business Class Fares,
    Last Minute Flights, First Class Tickets  </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e5487036dcd54d3fb319e74730b1135b.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Cheap First Class on Swiss</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>b730e8640cd14238bb294ddee286691e.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Cheap on Swiss</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cca10d3d1cc64dfdb5f5324b57762609.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Deals </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>19</airline_id><name>Iberia Airlines</name><title>Cheap Business Class Flights and Discounted First Class on Iberia Airlines </title><alias>Business-Class-Iberia-Airlines</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Iberia Airlines, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Serene airport lounges and spacious, premium cabins offer untold delights aboard Iberia Airlines. Enjoy the sumptuous luxuries of world-class Iberia Airlines with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply discounted business class tickets and last minute fares. With savings of nearly 70 percent with FlyFirst, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy all the benefits of premium travel without suffering the high cost.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Iberia Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Iberia Airlines is Europe&#38;#39;s fourth largest airline and the top air carrier providing service between Europe and Latin America. With a main hub in Madrid/Barajas, Iberia offers flights to 102 destinations in 37 countries with 103 aircraft. In 2011, Iberia Airlines merged with British Airways, creating the world&#38;#39;s third largest airline by revenue. The two major airlines now operate under the umbrella of the holding company, International Airlines Group. Iberia is a founding member of the oneworld network and employs about 15,500 staff members.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Iberia Airlines At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Business Class Plus passengers enjoy delectable cuisine designed by acclaimed chef Sergio Arola. Edible options include around-the-clock buffets filled with Spanish favorites and pre-flight meals of tender sirloin steak and other main courses at Iberia&#38;#39;s Madrid Velazquez VIP Lounge. The airline&#38;#39;s flagship Madrid lounges are tranquil, Feng Shui-designed retreats, brimming with natural elements, waterfalls and serene colors. Shower suites, business facilities, entertainment and reading options and high-speed Internet help passengers refresh and relax before, between and after flights.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;beria Airlines offers three types of business class levels, categorized by the length of the flight. For long-haul flights, particularly those between Europe and Latin America, luxury seating is provided in Iberia Airlines&#38;#39; Business Plus cabins. New Airbus A330 and converted A340 aircraft provide all the best new features of first and business class seats. Private seating enclosures showcase supple, cushioned seats that recline to a fully flat position. Each seat includes an individual on-demand entertainment system offering more than 80 television shows and movies in a number of languages, 200 musical options and a variety of interactive, 3D games. The plentiful entertainment is viewed on a personal 15.4-inch touch screen monitor and controlled with a 4.2-inch touch screen remote that doubles as a telephone and text message device. All seats have direct access to the aisle to facilitate easy movement throughout the cabin.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Iberia Airlines and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you are traveling on a short, last-minute European jaunt or you are embarking on a lengthy flight between Spain and Buenos Aires, Iberia Airline provides plenty of luxurious options to make your journey pleasant and comfortable. FlyFirst.com makes all of Iberia Airline&#38;#39;s luxurious seats affordable with unparalleled discounts on business class tickets and last minute fares.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Last Minute First Class Fares, Cheap Discounted Airline Flights, Best Deals Discounted Fares on First Class</description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets on Iberia Air, Best Deals, Discounted First Class Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0ed32a73f5a54bd191a4cd4e51064a79.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>First Class Tickets on Iberia</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9f5a391d70d34cdfbc0b273fb5e1d624.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Class to Europe</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c395230a5eca42c18eda5ceb73c911ef.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Air </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>20</airline_id><name>Austrian Air</name><title>Discounted First Class Tickets on Austrian Air , Cheap Business Class Flights</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Austrian-Air</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights on Austrian Airlines, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Europe.&#38;#160;Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Luxuriate in your flight with the gracious service, abundant amenities and lavish comforts of Austrian Airlines. You can enjoy all of Austrian&#38;#39;s fine appointments for a fraction of the cost with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s dramatically reduced business class fares and last minute deals. With FlyFirst.com and Austrian Airlines, you&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on published business class seats, but enjoy all of the full-price services.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Austrian Airlines&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Austrian Airlines transports more than 11 million travelers each year to 130 global destinations. More than 40 of of those destinations are concentrated in Central and Eastern Europe, while the airline flies 26 weekly routes to North America.&#60;br /&#62;
    With its main hub at the Vienna International Airport, all of Austrian&#38;#39;s operations are now managed by its subsidiary Tyrolean Airways. The airline is part of the Lufthansa Group, employs more than 6,200 staff members and is critically acclaimed for its culinary achievements and high level of customer service. In 2012, Austrian Airlines earned second place for its business class catering at the SkyTrax World Airlines Awards, and it earned first place in the 2011 awards for staff service excellence in Europe and business class catering. It also was bestowed the Crystal Cabin Award for the best Europe seat in 2011.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Austrian Air At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Business class passengers enjoy a host of luxury amenities and services at the Austrian Airlines lounges. On-site &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; centers feature computer workstations, free wireless Internet and access to printers and copy machines. Visitors refresh from an award-winning range of snacks and meals, Austrian wines, abundant drinks and delectable Austrian cakes. Serene retreat areas and entertainment options offer additional opportunities to rest and relax in comfortable settings.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Passengers can sink in to the plush luxury of new business class seating on Austrian Airlines&#38;#39; long-haul, international flights. Reclining to a completely horizontal position, the air-cushioned seats offer the ultimate in restful comfort with a special massage feature included. A &#38;quot;Flying Chef&#38;quot; is on board to prepare and serve specially-ordered meals, while in-cabin sommeliers help travelers select the perfect wine accompaniment. For an after-dinner snack, the airline also offers &#38;quot;flying coffee houses&#38;quot; with an array of 10 classic Austrian coffees prepared on-site. Business class passengers can while away the flight time with an on-demand entertainment system holding more than 100 hours of programming on a 15-inch touch screen monitor.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Austrian Air and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Revel in all the pampering services Austrian Airlines offers its &#60;strong&#62;business class travelers&#60;/strong&#62;, from tranquil airport lounges and well-appointed in-flight cabins to the iconic service of Austrian&#38;#39;s red-suited attendants. All of this comfort and class is available at a sliver of the &#60;strong&#62;published price&#60;/strong&#62; with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discount business class fares and last minute deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class on Austria Air, First Class Discounts, Cheap Last Minute Business</description><keywords>Best Deals Business Class, Cheap First Class Tickets, Last Minute First Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>809621754a9a49449328c6ea67a9ca81.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Deals </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>49b212b8ecff4f67bd6ca5d1b4b5737d.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Save Money Business Class</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>166dfa7634644c8da9210c2a39466f01.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Best Deals First Class Travel</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>21</airline_id><name>Qantas</name><title>Discounted Business Class Tickets, Last Minute First Class on Qantas</title><alias>business-Class-Discounts-Qantas</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Robust international flight schedules, &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;luxurious first and business class&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; amenities and attentive staff are the hallmarks of Qantas Airways. Save bundles on Qantas&#38;#39; premium &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;first class tickets and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s remarkable &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;, and enjoy all of the airline&#38;#39;s acclaimed pleasures at prices that are well within reach.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Qantas Airways&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Created in 1920, Qantas is Australia&#38;#39;s largest airline and the world&#38;#39;s second oldest air carrier. Qantas is known for its outstanding wine service, earning many industry awards, including Cellars in the Sky Awards&#38;#39; 2012 Best Overall Cellar. The airline&#38;#39;s 33,000 employees serve 28 million passengers each year and another 18 million passengers on its subsidiary Jetstar. Other Qantas subsidiaries include QantasLink, Q Catering and Express Ground Handling.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Qantas At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Premium passengers are invited to enjoy the relaxing amenities at Qantas&#38;#39; first and &#60;strong&#62;business class lounges&#60;/strong&#62; at a number of airports. Envisioned by famed designer Marc Newson, Qantas&#38;#39; First Lounge is a contemporary and serene retreat featuring spa services at Payot Day Spa, culinary delights created by Australian restaurateur Neil Perry and business services in fully-equipped business suites.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In the airline&#38;#39;s business class lounge, seasonal menu items, drinks and barista coffees are served throughout the day. Passengers have access to workstations, high-speed Internet, a host of televisions, refreshing showers and a variety of entertainment choices.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Settle in and relax while Qantas sees to every travel detail, including complimentary transfer service with &#38;quot;Chauffeur Drive.&#38;quot; At the airport, travelers appreciate dedicated check-in service, expedited immigration queues and exclusive boarding. In the air, passengers revel in extra-wide seats that convert to divine, full-flat beds covered in sheepskin mattresses and snuggle-worthy duvets. Snacks and light meals are available throughout the flight, while scheduled meal service offers an eight-course tasting menu or Neil Perry&#38;#39;s inspired dishes. &#38;quot;Sommeliers in the Sky&#38;quot; assist passengers in selecting vintages that best complement their chosen meals. Personal telephone and touch screen monitors provide abundant entertainment, and complimentary amenity kits are filled with pampering SK-II products.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Last Minute Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;I&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;nternational business class passengers enjoy many of the same services as first class, such as &#38;quot;Chauffeur Drive,&#38;quot; expedited lines, &#38;quot;Sommerlier in the Sky&#38;quot; and fresh, made-to-order meals. Business class passengers delight in the Qantas Skybed that reclines to a completely flat position, an in-flight lounge, personal entertainment systems, and Kate and Jack Spade amenity kits brimming with Malin+Goetz products.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Qantas And FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Qantas supplies the stellar service and luxury amenities, while FlyFirst.com provides the unparalleled discounts that make a journey worth remembering. Once you&#38;#39;ve sampled Qantas&#38;#39; service, you&#38;#39;ll appreciate the outstanding savings on&#60;strong&#62; first class tickets and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; offered by FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class Qantas, First Class Cheap Fare, Best First Class</description><keywords>Discount Business Class Flights, Cheap First Class Fares, Best Deals on First Class.</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b67de5b796b64507b3916e1f23fe689c.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fare</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>914229c19b3549699af461562984c612.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>null</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>508875bcf0e3404db0a5066c442c8119.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>22</airline_id><name>Cathay Pacific</name><title>Discounted Business Class &#38; Best Deals in First Class on Cathay Pacific</title><alias>First-Class-Cheap-Cathay-Pacific</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares on Cathay Pacific. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights on Cathay Pacific. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Experience the ultimate in luxury travel aboard Cathay Pacific&#38;#39;s award-winning cabins. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on first class seats and business class tickets with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled discount program while enjoying all of Cathay Pacific&#38;#39;s extraordinary services and amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Cathay Pacific&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Based in Hong Kong, Cathay Pacific is one of the world&#38;#39;s leading luxury airlines. The air carrier ranked No. 4 as the World&#38;#39;s Top Airline in 2011 and 2012 at the World Airline Awards, and consistently earns high marks from industry groups. Cathay Pacific travels to 168 destinations in 42 countries and is the third largest airline in the world. It operates eight wholly owned subsidiaries, including DragonAir, and holds interests in six other companies, such as Air China, Air Hong Kong and VN/CX Catering Services. Together, Cathay Pacific and DragonAir transport 27 million passengers each year.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cathay Pacific At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The air carrier maintains several extravagant &#60;strong&#62;first class lounges&#60;/strong&#62; at its home base in Hong Kong International Airport. Flagship lounge, The Wing, features Cathay Pacific&#38;#39;s signature, handcrafted Solus Chair, black marble flooring and walls covered in natural Eucalyptus. Passengers relax in The Champagne Bar, refuel in The Haven&#38;#39;s dining area and shower and snooze in the Cabanas. Hong Kong International also houses several other Cathay Pacific first and business class lounges including The Pier and The Cabin. The airline also operates a variety of premium class lounges at airports around the world.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap First Class Tickets&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Privacy and gracious service are the hallmarks of Cathay Pacific&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;first class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. The airline limits its premium cabins to just six to nine first class seats arranged in a 1x1x1 configuration to give every seat access to the aisle and promote privacy and spaciousness. Travelers enjoy personal on-demand entertainment systems viewed on large 17-inch television monitors, private wardrobes, posh amenity kits and travel bags and freshly prepared gourmet meals.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Discounted Last Minute&#38;#160;Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;It&#38;#39;s easy to see why Cathay Pacific was named the &#60;strong&#62;Best Business Class Airline&#60;/strong&#62; in 2012 at the World Airline Awards. The airline&#38;#39;s new &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; are adjustable to a variety of positions, including moving forward to accommodate privacy or back to encourage socializing with neighboring passengers. The seats convert to an 82-inch long full-flat bed with extra knee space and additional hip support. Passengers delight in extensive personal entertainment systems featuring more than 500 television shows, 100 movies and 70 games in 10 languages, all viewed on a wide 15.4-inch touch screen monitor.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cathay Pacific and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all that Cathay Pacific offers its premium travelers, it&#38;#39;s simple to enjoy luxury accommodations, and with all of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;terrific discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, it&#38;#39;s even easier to save thousands of dollars on &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class tickets.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discount Business Class Air, First Class Tickets Cheap, Last Minute Business</description><keywords>Business Class, Cheap First Class, Last Minute Business Class Fare, Dsicounts</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0fa32bdb08f249ae9234cc9a67b6f1a5.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>8f494057f32749baa1741e70e18460db.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c9946139e165417dae741926b3774e9c.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Save on Last Minute First Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><airline_id>23</airline_id><name>Virgin Atlantic</name><title>Cheap Business &#38; Discounted First Class with Virgin Atlantic</title><alias>First-Class-Cheap-Virgin-Atlantic</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights On Virgin Atlantic, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights Virgin Atlantic. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Contemporary interiors and purple-hued lighting are the hallmarks of Virgin Atlantic&#38;#39;s cabins, but the airline offers so much more for its &#60;strong&#62;premium passengers&#60;/strong&#62;. Relish Virgin Atlantic&#38;#39;s luxury while saving thousands of dollars with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discount first class fares and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on published fares and reap all of the sumptuous full-price services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;About Virgin Atlantic&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Based near England&#38;#39;s Gatwick Airport, Virgin Atlantic was established in 1984 to serve passengers traveling between England and New York. Today, Virgin Atlantic transports more than 5.3 million passengers each year to 34 destinations in North America, Europe, the Middle East, Australia, the Caribbean and Africa. In 2013, the company launched a short-haul service within the United Kingdom named Little Red. Committed to environmental concerns, Virgin Atlantic was the first commercial airline in the world to operate a flight using a biofuel blend, and the air carrier continues to work on creating a low-carbon aviation fuel. Often lauded for its service, Virgin Atlantic was named by Conde Nast&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Traveller&#60;/em&#62;as the best long-haul leisure airline in 2011.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Virgin Atlantic At The Airport&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Chic, contemporary and overflowing with posh amenities, Virgin Atlantic&#38;#39;s airport lounges receive abundant attention from industry leaders, travelers and the press corps. The airline&#38;#39;s newest airport clubhouses at New York&#38;#39;s JFK and Newark airports showcase the airline&#38;#39;s iconic style. At JFK, mingle with other &#38;quot;Upper Class&#38;quot; passengers at the swanky cocktail bar, relax in designer lounge chairs or take care of last-minute work issues at computer workstations. Many of Virgin&#38;#39;s airport lounges also offer spa and salon services such as those found at its flagship clubhouse in Heathrow Airport. There, Upper Class passengers relish a water wall cascading into a relaxing pool, a multi-screen entertainment area, a brasserie, a deli and a library.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Upper Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For &#60;strong&#62;business class passengers&#60;/strong&#62;, Virgin offers its Upper Class program featuring chauffeur transfer services to and from the airport, private security lines, supple leather seats that all directly access the aisle and on-board lounges. The touch of a button converts the comfortable Upper Class seat into an extra-wide flat bed that stretches six-and-a-half feet. Passengers enjoy ample work space and amenities that include power ports, a spacious table and laptop storage space. Entertainment systems with plenty of movies, television shows and games help travelers pass the time, and mood lighting creates a restful, serene on-board ambiance.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Virgin Atlantic and FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com frequently works with Virgin Atlantic to offer the very best deals on its Upper Class cabins. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll save bundles of money on &#60;strong&#62;first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; aboard premium airlines like Virgin Atlantic so that you can enjoy an affordable, &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel experience&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap First Class Tickets, Discount Business Class Fare, Last Minute First Class</description><keywords>Last Minute Business Class Fare, First Class Tickets, Cheap Business Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ef7eec9ed9c94b8aa95c2946853d3ec7.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>e37a1295a23942749c1286ff79d6fbd3.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>First Class Cheap Flights</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>529e2f560fff4e13824cdb1a2f438c64.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Business Class Deals Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>