<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><blog_id>1</blog_id><title>Cheap Buisiness Class Flights to Seoul, Korea, Save Thousands on First Class Tickets </title><alias>Business-Class-First-Cheap-Seoul</alias><posted>5/22/2013 12:00:00 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst Reveals Discounts on Business Class Fares to South Korea&#38;#160;
    FlyFirst, the business class and first class travel experts, announced today that it is offering dramatically discounted business class air Fares to Korea&#38;#160;Travelers using the expert services of FlyFirst can take advantage of fare discounts of up to 60 percent off regular ticket prices to the bustling finance and tourist hub of Seoul and other South Korean destinations.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;FlyFirst Reveals Discounts on Business Class Fares to South Korea&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst, the business class and first class travel experts, announced today that it is offering dramatically discounted business class air Fares to Korea&#38;#160;Travelers using the expert services of FlyFirst can take advantage of fare discounts of up to 60 percent off regular ticket prices to the bustling finance and tourist hub of Seoul and other South Korean destinations.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#8220;Flights from the U.S. to South Korea can range from nearly 12 hours to a little more than 14 hours, so we are delighted to be able to offer our customers affordable fares in the more comfortable business class cabins,&#38;#8221; says Julia Graft, FlyFirst PR manager. &#38;#8220;Whether traveling for business or pleasure, alone or with colleagues or family, business class seating is more spacious and better suited to lengthy and overnight flights.&#38;#8221; Plus,Business Class Ttavelers&#38;#160;can avail themselves of all the other perks of business class, such as higher-end meal service, large work space areas, greater entertainment options and access to service-oriented airport lounges. &#38;#8220;To be able to offer all those business class amenities at tremendously discounted rates is what FlyFirst is all about,&#38;#8221; Graft notes.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Its drastically reduced business air fares to South Korea and other international destinations are a result of FlyFirst network of partnerships with leading travel clearinghouses and companies. Those relationships enable FlyFirst to provide hundreds of discounted business class fares on the world&#38;#39;s best airlines and reduced rates on ground transportation and lodging. Even last minute flights, complicated multi-city itineraries and difficult connections can be accommodated by FlyFirst&#38;#8217; travel experts. The ultimate goal is to provide a seamless travel experience that is hassle-free for all customers, whether they are traveling on holiday or for an important business trip.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#8220;These deeply reduced fares are especially helpful since Seoul is rapidly becoming a leading travel destination for professionals and vacationers,&#38;#8221; Graft says. Its metropolitan economy ranks fourth in the world and is known for its vast technology industry that includes Samsung and LG. On top of its extensive economic draw for global businesses, Seoul is increasingly popular with pleasure travelers. In 2012, the dynamic metropolis accommodated more than 10 million international travelers. Many of those visitors enjoy the city&#38;#39;s abundant attractions, including Lotte World, the largest indoor theme park in the world and Moonlight Rainbow Fountain, the largest bridge fountain on earth. &#38;#8220;There is so much to experience in Seoul, and we are proud to be able to offer such profoundly discounted business class fares to South Korea&#38;#39;s most popular destinations,&#38;#8221; says Graft.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To book a discounted business class ticket to South Korea, call the FlyFirst travel experts at (888) 347-7817 or online at FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Buisiness Class Flights to Seoul, Korea</description><keywords>Cheap Buisiness Class Flights to Seoul, Korea</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>dc67c432c9664f379182a8ebfc4ae954.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>b5adf008aeda4f1da0a2f9579cd08fbd.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>2</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class, FlyFirst Offers First Class Service Fit for an Action Movie Star</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Tickets</alias><posted>5/22/2013 12:00:00 AM</posted><summary>Action movie star and famed martial artist Jean-Claude Van Damme took advantage of FlyFirst&#38;#39;s outstanding deals and personalized service to book his recent first class flight to Singapore. Best known for his roles in the movies&#38;#160;Bloodsport,&#38;#160;Street Fighter&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;Timecop, Van Damme received FlyFirst&#38;#39;s unparalleled personalized service and luxury flight fares at far below published rates. With Van Damme on board, FlyFirst again shows that its legendary discounts and customer service are fit for an action hero.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;div id=&#34;textpreview&#34;&#62;Action movie star and famed martial artist Jean-Claude Van Damme took advantage of FlyFirst&#38;#39;s outstanding deals and personalized service to book his recent first class flight to Singapore. Best known for his roles in the movies&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Bloodsport&#60;/em&#62;,&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Street Fighter&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Timecop&#60;/em&#62;, Van Damme received Fly First&#38;#39;s unparalleled personalized service and luxury flight fares at far below published rates. With Van Damme on board, Fly First again shows that its legendary discounts and customer service are fit for an action hero.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Van Damme is not the only celebrity to use FlyFirst for premium travel planning. The travel professionals at Fly First have supplied discounts on luxury flights for celebrities, executives and savvy travelers for more than nine years. Often, these industry titans depend on FlyFirst to coordinate sudden, complicated and uncertain travel itineraries at the best possible prices and with the utmost attention to detail. Unexpected delays, sudden travel changes and unpredictable issues can cost these VIPs millions of dollars. They rely on FlyFirst to ensure that all travel contingencies are resolved quickly.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Known for our simplified booking process, prospective customers simply complete our online form by listing preferred travel dates, choice of departure and arrival cities, cabin type and contact information. Immediately, Fly First goes to work unearthing the very best possible first class and business class deals available. Our travel professionals then offer clients several travel and pricing options and schedule the itinerary accordingly.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    From the time Fly First receives a travel request to the time the customer arrives home, our travel professionals remain committed to smoothing the way for a flawless travel experience. Last minute itinerary changes and emergencies are no problem for FlyFirst experts who continue to assist customers throughout their travels. Customers never travel alone when they book with Fly First.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    On top of industry-leading expertise and service, FlyFirst offers discounts for as much as 70 percent off published luxury airfare rates. Sometimes, our experts can find first class and business class fares that are as affordable as cheap coach airfares. Currently, Fly First offers business class flights to Singapore for as little as $3,370 and first class flights to London for $3,740.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Fly First maintains strong relationships with all of the major air carriers and a variety of travel companies. These partnerships give FlyFirst customers access to deals on all the major international airlines, including British Airways, Cathay Pacific, Emirates, United, Lufthansa and Virgin Atlantic. These airlines receive stellar marks for first class cabin design, high-end cuisine, comfortable seating and amenity-filled first and business class airport lounges.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    These unrivaled services provided by Fly First have been featured in national broadcasts including &#38;#160;Yahoo, San Francisco Chronicle and others. FlyFirst is a member of the American Society of Travel Agents, the Better Business Bureau and the National Association of Career Travel Agents.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more information about Fly First, visit www.FlyFirst.com or call (888) 347-7817.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discounted Business Class, Bests Deals, Save on First Class, Cheap Business</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to Europe, Last Minute First Class, Discounted Fares, Cheap Flights.</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>83a2d27acdaf4272bc1570e579cadc95.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>39f7834db10f46ecbca6a20538399f27.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>3</blog_id><title>Discounted Fares on Business and First Class to Asia, Last Minute Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Asia</alias><posted>5/22/2013 12:00:00 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class flights to Asia are now more attainable than ever with FlyFirst newly released discounts of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Specializing in affordable business class and first class travel, FlyFirst announced the new first class Asia Dissounts today, just in time for the busy spring and summer travel seasons. First class flights to busy Asian destinations such as Hong Kong, Seoul and Singapore start at just $4,685, and include all the usual luxurious first class services and amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Ordinarily, some of these first class tickets to vibrant Asian destinations such as Hong Kong and Singapore could cost more than $15, 000,&#38;quot; notes Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst. &#38;quot;Most Asian markets are booming, and FlyFirst is proud to be able to offer such affordable first class fares for business travelers and vacationers. These unbelievable low fares give growing global businesses and families on holiday a chance to experience the&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;last minute business class fares&#34;&#62;luxurious first class&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;cabin accommodations without breaking any budgets.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst offers hundreds of these discounted fares to most major Asian destinations. The 70-percent savings are available on many last minute flights, multi-city itineraries and for flights arranged well in advance of the travel dates. Many of the discounted first class seats are aboard the world&#38;#39;s most highly recognized first class airlines.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A first class ticket is an entree to a world of unparalleled luxury and service. Exquisite dining featuring meals designed by world-renowned chefs, spacious private seating arrangements, bed turn-down services and free-flowing champagne are the hallmarks of first class airline service. Many of the airlines&#38;#39; first class airport lounges offer complimentary spa treatments, dining, beverage service, varied entertainment and ample work spaces to start the travel experience on the right note. Some airlines even offer a separate airport terminal and customs desks for first class passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;We are confident that travelers will enjoy the customized first-class service offered by our airline partners, and we are delighted to be able to offer that sumptuous luxury travel up to 70% off&#38;#160;rack prices,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;Whether traveling on vacation or in pursuit of business expansion, these first class rates are unrivaled.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To book a first class seat to Asia at up to 70 percent off, call the travel experts at FlyFirst at (888) 347-7817&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discounted Fares on Business and First Class to Asia</description><keywords>Discounted Fares on Business and First Class to Asia</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>c0013cf3aa0d4b6f8dd0f282c9b597de.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>32a09a8d541a4527bfa25d40a6169964.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>4</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class to London, Discounted First Class &#38; Last Minute Flight Deals </title><alias>Last-Minute-Business-Deals-to-London</alias><posted>5/23/2013 10:38:43 AM</posted><summary>Traveling first class or business class to London is more affordable than ever with new, cheaper fares announced by the travel experts at FlyFirst. Once known as &#38;ldquo;The Big Smoke,&#38;rdquo; London boasts a thriving financial center, a vibrant theater and arts scene and some of the most famous historical sites in Westren Europe. Flying from the United States to London in comfort and style is budget-friendly with FlyFirst&#38;#39; newly released air fares. Business class fares begin at just $2,684, and white-glove first class fares start at only $3,589.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Traveling first class or business class to London is more affordable than ever with new, cheaper fares announced by the travel experts at FlyFirst. Once known as &#38;#8220;The Big Smoke,&#38;#8221; London boasts a thriving financial center, a vibrant theater and arts scene and some of the most famous historical sites in Westren Europe. Flying from the United States to London in comfort and style is budget-friendly with FlyFirst&#38;#39; newly released air fares. Business class fares begin at just $2,684, and white-glove first class fares start at only $3,589.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#8220;These outstanding rates are perfect for professionals who want to bring family along on business trips to London or simply for family pleasure vacations,&#38;#8221; says Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst. &#38;#8220;Business class and first class seats are roomier and more luxurious than coach seats, so this is a great and affordable way for adults and kids to travel on the long flight between the U.S. and London.&#38;#8221;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With so much to see and experience in London, it&#38;#39;s no wonder the city welcomes more than 14 million visitors each year. History lovers can spend days exploring the varied sites in and around London, including Westminster Abbey, the Tower of London and Tower Bridge, Trafalgar Square, the Parliament Building with its infamous Big Ben bell and St. Paul&#38;#39;s Cathedral.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Theater buffs and style mavens will delight in London&#38;#39;s West End district where they can take in a top-rated musical such as Les Miserables or A Chorus Line, enjoy a few nightclubs or explore the many shops and boutiques along the mile-long Oxford Street. London proclaims itself the shopping capital of the world, featuring more than 26,000 stores and the headquarters of noted designers like Stella McCartney, Jimmy Choo and Manolo Blahnik.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;London is a haven for art afficionados and &#38;#8220;foodies&#38;#8221; as well. World-famous modern art museum Tate Modern is one of London&#38;#39;s most iconic tourist stops, as are the Victoria and Albert Museum and the National Gallery. The city&#38;#39;s 6,000 restaurants offer every type of cuisine imaginable, including more than 50 Michelin Star restaurants.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For those who just want to roam the historic city, there are plenty of other sites to visit, including the London Eye, sporting events at Queen Elizabeth Olympic Park, Covent Garden, Picadilly Circus, Hyde Park and the Royal Botanic Gardens.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#8220;London offers a wealth of business opportunity and cultural exploration, and&#38;#160;FlyFirst&#38;#160;makes it attainable with its inexpensive business class and first class air fares,&#38;#8221; Graft says. For information about these deeply discounted business class and first class flights to London, call the travel experts at FlyFirst or visit them online at FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class to London</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to London</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1ca32004dd9d408a90b98d840d32da65.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5920a7dff96d4057b71291e567512d05.jpg</alias><content_id>4</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>5</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Unveils Discounts on First Class Travel to Asia at Up to 70% OFF</title><alias>First-Class-Cheap-to-Asia</alias><posted>5/26/2013 12:04:10 PM</posted><summary>First class flights to Asia are now more attainable than ever with FlyFirst newly released discounts of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Specializing in affordable business class and first class travel, FlyFirst announced the new first class&#38;#160;Asia Discounts Today, just in time for the busy spring and summer travel seasons. First class flights to busy Asian destinations such as Hong Kong, Seoul and Singapore start at just $4,685, and include all the usual luxurious first class services and amenities.
</summary><body>&#60;h2&#62;FlyFirst Unveils Discounts on First Class Travel to Asia at Up to 70% OFF&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class flights to Asia are now more attainable than ever with FlyFirst newly released discounts of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Specializing in affordable business class and first class travel, FlyFirst announced the new first class&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap last minute business class&#34;&#62;A&#60;/a&#62;sia Discounts Today, just in time for the busy spring and summer travel seasons. First class flights to busy Asian destinations such as Hong Kong, Seoul and Singapore start at just $4,685, and include all the usual luxurious first class services and amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Ordinarily, some of these first class tickets to vibrant Asian destinations such as Hong Kong and Singapore could cost more than $15, 000,&#38;quot; notes Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst. &#38;quot;Most Asian markets are booming, and FlyFirst is proud to be able to offer such affordable first class fares for business travelers and vacationers. These unbelievable low fares give growing global businesses and families on holiday a chance to experience the luxury first class&#38;#160;cabin accommodations without breaking any budgets.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst offers hundreds of these discounted fares to most major Asian destinations. The 70-percent savings are available on many last minute flights, multi-city itineraries and for flights arranged well in advance of the travel dates. Many of the discounted first class seats are aboard the world&#38;#39;s most highly recognized first class airlines.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A first class ticket is an entree to a world of unparalleled luxury and service. Exquisite dining featuring meals designed by world-renowned chefs, spacious private seating arrangements, bed turn-down services and free-flowing champagne are the hallmarks of first class airline service. Many of the airlines&#38;#39; first class airport lounges offer complimentary spa treatments, dining, beverage service, varied entertainment and ample work spaces to start the travel experience on the right note. Some airlines even offer a separate airport terminal and customs desks for first class passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;We are confident that travelers will enjoy the customized first-class service offered by our airline partners, and we are delighted to be able to offer that sumptuous&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class flight&#34;&#62;L&#60;/a&#62;uxury at u to 70% OFF&#38;#160;rack prices,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;Whether traveling on vacation or in pursuit of business expansion, these first class rates are unrivaled.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To book a first class seat to Asia at up to 70 percent off, call the travel experts at FlyFirst at (888) 347-7817&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>FlyFirst Unveils Discounts on First Class Travel to Asia at Up to 70% OFF</description><keywords>FlyFirst Unveils Discounts on First Class Travel to Asia at Up to 70% OFF</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>eb44e783f76b45ca9796bfe0fb8658ac.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7279bdd6821947f99f5ccab07ad8f671.jpg</alias><content_id>5</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>6</blog_id><title> FlyFirst Announces Deeply Discounted Business Class Fares to Europe</title><alias>Business-First-Class-Europe</alias><posted>5/27/2013 10:19:16 AM</posted><summary>Business class and first class travel expert, FlyFirst announces its latest discounted business class fares to Australia on some of the world&#38;#39;s most reputable and high-end airlines. Travel in business class comfort and style&#38;#160;Europe&#38;#160;from Australia. for as little as $3,894, round trip, and from to any other international destination with discounts as great as 60%
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Business class and first class travel expert, FlyFirst announces its latest discounted business class fares to Australia on some of the world&#38;#39;s most reputable and high-end airlines. Travel in business class comfort and style&#38;#160;Europe&#38;#160;from Australia. for as little as $3,894, round trip, and from to any other international destination with discounts as great as 60%. &#38;quot;Most business class flights from the U.S. to Australia would cost at least twice that amount,&#38;quot; notes Julia Graft, FF PR Manager. &#38;quot;And since Australia is a terrific access point for popular Asian destinations, FF also is offering remarkable business class fares between Australia and other popular international locations.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:20px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-family:georgia,serif;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#b99d5b;&#34;&#62;The special savings are valid on the following travel options:&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-family:georgia,serif;&#34;&#62;Last Minute Fares on all major airlines&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-family:georgia,serif;&#34;&#62;Business and First Class Tickets to Asia&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:16px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-family:georgia,serif;&#34;&#62;Business and First Class Tickets To Europe&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst&#38;#160; works hand-in-hand with airline wholesalers and travel companies to provide travelers the very best business class fares on the world&#38;#39;s most highly rated airlines. Whether travelers are looking for last minute flights, complicated itineraries to multiple cities or other travel accommodations and transport, the experts at FF find and negotiate the best rates available. Because FF maintains long-standing relationships with its travel partners, it has access to deals not available to the general public and shares those tremendous savings with its customers. Best of all, in addition to its discounted fares, FF is known for its stellar customer service providing seamless, hassle-free travel experiences.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Lengthy international flights can be wearisome, so traveling in the comfort of business class makes sense. Having the space to work and sleep on a long, 14-hour flight from Los Angeles to Sydney can make the trip more enjoyable and productive. &#38;#8220;Business class seats&#38;#160;&#38;#160;are wider and plusher, and often offer private video monitors, extra work space and other professional amenities,&#38;#8221; Graft says. Many major airlines&#38;#39; business class seats recline to a full-flat position so that travelers can sleep on long-haul or overnight flights. Business class travelers also receive more personalized service, special meals created by world-renowned chefs and access to exclusive airport lounges and other custom services.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether traveling to Australia for business or pleasure, business class accommodations can help travelers arrive in Oz rested, relaxed and ready to experience all that the country has to offer. Australia&#38;#39;s two largest cities, Sydney and Melbourne, are not to be missed. Melbourne is home to a variety of art and cultural museums, sporting events and business districts. Sydney, known for its iconic waterfront Opera House, gives visitors a chance to make a breathtaking climb on the famous Harbour Bridge or enjoy the sand and surf on Bondi Beach. FlyFirst can coordinate further travel to Australia&#38;#39;s other vibrant cities, such as the West Coast&#38;#39;s Perth and the north&#38;#39;s Darwin, all at unbeatable prices.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description> FlyFirst Announces Deeply Discounted Business Class Fares to Europe</description><keywords> FlyFirst Announces Deeply Discounted Business Class Fares to Europe</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>77fc269e7d61431eb397a202c82e115a.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>e54a37fb92b14b1ebec2c63eadfd3086.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>7</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Announces Top Tips for Cheap Business Class Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Tickets</alias><posted>5/28/2013 9:36:49 PM</posted><summary>Today&#38;#39;s global marketplace compels professionals to travel the world seeking access to new markets and working 24 hours a day, seven days a week in the process. The advent of business class air travel mirrors the growth of the global economy, creating a level of travel that offers far greater comfort and service than economy class. While not as expensive as first class,&#38;#160;business class air fares can still be a bit pricey.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst Announces Top Tips for Cheap Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Today&#38;#39;s global marketplace compels professionals to travel the world seeking access to new markets and working 24 hours a day, seven days a week in the process. The advent of business class air travel mirrors the growth of the global economy, creating a level of travel that offers far greater comfort and service than economy class. While not as expensive as&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class to asia&#34;&#62;f&#60;/a&#62;irst class, business class air fares can still be a bit pricey.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The business and first class travel experts at FlyFirst(FF) want business and pleasure travelers to know that, with a little ingenuity and planning, business class fares are within reach for a variety of budgets. Here are a few of their tips for getting the best deals on business class travel:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Book in advance. The on-demand pricing structure of many airlines means that the earlier seats are booked, the better the pricing. Booking airfares one to two months ahead of time can translate to savings of up to 60 percent on many airlines. Now is a perfect time to start searching for, and booking, business class flights for late spring and early summer.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Be flexible. Just as with coach airfare, travelers willing to fly overnight, very early in the morning or on quieter days will realize the best savings. The benefits of business class are even more apparent on those red-eye flights, since travelers have more travel room and seats that are more suitable for sleeping.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel off-season. For business class, off-season is summertime when business slows down a bit to accommodate summer vacations and holidays. &#38;quot;Particularly in Europe, where August is the sacred holiday month, business class capacity is often wide open in summer,&#38;quot; advises Julia Graft, PR manager for FF. &#38;quot;The abundance of seats makes summer a great time to travel via business class, especially if the travel is for a pleasure vacation.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Take advantage of unsold seats.Business Class&#38;#160;seats are very infrequently sold out, and those unsold seats often can be purchased at discounted prices, called Y-Up fares. Travelers can call the airlines or an airline booking service and ask for available Y-Up fares. These discounts are especially helpful if travel arrangements are being planned in less than 30 days.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Use frequent flier miles. Often, business class travel is less expensive when using frequent flier miles to supplement an unrestricted coach fare. Travelers can purchase an unrestricted ticket in economy/coach class, then call the airline to ask for an upgrade using mile credits obtained through rewards programs or credit card programs. Before committing to this method, however, travelers should check out the other options to determine the best pricing available.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Use a discount travel booking service. Travel experts&#38;#160;like those at FF have years of experience in negotiating and unearthing the very best deals on business class travel. Using such a service can save travelers loads of time and money and pave the way for a hassle-free travel experience.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether travelers are flying across the world for business or across a continent for a family vacation, business class can offer the perfect combination of comfort and affordability. &#38;quot;Using these FlyFirst tips, we are certain travelers can find reasonably priced business class airfares to suit their individual budgets,&#38;quot; Graft concludes.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>FlyFirst Announces Top Tips for Cheap Business Class Flights</description><keywords>FlyFirst Announces Top Tips for Cheap Business Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>12f31b741c7446fba33b74685bc86bbf.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>a56a2ce11c0043cb8f278daf330a976a.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>8</blog_id><title>Famous Consumer Advocate Kevin Trudeau Uses FlyFirst for His Personal and Business Travel Needs</title><alias>Firs-Class-Trips-Discount</alias><posted>5/29/2013 6:08:17 AM</posted><summary>The list of celebrities and stars using FlyFirst&#38;#39;s deeply discounted luxury flight services just grew a little longer. Famous consumer nutrition and health advocate Kevin Trudeau recently booked a stellar first class flight deal with FlyFirst.com. With his travel reservation, Trudeau receives the high quality service and dramatically slashed first class fares that define FlyFirst.com.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;The list of celebrities and stars using FlyFirst&#38;#39;s deeply discounted luxury flight services just grew a little longer. Consumer nutrition and health advocate Kevin Trudeau recently booked a stellar first class flight deal with FlyFirst.com. With his travel reservation, Trudeau receives the high quality service and dramatically slashed first class fares that define FlyFirst.com.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Radio show host and author Trudeau devotes much of his energy to consumer advocacy, so it&#38;#39;s fitting that he chooses to save as much as 70 percent on premium air travel with FlyFirst.com. Trudeau, along with many other celebrities such as actor and martial artist Jean-Claude Van Damme, corporate executives, business professionals and experienced travelers count on FlyFirst.com to provide a flawless travel experience. Even better, they appreciate access to the same luxurious services and amenities as full-price customers while paying a fraction of the fare.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst provides customers with the complete confidence that they are receiving the very best available first class deals, business class fares and personalized service. Our travel experts are well-versed in all elements of travel planning, and they call on FlyFirst&#38;#39;s extensive network of travel partners to provide unmatched discounts.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The outstanding savings available through FlyFirst.com are valid for a variety of travel needs, including last minute first class flights, one-way trips, multi-city destinations, last minute business class tickets and open-ended return flights.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Step-by-step, FlyFirst travel professionals remain dedicated to each customer&#38;#39;s travel needs. There&#38;#39;s never any need to worry about needing sudden mid-trip itinerary changes since FlyFirst&#38;#39;s experts are available to smooth any and all unexpected changes, roadblocks and travel emergencies.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    We partner with all of the best international and domestic airlines to provide FlyFirst.com customers with access to top-rated air carriers. Our travel professionals are knowledgeable about all of the best airlines, international airports and airport lounges so that they can guide FlyFirst customers in selecting the itinerary that best suits their travel needs. Lufthansa, Cathay Pacific, British Airways, Delta, Virgin Atlantic and Emirates are just a few of the air carriers used by FlyFirst.com.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst&#38;#39;s high-quality service and savings continue to receive nationwide attention in broadcasts around the country, Yahoo, San FRancisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Sun and many more. The company is known for its simplified international and domestic flight online request form. Travelers merely provide their contact information, preferred dates of travel, selected departure and destination cities and chosen class of travel. FlyFirst travel agents immediately scour their vast resources to find the best prices, and they then offer prospective travelers several itinerary options and airport suggestions. The overarching goal of FlyFirst.com is to provide customers with an impeccable travel experience from start to finish.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst.com is a member of the Better Business Bureau, the National Association of Career Travel Agents and the American Society of Travel Agents.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more information about FlyFirst.com and its broad range of discount luxury travel services, call (888) 347-7817 or visit the company online at FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Famous Consumer Advocate Kevin Trudeau Uses FlyFirst for His Personal and Business Travel Needs</description><keywords>Famous Consumer Advocate Kevin Trudeau Uses FlyFirst for His Personal and Business Travel Needs</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>2974729b4ebb4c33be2d4db81cbd9d28.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0de1b3ee00dc46c2ad79ac8ca465bc4e.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>9</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Announces 10 Busiest Airports in the World</title><alias>Discount-Business-Class</alias><posted>6/2/2013 4:52:47 PM</posted><summary>More than 5.4 billion people traveled by air in 2011, an increase of 5.3 percent, and all indications point to a similarly steady growth in 2012. To help air passengers pinpoint the best airport for their own upcoming travels, the business class and first class&#38;#160;travel experts at FlyFirst discuss the 2012&#38;#39;s 10 Busiest Airports in the World, based on preliminary statistics compiled by the Airports Council International.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;More than 5.4 billion people traveled by air in 2011, an increase of 5.3 percent, and all indications point to a similarly steady growth in 2012. To help air passengers pinpoint the best airport for their own upcoming travels, the business class and first class&#38;#160;travel experts at FlyFirst discuss the 2012&#38;#39;s 10 Busiest Airports in the World, based on preliminary statistics compiled by the Airports Council International.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For more than a decade, the Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport has been the world&#38;#39;s busiest airport, and is expected to retain its No. 1 spot in 2012. From January to November in 2012, the airport handled the enplanement and deplanement of more than 88 million passengers, an increase of 3.3 percent over 2011. In spite of its tremendous passenger volume, Atlanta&#38;#39;s airport earns high marks in on-time measurements. The airport infrequently experiences flight cancellations, at a rate of a little more than half of one percent.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#8220;We urge travelers not to automatically avoid busy airports,&#38;#8221; says Julia Graft, FF PR manager. &#38;#8220;Airports like Atlanta&#38;#39;s can sometimes offer more available routes and capacity and may be more efficient than smaller, regional airports.&#38;#8221;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;China&#38;#39;s Beijing Capital International Airport is a distant second to Atlanta with 75 million passengers from January to November, 2012. It will likely retain its No. 2 ranking in 2012, experiencing a 4.3 percent increase in passenger traffic. A bustling hub for Air China, the airport earned high marks in customer service in 2011, placing third in the Airports Council International&#38;#39;s Airport Service Quality Awards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;London&#38;#39;s Heathrow Airport and Chicago&#38;#39;s O&#38;#39;Hare International Airport will likely end 2012 at third and fourth places, respectively. Heathrow handled more than 64 million passengers during the first 11 months of 2012. Its entire network of six London-area airports is consistently ranked as the busiest airport system in the world. O&#38;#39;Hare&#38;#39;s traffic is relatively close to Heathrow&#38;#39;s, with 62 million passengers during the 11-month period. O&#38;#39;Hare&#38;#39;s growth for the year was small, at just under one percent.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Tokyo international airport in Japan experienced a stellar 8.1 percent increase in the first 11 months of 2012, with nearly 62 million passengers in the first 11 months of 2012. The airport has ranked fifth on the list each year since 2009.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The only airport new to the preliminary Top 10 list is Indonesia&#38;#39;s Soekarno-Hatta International Airport at No. 10. &#38;quot;The airport has steadily risen in the rankings over the past few years, placing 12th in 2011 and 16th in 2010,&#38;quot; notes Graft. &#38;quot;Its 15.6 percent increase in passenger traffic is significant and makes it an airport to watch in the coming months.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Here are the preliminary rankings for the 10 busiest airports in the world for January to November, 2012:&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    10. Indonesia Soekarno-Hatta International Airport &#38;ndash; 52.6 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    9. Frankfurt Airport, Germany &#38;ndash; 53.5 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    8. Dallas-Fort Worth International, U.S. - 53.7 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    7. Charles de Gaulle Airport, Paris, France &#38;ndash; 56.9 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    6. Los Angeles International, U.S. - 58.4 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    5. Tokyo International, Japan &#38;ndash; 61.9 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    4. Chicago O&#38;#39;Hare International, U.S. &#38;ndash; 62.1 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    3. London Heathrow, United Kingdom &#38;ndash; 64.4 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    2. Beijing Capital International, China &#38;ndash; 75.3 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    1. Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International, U.S. - 88.0 million passengers&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>FlyFirst Announces 10 Busiest Airports in the World,  cheap business class travel deals, cheap first class deals travel, cheap flights travel deals, Business travel, First Class Travel, cheap discounted business class travel </description><keywords>FlyFirst Announces 10 Busiest Airports in the World Affordable Business Class , affordable first Class tickets, save money on business class airfare, save money on First Class Tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5ad1b439e80e4a4a9c03aacd701f2eed.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>1781ebd1fb1d4adab1ad37267911028b.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>10</blog_id><title> FlyFirst Announces Top 10 Best Seats in First Class Cabin</title><alias>First-Class-Cheap-Dsicount</alias><posted>6/4/2013 9:31:01 AM</posted><summary>Today&#38;#39;s competitive airlines build their reputations on meeting first class passenger expectations of superior facilities, the finest amenities and five-star service. &#38;ldquo;Elaborate first class airport lounges only go so far, however, in keeping the first class passenger satisfied,&#38;rdquo; says&#38;#160;FlyFirst&#38;#160;PR Manager Julia Graft. &#38;ldquo;The in-flight first class seat is just as critical in earning the loyalty of well-heeled travelers.&#38;rdquo;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Today&#38;#39;s competitive airlines build their reputations on meeting first class passenger expectations of superior facilities, the finest amenities and five-star service. &#38;#8220;Elaborate first class airport lounges only go so far, however, in keeping the first class passenger satisfied,&#38;#8221; says&#38;#160;FlyFirst&#38;#160;PR Manager Julia Graft. &#38;#8220;The in-flight first class seat is just as critical in earning the loyalty of well-heeled travelers.&#38;#8221;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To help travelers get the most out of their first class fares, the business and first class travel experts at FlyFirst (FF) recently compiled a list of the Top 10 Best First Class Seats.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Always at top-of-mind for its elegant service, Qatar Airways does not disappoint with its first class seating. The service is exquisite, including a 10-course meal with caviar and free-flowing champagne. The seats are equally impressive with generous storage space, a personal television and seats that extend to full-flat beds for long overnight flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;U.S.-based carriers infrequently attain a spot on these first class lists, but FF likes American Airlines relatively new swivel seats. The first in the industry to offer swivel seating, American Airlines&#38;#39; seats recline to a 6&#38;#39;6&#38;#8221; full-flat bed, and the seat&#38;#39;s two drop-down arm rests provide extra space. The seats operate electronic reclining and lumbar support for additional on-board comfort.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Lufthansa&#38;#39;s First Class cabins include spacious leather seats that convert to full-flat beds. The airline&#38;#39;s 747 aircraft offer first class passengers both a seat that converts to the bed and a chair so that travelers can visit with one another or just spread out. Cabin humidifiers are a nice touch, as are the fine dining options.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First class passengers have more room to spread out and enjoy a little privacy aboard Cathay Pacific. The airline only installs six to nine first class seats on any airplane, in a 1x1x1 configuration. &#38;#8220;That limited seating translates into more personal space and less aisle traffic,&#38;#8221; Graft says. The airline, known for its first class service, offers all the usual first class amenities as well, including a personal television monitor, storage space and plenty of champagne.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Aboard Emirates&#38;#39; Airbus 380, first class seats are actually private suites with full-flat beds and turn-down service. The on-board showers nicely complement other amenities and in-flight entertainment system that always receives top marks from passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FF enjoys Etihad&#38;#39;s push-button control seats that lie fully flat at an impressive 6&#38;#39;8&#38;#8221; and Malaysia Air&#38;#39;s comfortable seats/beds, top-notch linens, toiletries and soft pajamas. Rounding out the list of the top 10 first class seats are &#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class with Singapore air&#34;&#62;Singapore Airlines&#60;/a&#62;, Qantas, and Jet Airways. Singapore Airlines&#38;#39; Airbus 380 first class seats are leather and span 35 inches across. Situated in individual pods, the seats offer privacy and large television monitors. Qantas&#38;#39; provides very large seats with plenty of privacy, ample storage and a plush sheepskin underpaid for sleeping. Jet Airways&#38;#39; first class seating includes excellent in-flight entertainment, comfortable flat beds and sliding privacy screens.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For information about other first class seating options, contact the business and first class travel experts at FF by calling 888-347-7817&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description> FlyFirst Announces Top 10 Best Seats in First Class Cabin, Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares, last minute business class fares, discounted airlines deals</description><keywords>Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares, last minute business class fares, discounted airlines deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>675fcc74d39b4bed8ef85948682a9a56.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>20b5c8b5ba174d27a7769d9b95f528b2.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>11</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Announces Up to 65% Off All Summer International Business Flights</title><alias>Business-International-Flights</alias><posted>6/9/2013 6:56:09 PM</posted><summary>Today, business class and first-class travel leader FlyFirst announced summer blockbuster discounts of up to 60 percent off all international business flights on major airlines
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst Announces Up to 65% Off All Summer International Business Flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Today, business class and first-class travel leader FlyFirst announced summer blockbuster discounts of up to 60 percent off all international business flights on major airlines&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The dramatically discounted rates are valid on a variety of tickets, including last minute fares on all major airlines and first class flights to South America aboard American Airlines. &#38;#8220;We work diligently to negotiate the very best rates possible on first-class and business class flights,&#38;quot; says Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst, &#38;quot;and we are proud to offer these outstanding fares to our treasured customers.&#38;#8221;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The special summer savings are valid on the following travel options:&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    - Last minute fares on all major airlines&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    - Business and first class fares on American Airlines routes to South America&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    - Business and first class tickets to Asia on all major airlines&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    -Business Class and First Class&#38;#160;on all major Airlines&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At regular fares, a first class passenger on a major U.S. airline could expect to pay $7,000 to $14,000 on a first class flight from Los Angeles International Airport to Rome&#38;#39;s Fiumicino Airport in July. These new deep discounts offered at FlyFirstoffer a remarkable cost savings, slashing some fares by as much as 60 percent as well as for Business Class flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The discounted rates are ideal for luxury vacation travelers and busy executives traveling for professional purposes. &#38;#8220;Business class and first-class travel is now well within reach for most professional and personal budgets,&#38;#8221; says Graft. &#38;quot;Summer is a great time to experiment with luxury travel anyway, since business class and first-class tickets are less in demand. Add our steep discounts into the mix, and we know we can offer an unbelievable savings package for our customers.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Summer discounted flights must be booked by May. 25, 2013, and are available only for groups of up to three people. Summer discounts apply only to air fares, not to any hotel or car costs.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To access these unprecedented business class and first-class international air fares, contact one of FlyFirst&#38;#160;knowledgeable travel specialists today at (888) FIRST 17 or (888) 347-7817, or contact us online @ www.FlyFirst.com&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Ticket, Cheap First Class Fare, Discounted Airline Flights. </description><keywords>Cheap Business and First Class fares, last minute business class, cheap airline , last minute business class cheap</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0b59db19da2b49ea959762440c514043.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>08e26439458c4744b0d2fbcce2b9bd7e.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>12</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Announces Top 10 U.S. Most Luxurious Airport Lounges</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Flight</alias><posted>6/10/2013 8:06:05 PM</posted><summary>Escape at the Airport: Top 10 U.S. Lounges to Make Your Time on the Ground Worthwhile.&#38;#160;The trend towards bigger, fancier and more&#38;#160;luxurious airport lounges&#38;#160;is a great boon to travelers. We&#38;#39;ve compiled a list of our favorite U.S. airport lounges that are sure to make you want to hang out in the airport just a little bit longer than usual.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Escape at the Airport: Top 10 U.S. Lounges to Make Your Time on the Ground Worthwhile&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The trend towards bigger, fancier and more&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class Flights&#34;&#62;luxurious airport lounges&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;is a great boon to travelers. We&#38;#39;ve compiled a list of our favorite U.S. airport lounges that are sure to make you want to hang out in the airport just a little bit longer than usual&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Virgin Atlantic Clubhouse, New York&#38;#39;s JFK Airport&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Trendy and cosmopolitan, the JFK Clubhouse is 10,000 square feet of pure delight. Mingle in the modern bar, relax with a free 15-minute massage at Bumble &#38;amp; Bumble salon or play a game of billiards. The Clubhouse is located in Terminal 4 and is open to Virgin Atlantic&#38;#39;s Upper Class passengers, UK Amex Centurion card members and Virgin&#38;#39;s Flying Club gold members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Alaska Airlines Board Room, at Seattle-Tacoma Airport&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    With a serene, contemporary ambiance, the Board Room is a satisfying retreat in Seatac&#38;#39;s Concourse C. Savor complimentary Starbucks espresso, or sip on sodas, beer, wine or cocktails. Fresh snacks are offered throughout the day. Monthly special events feature local restaurants, brewers and winemakers. The Board Room, the 2012 Priority Pass Lounge of the Year, is open to Board Room members and MVP or Gold Alaska Airlines Mileage club members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;last minute business class&#34;&#62;Oneworld Lounge&#60;/a&#62;, Los Angles International&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Shared by British Airways, Japan Airways, Qantas and other Oneworld partners, the Oneworld Lounge sparkles with Macintosh computer terminals, a full bar, buffet, power outlets and comfortable seating. Located on the International Terminal&#38;#39;s Level 5, the lounge is open to Oneworld airlines&#38;#39; first and business class passengers and Oneworld Emerald and Sapphire members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Virgin Atlantic at Liberty Airport in New Jersey&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Spacious and welcoming, the Clubhouse invites members to dine from an extensive menu, watch a movie on a large flat-screen television or rest in private sleeping pods. The 5,000 square foot clubhouse offers every workplace amenity, from charging stations and work surfaces to adapters. Located in Terminal B, the lounge is open to Upper Class passengers, Virgin&#38;#39;s Flying Club gold members and UK Amex Centurion card members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Cathay Pacific Lounge, San Francisco International&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    White Italian marble, black Chinese granite and Venetian glass make this lounge an elegant oasis. Abundant fully-equipped workstations make it convenient to catch up on the office, and the trademark noodle bar offers delicious refreshment. Located on Level 4 of the International Terminal, the lounge is open to Cathay Pacific and Oneworld airlines&#38;#39; first and business class passengers and Emerald and Sapphire Oneworld members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;American Airlines Admirals Club, Denver&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Woodsy and warm, the Admirals Club offers a cyber cafe featuring equipped workstations, a quiet zone, flat-screen televisions, a full-service bar and plentiful snacks and beverages. Located in Terminal A, the lounge is available to American Airlines&#38;#39; business and first class passengers, Amex Platinum members and Oneworld Emerald and Sapphire members.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Delta SkyClub, Miami&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    A little South Beach flair makes this lounge a fun, relaxing area. Shower suites, a chic bar, supple armchairs and a quiet zone lure travelers to the lounge. Located on Level 4, the SkyClub is open to Delta business class passengers, Delta Platinum or Reserve card members or a Diamond Medallion member,&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Lufthansa Lounge, Boston&#38;#39;s Logan Airport&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Lufthansa brings modern Bavarian treats to its passengers, with plentiful German brews, soft leather chairs and workstations. Remodeled in 2011, the lounge is located in Terminal E and open to Lufthansa&#38;#39;s business, Senator and first class passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Emirates Lounge, New York&#38;#39;s JFK&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    In true first-class tradition, the Emirates lounge offers an endless buffet, supple leather seating, shower suites and plentiful entertainment. Open to Emirates&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/airline/Emirates&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;emirates&#34;&#62;first and business clas&#60;/a&#62;s passengers, the lounge is located at Terminal 4.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/airline/British-Airways&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;british airways&#34;&#62;British Airways&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;Terraces Lounge, Seattle Tacoma&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Colorful seating, abundant workstations and bountiful drinks and snack make this lounge a winsome respite from the bustling airport. Available to British Airways first and business class travelers, BA Executive club members and Sapphire and Emerald Oneworld members, the lounge is located in the South Satellite terminal.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business class airline tickets, first class flights, business air flights</description><keywords>Cheap business class, first class, cheap flights, first class airline, cheap air </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>d031df65b6e54ad7b75779a6e30d4c6e.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0a386b6217214520b9b05d3c8c4d5758.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>14</blog_id><title>Cheap Business and First Class this Summer, Save Thousands </title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap</alias><posted>6/17/2013 4:35:29 PM</posted><summary>With more than 1.5 billion Americans taking to the skies for vacations in 2012, the popular summer tourist season can get very busy. FlyFirst, a leading luxury travel booking service, advises travelers for business and pleasure to schedule their summer trips now, before the peak of the season is underway.&#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;With more than 1.5 billion Americans taking to the skies for vacations in 2012, the popular summer tourist season can get very busy. FlyFirst, a leading luxury travel booking service, advises travelers for business and pleasure to schedule their summer trips now, before the peak of the season is underway. To help consumers save on summer travel,&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Cheap Business Class Flights&#34;&#62;FlyFirst offers&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;its four top tips for making the most of a travel budget during the peak season.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Research the destination. Tens of millions of U.S. travelers use the Internet to research their travel accommodations each year. Prospective travelers should put the power of the Internet to use in researching the destination and getting a feel for which summer months are the least expensive. Travel to and from China, for example, is rapidly increasing, and demand for seats on those flights is growing as well. In August, though, travel to China drops off, making it the perfect time to book a trip to the country.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Book in advance. Many airlines use on-demand pricing, so as the available seats are reserved, the pricing increases. This increase can be avoided if travelers book their flights in advance, when there are as many seats open as possible. In addition, other airline costs, such as oil and labor, may increase as the summer progresses, so booking early may help travelers avoid those cost increases.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If booking well in advance isn&#38;#39;t possible, take advantage of unsold seats in other travel classes.&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/continent/asia&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class flight&#34;&#62;Business class seats&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;rarely sell out, and those open seats can be purchased at discounted Y-Up fares. So, for those who need to find a flight within the next 30 days, calling the airline or an airline booking service and asking for available Y-Up fares in business class may be the way to go.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Only the very savvy travelers know to ask for the Y-Up discounts,&#38;quot; notes Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst. &#38;quot;The discounts can be considerable, and vacationers can benefit from the extra space and amenities offered by business class in the process.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For some countries, business travel slows down in the summer. Many European countries, for instance, virtually shut businesses during the holiday month of August. For those destinations, check the pricing of business class tickets and first class fares. Since there is often unused capacity in those classes of travel, the prices may often be more affordable than one would expect. Prices for business class flights from Los Angeles to London, for example, decrease significantly in August.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Take advantage of frequent flier miles, credit card miles and services that can optimize those rewards. Countless credit card companies offer travel mileage accrual on everyday purchases and offer greater flexibility on redeeming airlines. Capital One Venture Rewards Card and Chase Sapphire Preferred Card both get high marks for flexibility and reward bonuses. To maximize the accrued reward points, travelers should consider using services that know all the ins and outs of the reward systems. Award travel booking services like&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.awardgenius.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;save money&#34;&#62;AwardGenius.com&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;help consumers get the most out of their accrued points.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With a little planning, travelers can save considerably on travel during the bustling summer season. For information about saving money on summer travel and to find out more about the services provided by FlyFirst, call (888) 347-7817, or visit FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap first class tickets business class last minute business deals</description><keywords>cheap business class first class deals last minute business class airfare first class tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6f3db310e710455d8e3654ef68904794.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5706faf1a8cb4f59a79a682b1a844299.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>15</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Asia, Discounted First Class Tickets </title><alias>Save-Business-Class</alias><posted>6/20/2013 3:19:25 PM</posted><summary>Those looking for the ultimate travel experience should consider using the services of a reputable luxury travel booking service. FlyFirst offers&#38;#160;cheap business class to Asia. The travel agents at these services are well-versed in finding the very best deals on business class flights and can help provide knowledgeable options to travelers.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;Travelers don&#38;#39;t have to miss out on the luxury of business class flights to Asia this summer.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;In the U.S., studies show that Americans make more than 1.5 billion pleasure trips each year,&#38;quot; says&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Cheap Business class flights&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;PR Manager Julia Graft. &#38;quot;A significant portion of those trips are made during the summer season, increasing demand for economy fares. On the other hand, business travel to Asia drops off as Asians themselves take holidays, leaving extra unsold capacity in business class. This creates a perfect storm for business class pricing, making it often as affordable as coach for summer flights to Asia.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Bustling Hong Kong, home to many mulitnational corporations and the beautiful Victoria Harbour, is a popular destination for business travelers and vacationers alike. Those looking for comfortable airfare to&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/city/Hong-Kong&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class to hong kong&#34;&#62;Hong Kong&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;this summer are in luck, with business class flights starting at less than $3,180 from New York City. For travelers wishing to explore the welcoming city of Seoul, South Korea, business class flights are as low as $3,460. Gleaming Singapore brims with industry, a busy shipping port, world-class gambling and high-end shopping, attracting business and pleasure travelers to the Lion City. Deals on business class flights to Singapore are even more inexpensive than Seoul, starting at $3,370.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Those looking for the ultimate travel experience should consider using the services of a reputable luxury travel booking service. FlyFirst offers&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/continent/asia&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Cheap business class to Asia&#34;&#62;cheap business class to Asia&#60;/a&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;. The travel agents at these services are well-versed in finding the very best deals on business class flights and can help provide knowledgeable options to travelers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Is Tokyo&#38;#39;s Narita International Airport a cheaper alternative to Haneda Airport? Which airport is easier to navigate with young children?&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/city/Singapore&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap last minute flights&#34;&#62;Luxury travel&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;experts at sites like FlyFirst.com know the answers to those questions and can guide consumers to the airports, airlines and travel itineraries that best suit their particular situations and individual needs.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With the airlines&#38;#39; summer sales underway, this is an ideal time to use frequent flier miles and awards acquired through credit card companies. The miles are most efficiently used on international first and business class travel, even when sales are not offered. The award miles are even more effective during this sale season, when business class prices are already low. Award travel sites are experts at maximizing the points accrued by consumers and can save travelers thousands of dollars. Sites like AwardPlanners.com can help travelers find the best upgrades and the best prices, while helping travelers navigate the often-complicated rules and restrictions of miles rewards programs.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;It&#38;#39;s rewarding to hear travelers&#38;#39; excitement when they find out how inexpensively they can fly to Asia in&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/continent/asia&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;business class&#34;&#62;luxury business class&#60;/a&#62;,&#38;quot; says FlyFirst&#38;#39;s Graft. &#38;quot;These outstanding prices aren&#38;#39;t likely to last as summer progresses, though, so we encourage anyone who is thinking about a dream trip to Asia to start planning their trip as soon as possible.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For more information about FlyFirst, call (888) 347-7817, or visit the company&#38;#39;s website at&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#62;http://www.FlyFirst.com&#60;/a&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap business class flight to asia, discounted business class to Asia, last minute flights</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to Asia, cheap first class, discounted business class fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b4068d9a11d740b682725cfacd051eb1.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c68fd53e14a64aedb8f831eed1b92a9e.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>16</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class &#38; Discounted First Class Fares to Hong Kong</title><alias>Business-Class-First-Discount</alias><posted>6/22/2013 3:32:23 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Hong Kong, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Hong Kong. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Hong Kong.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book&#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Mystical Orient or Thriving Western City?&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Hong Kong is a delightful study of merging cultures, economies and lifestyles.&#60;br /&#62;
    Architecture, new and old, is Hong Kong&#38;#39;s most notable contrast. More than 1,000 high-rise buildings tower over the city and surround Victoria Harbour. Majestic mountains are a calming backdrop to the skyscrapers, mixing nature with modern development. Spectacular lights illuminate the night sky as The Center&#38;#39;s neon show marks the end of another day, while the Symphony of Lights music and laser show plays across 44 Hong Kong buildings to set the stage for another night of pulsing discos and nightclubs.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Hong Kong&#38;#39;s historic buildings are low-tech but no less grand than the mighty skyscrapers. Testaments to the city&#38;#39;s long-time religious freedoms, Hong Kong is full of ancient temples and churches. Ohel Leah Synagogue, Hung Shing Temple and Lin Fa Temple are tucked among the city&#38;#39;s skyscrapers, but head away from the city&#38;#39;s tallest buildings to see the stunning traditional Muslim architecture of Kowloon Masjid.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Victoria Peak offers gorgeous views of the city, harbors and Lamma Island. The trip to The Peak is an adventure in its own right aboard the funicular railway Peak Tram.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Travel in World-Class Style to a World-Class City in Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your Hong Kong adventure with a first-rate travel experience courtesy of Fly First&#38;#39;s affordable first class fares and awesome business class deals. With all that the vibrant city has to offer, you&#38;#39;ll want to arrive ready to work and play, and there&#38;#39;s no better way to ensure that than to travel in luxurious comfort. From the moment you embark on your trip, you&#38;#39;ll have access to top-of-the-line amenities and services. From refreshing services at exclusive airport lounges to the spacious comfort of business and first class cabins, your every need will be served.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Save bundles of money on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;business class deals to Hong Kong&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;with FlyFirst.com. Big&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;last minute discounts&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;on premium travel are just part of our extensive services. One-way, around-the-world, multi-city and round-trip journeys all receive our industry-leading&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, saving you as much as 60 percent on airfare. Our expert travel professionals are available to assist you with all your travel needs to ensure that your trip to Hong Kong is flawless. When you book with Fly First, you book with confidence and the knowledge that you are receiving the best last minute discounts and&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;greatest business class deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;available.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class Flight to Hong Kong, first class flight, last minute flights</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class, last minute flights, cheap first class, cheap business class fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>02f85edb189c4219a56e93f31df22cc5.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>518378e33de04d3a9c66555469822ae8.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>17</blog_id><title>Discounted First Class Fare &#38; Cheap Business Class Flights to Seoul. Last Minute Deals  </title><alias>Cheap-Business-Tickets-Seoul</alias><posted>6/22/2013 3:35:51 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Seoul, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Seoul. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4 style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Seoul.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Reveal the Soul of Seoul&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Although it&#38;#39;s known more for its status as a modern international city and technology center, a wealth of history, art and cuisine thrives in Seoul. Whether you are in town for business or pleasure, make time to visit the heart of Seoul, the Gyeongbokung Palace. Seoul was built around this 14th century Joseon royal seat and it bears the marks of the intervening centuries, including Korean War bullet holes. Four other impressive Joseon Dynasty palaces make up the legendary Five Grand Palaces and are not to be missed.&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    Ancient dynasties and rulers have given way to today&#38;#39;s ruling class of Seoul, the booming technology and electronics industry. For business professionals traveling to Seoul, the opportunities here are colossal. Seoul is home to some of the world&#38;#39;s largest and most successful electronics firms, participating in a national economy that is ranked No. 4 in the world. Be poised to make the most of your opportunities in Seoul by traveling in the restful comfort of luxury. With FlyFirst.com&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;first class deals,&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;the airfare will leave you with enough funds to truly enjoy the city&#38;#39;s exciting activities.&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    After a busy day working or a fun-filled day of touring, head up to the top of N Tower. The cable car ride to the top is thrilling and the observation deck offers jaw-dropping views of the city from 1,200 feet above sea level.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Soothing Sojourn to Seoul in Cheap Business and First Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Business or pleasure, alone or with family, your journey to Seoul is made more pleasant in luxurious first or business class. With all that the dynamic city has to offer, traveling in deluxe accommodations ensures that you will be rested and set to explore Seoul&#38;#39;s many attractions.&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    As premium passengers, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy immeasurable service from the minute you reach the airport. Graciously appointed airport lounges offer a respite from the masses as well as a bounty of delicious refreshments to start your long journey. On board your flight, your every wish will be catered by attentive staff members serving five-star meals. You will have plenty of room to work, sleep and relax so that you have the energy to take on Seoul when you land.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Every travel request and itinerary is treated to the same stellar Fly First service and discounts, whether you need multi-city flights or&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;last minute seats&#60;/strong&#62;. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you know that you are accessing the&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;best discounts available&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;on&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;business class tickets and the greatest first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;around.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class to Seoul, First Class Tickets, discounted , business class fares</description><keywords>First Class Flights, Cheap Business Class, Last Minute Business Class Fares, first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bc1997927d0241b4804af6ad0b474e5d.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ad843a01cc284e60811bcc8a12fb17a9.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>18</blog_id><title>Discounted Business Class Fare, Last Minute First Class to London, Call Us Now and Save Thousands </title><alias>Best-Deals-First-Class-to-London</alias><posted>6/22/2013 3:38:41 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to London, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to London. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to London. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Experience the ultimate trip to London with FlyFirst&#38;#39;s affordable business class flights and first class fares, and you&#38;#39;ll save nearly 60 percent off published airfare so that you can experience the old and the new in London.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The River Thames, Big Ben and Treasured Gems&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For more than two millennia, London has been the touchstone of development, beginning as a Roman settlement and growing to the established, but not stagnant, global city of today. Its ever-changing progress is highlighted in its influence in finance, industry and culture and is showcased in the recent opening of The Shard, the 72-skyscraper that forever changed London&#38;#39;s skyline.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Even with exciting new skyscrapers, London retains its charming historical buildings and features. Big Ben, Tower Bridge, Buckingham Palace, Trafalgar Square and St. Paul&#38;#39;s Cathedral are fascinating, both for their history and their exquisite architecture. Throughout the London area, visitors are presented with Georgian and Tudor castles, Gothic palaces, majestic cathedrals and Victorian manses, creating contrast and unity in the eclectic metropolis that is London.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Culture abounds here, too, with sparkling gems of creativity such as delectable five-star restaurants, high-end shopping boutiques, famed theatrical productions, enchanting museums and a vivacious music scene. All are attractions to be experienced by both business and pleasure travelers and offer terrific entertainment at the end of the day.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Almost Fit for a Queen with Discounted First Class Ticket&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all that London has to offer and experience, making the long flight to jolly old England in comfort and style is a wise choice. Blissful first and business class journeys begin at the airport with exclusive lounges featuring serene lounges, scrumptious food and refreshment, refreshing spa services and an opportunity to socialize with other luxury travelers.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Premium airplane cabins continue the white-glove service with culinary masterpieces, pampering bed turn-down service and all its&#38;#160;accouterments, lushly padded seats and ample work space and storage. All of these services are created to meet your every need and assure that you arrive in London rested and set to enjoy the big city.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Premium flights to London don&#38;#39;t require a royal budget when you use the amazing discounts offered by FlyFirst.com. Regardless of your needs,&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;our luxury travel deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;are available on all types of flights, from one-way and round-trip fares to last minute and complicated flights.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Call us today to get started on planning your dream trip to London. Our expert travel professionals are standing by to find you the very&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;best unpublished prices on business class flights and first class deal&#60;/strong&#62;s so that you can enjoy London to the fullest.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap business class ticket to London, discounted First Class to London, best deals to london</description><keywords>cheap flights, first class tickets, cheap business class fares, first class tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>24eb203a5ce54401b9e1bee4f1a2474d.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7356695d99184a6fbffb752c4296a3e6.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>19</blog_id><title>First Class Tickets &#38; Discounted Business Class Flights to Singapore </title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Singapore</alias><posted>6/23/2013 1:25:30 PM</posted><summary>Last Minute Business Class flights to Singapore, we specialize on cheap business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Singapore. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4 style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Singapore.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Opportunity, Glamor and Culture&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Singapore&#38;#39;s 63 islands are a bounty of opportunity, both for business travelers as well as vacationers. For those journeying to the Lion City for business, you have much to explore. A robust shipping industry, more than 7,000 multinational companies and the world&#38;#39;s No. 4 largest financial center are just a few of Singapore&#38;#39;s features. Its port is the fifth busiest in the world, and that vitality brings with it a host of supporting and ancillary businesses and opportunities. As an original member of the Four Asian Tigers, Singapore continues its tradition as an economic powerhouse.&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    World-class casino resorts, high-end shopping, fascinating cultural museums and grand historical architecture are just a few of Singapore&#38;#39;s many delights. For those seeking elective medical treatments outside the U.S., Singapore&#38;#39;s medical tourism industry is thriving due to its modern facilities and highly-trained physicians.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Begin Your Journey With Premium Travel in Cheap Business &#38;amp; Discounted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Make the most of your flight time to spectacular Singapore with the spacious seating, fine dining and personal fully equipped work spaces on board your premium cabin. With our FlyFirst.com deals on everything from luxury last minute flights&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;to first class fares, you&#38;#39;ll be able to enjoy the flight without worrying about a large price tag.&#38;#160;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    Business and first class opulence begins even before you reach your airplane. Once you arrive at the airport, you gain access to exclusive lounges with delectable dining, salon and spa services, plentiful entertainment and relaxing lounge areas. The deluxe service continues throughout your flight, delivering you to&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;rested, refreshed and able to enjoy all of Singapore&#38;#39;s pleasures.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 7px 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;With our incredible savings on&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62;, you have every reason to enjoy the tremendous amenities of first and business class travel. Whether you are planning to attend a conference in Singapore months in advance or you suddenly need to travel for a spur-of-the-moment meeting, FlyFirst can coordinate your trip from start to finish, all while offering airfares at up to 60 percent off conventional ticket prices.&#38;#160;&#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    &#60;br style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34; /&#62;
    Our travel professionals are available to make your trip to Singapore a flawless experience that you will treasure for years to come. Take advantage of our discount&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;and enjoy reduced-fare first class flights today.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Flights to Singapore, Cheap First Class Tickets, last minute flights</description><keywords>Cheap First Class To Singapore, Cheap Business Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bdb811d2aed8415799b9217606f4cc24.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>104e2fc5e56146799eaa4d89bf0ef56b.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>20</blog_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights to Bangkok, Best Deals on First Class. Save Thousands on Cheap Business Class Tickets. </title><alias>First-Class-Fare-Bangkok</alias><posted>6/24/2013 6:45:59 PM</posted><summary>Last Minute Business&#38;#160;Class flights to Bangkok, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Bangkok. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your odyssey to gorgeous Bangkok, Thailand, in deluxe splendor with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;deeply discounted first and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Vibrant Cultures, Vital Industries, Vivid Colors&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Although it&#38;#39;s been decades since Thailand was known as Siam, the country&#38;#39;s cherished historic cultures and landmarks remain, and there&#38;#39;s no better place to experience those treasures than in the booming city of Bangkok.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The third most popular tourist destination in the world, Bangkok is set on the Chao Phraya River delta. It&#38;#39;s home to many awe-inspiring, colorful Buddhist temples, including Wat Arun on the river&#38;#39;s west bank. Wat Arun&#38;#39;s impressive 230-foot spire is one of Bangkok&#38;#39;s most notable landmarks and is intricately brilliant architecture. Bangkok&#38;#39;s largest temple, Wat Pho, features a vivid red and yellow exterior and an extraordinary 154-foot, gold-plated reclining Buddha. Whether you are traveling for business or for pleasure, the temples&#38;#39; amazingly detailed designs and sacred nature are not to be missed.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With all of its meaningful historical sites, it&#38;#39;s easy to forget that Bangkok is a thriving metropolis. Home to dozens of regional headquarters for multinational companies, Bangkok is a Southeast Asian center of industry and finance.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As a modern city, Bangkok brims with all the amenities and adventures you would expect of a major international hot spot. Abundant shopping centers surround the city&#38;#39;s Siam Square, as do most of Bangkok&#38;#39;s many high-rises and skyscrapers. Although infamous for its red-light district, Bangkok has a dynamic, legal nightlife scene. After a busy day of sightseeing or meetings, unwind a little and take in the exciting nightclubs in the Patpong district and along Khaosan Road.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make the Trip to Bangkok in Comfort Business Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Don&#38;#39;t exhaust yourself on the long flight to Bangkok. Instead, conserve your energy by traveling in the appealing&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;of first or business class. You&#38;#39;ll relish the services at exclusive airport lounges, and you&#38;#39;ll bask in the luxurious experience of premium airplane cabins. Roomy enough to stretch out and work, your seating is designed to encourage peaceful sleep and productive flight time. You&#38;#39;ll arrive in Bangkok exquisitely rested so you can enjoy the city&#38;#39;s many delights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our 60 percent savings on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;luxury travel airfare&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;is delivered to you with professionalism and the utmost concern for your travel needs. We offer these&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;incredible savings&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;on all types of travel, from last minute trips to complicated multi-city destinations. When you&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;book with FlyFirst.com&#60;/strong&#62;, you book with confidence, knowing that you are receiving the very best&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts available&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today to secure your terrifically&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;reduced business class fares and last minute flight deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;so you can travel to Bangkok in tranquil comfort.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap first class, deals business class, last minute class, best deals business class , cheap business fare</description><keywords>cheap business class tickets, discounted business class, last minute flights, cheap first class, business class deals </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1a68f8adbff74b64bd6fa9d370d6c9b1.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>af9a0ea890d345d7b7318398d23e7d8d.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>21</blog_id><title>Discounted Business Class to Australia, Cheap First Class Fare</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Australia</alias><posted>6/25/2013 12:55:41 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Australia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Australia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Australia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Fossils, Cliff-side Baths and the Great Barrier Reef&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Bountiful beaches, bustling cities and the vast Bush make the land down under an appealing spot for travelers. Even Australia&#38;#39;s modern cities are flavored with the unique character of Australian ingenuity and flair. Iconic Sydney Opera House&#38;#39;s dazzling white sails welcome visitors to the harbor-side metropolis and a world of uncommon adventure. Bustling Melbourne and Brisbane on the east coast, Perth on the west and Darwin on the north teem with robust business districts, wide-open beaches and a welcoming spirit.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Adventuresome travelers relish Australia&#38;#39;s adrenaline-inducing activities such as climbing the Sydney Harbor Bridge, scuba diving the Great Barrier Reef, ascending the steep Blue Mountains aboard the Scenic Cableway and spotting Daintree Village crocodiles. Active travelers don&#38;#39;t miss a chance to surf Australia&#38;#39;s stellar waves, traverse the Blue Mountains&#38;#39; many canyons and hike the Overland Trail.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Riversleigh&#38;#39;s countless rare fossils, Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary&#38;#39;s fascinating wildlife and the exhibits at the Australian Museum offer hours of entertainment for families traveling to the vast nation. Rejuvenate in Newcastle&#38;#39;s ocean baths, including the Bogey Hole baths carved out of the cliffs by convicts in the early 1800s.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Take Advantage of Luxury Travel in Discounted Business &#38;amp; First Class Seat&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Save your energy for exploring Australia by traveling in the lap of luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s business class deals and reduced-fare first class flights. At the airport, you may enjoy special customs and security queues, privileged entree to high-end lounges and all the refreshing services imaginable. On board your flight, dine on five-star quality meals with free-flowing champagne and make use of your lengthy flight with comfortable beds and expansive work spaces. With business and first class flights, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Australia rested and keen to experience all that Oz has to offer.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our expert travel professionals will save you up to 70 percent on first class flights to Australia and provide you with unrivaled service in the process. At times, we can offer business class deals and&#60;strong&#62;cheap first class flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;at prices comparable to economy class. We are the industry leaders in&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;luxury trave&#60;/strong&#62;l and offer you peace of mind that you are receiving the very best&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;prices available on premium flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today or use our simple online form to get a fast, free quote on your unforgettable Australian adventure.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class to Australia, Last Minute First Class to Australia. </description><keywords>First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Flights, Cheap First Class Fare, Discounted Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>9ba35616053b4ea8a500fec25ff21425.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cd9317087dee47188f905529dd0fb96b.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>22</blog_id><title>Save Thousands on Cheap Business Class To Europe, Last Minute First Class Tickets </title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Europe</alias><posted>6/27/2013 10:16:11 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Europe.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Your European adventure awaits, offering warm Mediterranean beaches, thrilling mountain getaways, fascinating prehistoric wonders and sophisticated cultural pursuits. These exciting escapes are affordable when you travel to Europe with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar savings on first class fares and business class tickets. With discounts of up to 70 percent off published rates, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty left over to spend on your European exploits.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Monoliths, Medieval Castles and Menus&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you are traveling to Europe for business or pleasure, the region brims with appealing activities and attractions. From cave paintings at Spain&#38;#39;s Altamira Cave and France&#38;#39;s Lascaux to mysterious monoliths at Stonehenge in England and Carnac in France, Europe is a great place to explore the works of early man. For more recent historical marvels, tour the impressive Alhambra in Spain, Edinburgh Castle in Scotland, the picturesque windmills in Amsterdam and the Colosseum in Rome. Cruise along the Rhine River to see amazing medieval castles and fortresses in&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;cheap business class ticket&#60;/strong&#62;, or wind your way through the historic canals of Venice to take a step back in time.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Although the region has vast historic attractions, there are plenty of contemporary adventures available. Shop some of the world&#38;#39;s best boutiques in Paris, London and Milan or peruse art and architecture in Bacelona, Paris and Belgium. Wander through breathtaking museums in Switzerland, Italy and France, or ascend to some of the tallest skyscrapers in the area for breathtaking views of celebrated cities.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Above all, make time to sample Europe&#38;#39;s treasured regional flavors, including paella in Spain, chocolates in Switzerland and Belgium, complex cuisine and simple pastries in France and fresh seafood and wine in Italy.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Passage to Europe on&#38;#160;Cheap&#38;#160;Business or First Class Flight&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all of these awe-inspiring experiences available, why not make your journey to Europe just as pleasurable? Flying in the comfort and style of first class fares and business class seats can be part of the complete experience with stellar discounts from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy exclusive, inviting airport lounges and expedited airport queues. On your flight, you&#38;#39;ll settle into plush, over-sized seats and dine on high-end cuisine. Your gracious flight attendant offers free-flowing champagne, bed turn-down service and deluxe amenity bags to make your flight peaceful and pleasant.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our expert travel professionals are skilled at scoping out the very best deals available on premium flights to Europe. These tremendous savings are available on all types of flights to Europe, including multi-city trips, one-way excursions,&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;and open-ended return tickets. Regardless of your travel needs, FlyFirst.com is committed to finding the deepest savings to make your European adventure affordable and luxurious. Call us today to find out how much you can save on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;first class fares and&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;strong&#62;business class tickets to Europe&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Flights to Europe, Last Minute First Class Tickets , Discounted Business Class Fare</description><keywords>Business Class to Europe , Last Minute First Class, cheap Flights to Europe</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cdc0d6e96f7d466989442b14d7166a5d.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>46a6dc27ec4647f7b3f00e96d1c4697f.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>23</blog_id><title>Best Deals on Business Class to China, Discounted First Class to Asia</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Tickets-to-Asia</alias><posted>6/27/2013 10:23:07 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to China, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to China. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h4&#62;Journey comfortably to the land of the sleeping giant with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s outstanding&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts on first class tickets and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, saving you up to 70 percent off regular fare prices.&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;A Land of Extremes&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With a country this immense, it&#38;#39;s unsurprising that one of its most notable characteristics is its accumulation of highs and lows. At 1.35 billion people, its population is the largest in the world, and it boasts an economy that is expanding more quickly than any other. Its terrain varies tremendously, from the world&#38;#39;s tallest mountain in Mount Everest to the world&#38;#39;s fourth lowest point at the Turpan Depression. Climates vary from frigid glaciers to warm, sunny beaches. With this diversity, China overflows with attractions to enchant travelers of all ages.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In keeping with China&#38;#39;s record-holding nature, the country&#38;#39;s most iconic landmark stretches for more than 13,000 miles. The Great Wall of China, originating in 220 B.C., is a masterpiece of function blended with exquisite form. China is home to part of the thousand-mile wide Gobi Desert and record-breaking 300-mile-per-hour high speed magnetic levitation trains. Its pristine beaches and superlative resorts of Yalong Bay on Hainan Island rival Hawaii for lush palm trees and intriguing wildlife.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;View giant pandas at Wolong National Nature Reserve, sample Shanghai and Beijing cuisine and shop along Nanjing Road. Tour fascinating religious sites such as the Guoging Temple and the 1,300 year old Huaisheng Mosque, one of the world&#38;#39;s oldest mosques. While in Beijing, don&#38;#39;t miss the Forbidden City, home of the Palace Museum and Chinese emperors of the past.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class Luxuries and Cheap Business Class Flights&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;When traveling to a land of such magnitude, it&#38;#39;s fitting to make the trip in the ultimate opulence of plush first and business class flights. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy exclusive invitation to reserved airport lounges with superior services and complimentary edible delights. Sumptuous bedding, five-star quality meals and dedicated attendants highlight the flight experience. Most premium travelers enjoy expedited security and boarding queues and various concierge assistance. All of the luxuries are designed to help you arrive in China as rested and relaxed as possible.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;FlyFirst.com leads the way in providing unmatched discounts on first class flights and business class tickets. Known for first-rate service, our expert travel professionals provide discounts of up to 70 percent off&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;business and first class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. These stellar discounts apply to first class flights of all types, including one-way,&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;and multi-city flights. Call today for a fast quote on your impending trip to China, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be jetting away to China in blissful comfort.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Tickets to China, Business Class Cheap Airline Flight</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class To China, Last Minute First Class fare, Business Class Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>31e7d98eced74021a8f3487d7633b4a6.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>523cd1f52c2745389e23a7de35199ea7.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>24</blog_id><title>Discounted Business Class to Switzerland, Cheap First Class</title><alias>Save-Big-on-Last-minute-First-Class-Flight-Deals</alias><posted>6/28/2013 9:54:16 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Switzerland, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Switzerland. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div style=&#34;clear:both;&#34;&#62;
    &#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Switzerland.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Explore Invigorating Switzerland&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Certainly, Switzerland offers its iconic, world-class chocolates, terrifically accurate timepieces and fresh-from-the-cow cheeses, and you should definitely sample one or all of these perfections. For a truly rewarding trip to the beautiful country, though, move beyond the stereotypes and explore Switzerland&#38;#39;s robust recreation and rich cultural attractions.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The towering Alps dominate much of Switzerland&#38;#39;s landscape and provide ample opportunities to get outside and relish the crisp, fresh air. Hiking, cycling and skiing are favorite pastimes at the famous slopes. While the Matterhorn is the country&#38;#39;s most famous mountaintop, there are countless others to experience. Take a ride on the world&#38;#39;s first revolving gondola to delight in a 360 degree view of Mt. Titlis, or head to Alpnachstad for an even more unique thrill. There, you&#38;#39;ll board the steepest cog railway in the world to ascend more than 5,500 feet at a 48 percent gradient to Pilates Kulm.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you&#38;#39;ve enjoyed the abundant recreation, enjoy some of Switzerland&#38;#39;s more relaxing attractions. Get a peak at Heidi&#38;#39;s World, tour some of the country&#38;#39;s 1,000-plus museums or scout the 44 B.C. Roman settlement August Raurica. Take a step back in time at Stein am Rhein and its looming mountaintop Hohenklingen Castle. Stein am Rhein&#38;#39;s Old Town is fabulously preserved and includes the medieval St. Georgen&#38;#39;s Monastery.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Affluence Is The Hallmark Of Luxury Travel, Travel in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;It&#38;#39;s fitting to travel to one of the world&#38;#39;s wealthiest countries aboard opulent first and business class. As soon as you enter the airport, you&#38;#39;ll be pampered at choice lounges offering everything from complimentary meals and business centers to spa services and entertainment. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll savor champagne with five-star cuisine as you settle in to roomy leather seats. The ultimate bed turn-down service includes fresh pajamas, cushioned mattresses and fluffy pillows. You&#38;#39;ll arrive in Switzerland refreshed and eager to appreciate all Switzerland offers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our unrivaled service leads the industry in providing dramatically&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounted business and first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. Our skilled travel professionals can save you as much as 70 percent, sometimes ticket prices are even less than regular coach fares. Our remarkable&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;apply to premium travel of all types, including multi-city, open-jaw and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today or submit our simple online form to find out how much money you can save on your next expedition to Switzerland.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;
    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class, First Class Tickets, Discounted Business Class Fare, cheap first class to switzerland</description><keywords>Business Class to Switzerland, First Class Cheap, Last Minute Business Class Fare, Discounted First Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>fdb374acd0244e60b8c5eab79915d0e5.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3c6f44e10faf4dd7a2713877ed776e0f.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>25</blog_id><title>Cheap First Class &#38; Last Minute Business Class to Taiwan, Discounted Tickets</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Best-Deals-to-Taiwan</alias><posted>6/28/2013 10:07:27 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Taiwan, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Taiwan. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h3&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Taiwan.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Skyscrapers and Waterfalls&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;One of the original Four Asian Tigers, Taiwan is an economic powerhouse with a long history of European, Chinese and Japanese influences. In Taiwan&#38;#39;s north, Taipei and New Taipei City are gleaming, bustling cities with some of the largest populations in the world. Relish unique views from the 91st-story outdoor observation deck of Taipei 101, one of the tallest buildings in the world. Its iconic design molds modern steel and glass into pagoda-like tiers and is an appealing symbol of the country.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The Taipei area is full of cultural delights, from the grand Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Hall and Fort Santo Domingo to the divine beauty of the Zushi Temple in Sanxia. Fascinating museums are scattered throughout the area, including the Shihsanhang Museum of Archaeology and the Museum of World Religions. Travelers enjoy wandering the paper lantern-lined streets and ending an exciting day at Taipei&#38;#39;s vibrant night markets.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Away from the cities, the country&#38;#39;s mountains are filled with lush forests, thundering waterfalls and sinuous rivers. Take in the serenity of the 11-mile long Taroko Gorge canyon and hike Lalashan Mountain&#38;#39;s many trail. At Lalashan, delight in the region&#38;#39;s abundant peach orchards and 2,800-year-old giant cypress trees.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;At the southern end of Taiwan is its oldest city, Tainan. Stunning temples such as Wufei Temple and Datianhou Temple pepper the city. Visitors marvel at the imposing fortress Eternal Golden Castle and the Chihkan Towers, also known as the Tower of Red-haired Barbarians. Tainan also boasts a lively metropolis with a bounty of night markets and shopping areas.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury You Deserve in Business and First Class Seats&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With all that you want to experience in Taiwan, make the journey there comfortable and restful aboard plush first and business class cabins. You&#38;#39;ll have access to privileged airport lounges featuring countless pampering services and refreshments. On your flight, you&#38;#39;ll settle into soft, leather seats that provide enough room for comfortable dining, working and sleeping. With all these gracious, &#60;strong&#62;luxury services&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Taiwan refreshed and eager to explore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;At FlyFirst.com, you have access to stellar discounts on first class fares and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Our expert travel professionals &#60;strong&#62;offer discounts&#60;/strong&#62; of up to 70 percent off all types of premium travel, including multi-city trips and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. When you use FlyFirst.com, you are assured that you are receiving the very &#60;strong&#62;best available first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and discounted business class flights to Taiwan.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class to Taiwan, First Class Fare, Discounted Business Class, First Class Tickets </description><keywords>Best Business Class Deals to Taiwan, Cheap First Class to Taiwan, Last Minute Business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0924ca8f33714660b724a033bd2296f5.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>68165a1478b949ca9329761b2767e684.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>26</blog_id><title>Best Deals on Business &#38; First Class to Thailand, Save UP to 70%</title><alias>Save-Bid-Cheap-Business-to-Thailand</alias><posted>6/28/2013 10:32:15 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Thailand, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Thailand. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h3&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Thailand.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Uncover the Mysteries of Siam&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Although Siam has long since given way to the name &#38;quot;Thailand,&#38;quot; the nation&#38;#39;s deeply embedded religions and culture continue to influence Thailand. Experience the country&#38;#39;s rich past, present and future in the hectic city of Bangkok, the world&#38;#39;s third most visited city. For awe-inspiring glimpses of Thailand&#38;#39;s Buddhist temples, trek to intricately decorated Wat Arun and the immense red and yellow Wat Pho. Wat Pho is Bangkok&#38;#39;s largest temple and is known for its gold-plated reclining Buddha that stretches more than 150 feet. Famous for its energetic nightlife, Bangkok also offers lively theater and world-class shopping.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Delightful tropical beaches line Thailand&#38;#39;s coast and surround its many islands. Kayak, parasail or ride elephants along the beach in popular Phuket or settle into the pristine sand and quite beaches of Ko Chang and Ko Lipe.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Even away from the beaches, Thailand offers a world of breathtaking activities. Hike through stunning nature reserves of Khao Sok National Park or head to Kanchanaburi to see the storied bridge spanning the River Kwai. Ayutthaya is Siam&#38;#39;s original capital and lures visitors to ensconce themselves in the history and tradition of Thailand. As the one-time trading capital of Asia, Ayutthaya housed more than one million residents by 1700 and now is home to the temple Wat Phra Si Sanphet and countless ruins of ancient monasteries.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make Your Journey Luxurious in Discounted&#38;#160;Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Flights to Thailand are time-consuming, but they can be restful when flying aboard the luscious comfort of first and business class cabins. The luxury begins at the airport with exclusive invitation to reserved airport lounges. The lounges feature refreshing dining, ample entertainment, relaxing spa and salon services, gracious concierge assistance and fully equipped business centers. On board your flight, you&#38;#39;ll relish even more personalized service. From delectable meals designed by world-famous chefs and endless cocktails to elite bed turn-down services, you&#38;#39;ll extol the virtues of first and business class forevermore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you need&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;or&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;business class deals&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;for a multi-city trip, FlyFirst.com offers the same&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;deep discounts&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Our expert travel professionals are dedicated to offering unparalleled service while providing the ultimate discounts. At times, we can even offer first class tickets that are less expensive than economy fares. Call us today to book your amazing deals on last minute flights and first class fares so you can be on your way in comfort and style to stunning Thailand.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Deals to Thailand, Discounted Business Class, Cheap Business Class Fares </description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to Thailand, Discounted First class Fare, Save on Business Class, Last Minute Business Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>01e68c486fc64e2db72df25e1b27ea24.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>26ee5d5c301d4dbfa32bfcc622694092.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>27</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class to United Kingdom, Discounted Fares in First Class, Call Us Today and Save Tomorrow. </title><alias>Cheap-Business-United-Kingdom</alias><posted>6/28/2013 10:36:14 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to London, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to United Kingdom. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to UK.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With a history spanning 30,000 years, the U.K. teems with ancient ruins and historic sites. In the north, tour the 5,000-year-old village of Skara Brae, or discover the treasures of Scotland&#38;#39;s Edinburgh and Culzean castles. Soak in the atmosphere of the cliff-side medieval Dunluce Castle in Northern Ireland, or marvel at England&#38;#39;s mystical Stonehenge. England overflows with cultural sites, from St. Paul&#38;#39;s Cathedral and Buckingham Palace to dozens of museums and historic estates.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you&#38;#39;ve explored the region&#38;#39;s history, enjoy some of the world&#38;#39;s most spectacular natural wonders. In Scotland, visit Loch Ness and the Highlands&#38;#39; Isle of Sky, and in Northern Ireland, don&#38;#39;t miss the 40,000 stone volcanic &#38;quot;pillars&#38;quot; of the Giant&#38;#39;s Causeway in County Antrim. Delight in beautiful hikes near the Pistyll Rhaeadr, Wales&#38;#39; tallest waterfall or explore the caves at Cheddar Gorge in England.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you prefer cultural sites or adventures, the U.K.&#38;#39;s variety makes for an unforgettable trip.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Royal Luxury is Yours with&#38;#160;Discounted First Class Ticket&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Treat yourself to the luxury you deserve by flying to the U.K. aboard sumptuous first and&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;cabins. You&#38;#39;ll have exclusive entree to some of the best airport lounges where you can grab a bite to eat, mingle with fellow elite travelers, wrap up work duties, enjoy a massage or refresh with a cleansing shower. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll sink into wide leather seats that lie flat to encourage restful slumber, free-flowing champagne and meals created by famous chefs. All of these services and amenities will deliver you to the U.K. feeling like royalty.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With our impressive FlyFirst.com&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, you won&#38;#39;t have to pay an arm and a leg for royal service. Our&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;are secured at discounts of up to 70 percent off published rates and ensure you can travel in style. These outstanding discounts are available for all travel needs, from last minute flights and one-way trips to multi-city itineraries and open-ended trips. On top of our unrivaled&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, our knowledgeable travel professionals are always available to offer first-rate service. We specialize in providing the ultimate assistance throughout your trip so you don&#38;#39;t have to worry about last minute itinerary adjustments or emergency issues. To secure your amazingly affordable first class seats and&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;reduced business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, call us today, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be jetting to the U.K. in royal splendor.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>best deals first class tickets, cheap flights business class united kingdom </description><keywords>cheap first class tickets, discount business class deals, save on first class fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>62cf956d36d94d62b6da91aba72bed74.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5b9c65c8799b4d3f8f64feb7400ba490.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>28</blog_id><title>Save Big on Business Class &#38; First Class Tickets with FlyFirst to Vietnam</title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-Deals-to-Vietnam</alias><posted>6/29/2013 12:19:42 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Vietnam, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Vietnam. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 0px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Vietnam.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Ancient Cities and Pristine Beaches&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Dating back to the Paleolithic Age, Vietnam&#38;#39;s long history is told through its many palaces, ancient cities and natural resources. Like a misty movie set, Ha Long Bay&#38;#39;s deep aquamarine water is surrounded by a cove of rising monoliths. The bay holds abundant caves perfect for exploring and plenty of tourist attractions.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Travel to ancient town Hoi An for a glimpse of life in a 15th century trading port, and view the ornate Cao Dai temples in Tay Ninh, Da Lat and My Tho. History and cosmopolitan buildings intermingle in big cities Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi, where locals and visitors can marvel at the Presidential Palace and Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Lavish Luxury to Vietnam in Affordable Business Class Cabin&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Whether you&#38;#39;re traveling alone or with colleagues or family, your journey to Vietnam is more enjoyable in spacious first or&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;. As a premium traveler, you&#38;#39;ll receive pampering service from the moment you reach the airport. Appealing airport lounges provide a retreat from the airport masses and offer you gracious services and amenities designed to help you relax. In the air, your luxury cabin invites you to settle into the roomy leather seats, kick up your feet and let the accommodating attendants take care of you. You&#38;#39;ll dine on five-star quality meals, sip free-flowing beverages, access state-of-the-art entertainment systems and relish the fully-flat bedding. All of this and more is designed to create a space where you can make the most of your flight time.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2 style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding-top: 25px; font-family: Poly; font-size: 21px; color: rgb(185, 157, 91); line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;When you book with FlyFirst.com, you book with the confidence that you are receiving the very best available rates on&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;first class seats and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Our experienced travel professionals are dedicated to finding the deepest discounts on all types of travel, including one-way trips, multi-city destinations, open-ended return tickets and&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on published fares; sometimes, our first class seats and business class flights are as inexpensive as coach.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div style=&#34;margin: 0px; color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: Arial; line-height: normal; text-align: justify;&#34;&#62;On top of stellar discounts, we are committed to providing you with the ultimate in personalized service. Whether you have complicated travel requirements or need assistance rearranging plans in the middle of your trip, we are here to serve you. Call us now to secure your outstanding&#38;#160;&#60;strong style=&#34;margin: 0px;&#34;&#62;discount on first class seats or last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;so that you can be on your way to brilliant Vietnam&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Cheap to Vietnam, Discount Business Class Tickets, Last Minute Cheap Fare</description><keywords>First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class, Cheap Flights to Vietnam , Cheap Airline Fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b4801fcdc90a484e9ae05809f0a28b57.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>008d88fc79094af6bec61f3f67a3566a.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>29</blog_id><title>Discounted Business Class to Spain, Save Thousands on First Class, Call Us Now or Send Your Request </title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Discount-To-Europe</alias><posted>6/30/2013 5:18:14 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Spain. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Spain.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Palaces, Paella and Mountain Peaks&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Warm people and an even-warmer climate beckons you to the lovely country of Spain. With ravishing cathedrals and palaces, there are plenty of cultural sites to explore in Spain&#38;#39;s many cities.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Famed Spanish artist Gaudi grandly designed nine of Barcelona&#38;#39;s magnificent structures, such as the Sagrada Familia, and should not be missed. Other fascinating sites in Barcelona include the Picasso Museum and the Catalan Gothic-styled Barcelona Cathedral.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In Madrid, visitors delight in the Plaza de Cibeles and the 18th century Royal Palace, the Spanish Royal Family&#38;#39;s official residence. The palace holds 3,418 rooms, some of which are open to the public.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The bustling coastal city of Valencia is the home of delectable paella and a cosmopolitan art scene. Revel in the artistry of the beautiful 15th century Silk Exchange building, then head to the city&#38;#39;s most iconic landmarks of Valencia Cathedral and its Miguelete Tower.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Dozens of other notable structures are spread throughout Spain, including the prehistoric Altamira Cave paintings in Cantabria, the ancient Roman Aqueduct of Segovia and Granada&#38;#39;s grand Alhambra. The massive Alhambra holds a 9th century citadel, Muslim palaces constructed in the 14th century and a 16th century palace built for Charles V.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Spain offers bountiful recreation at its many mountains, lakes and beaches. Burn off some of those late-night tapas calories by hiking or snowshoeing in the Pyrenees&#38;#39; Sant Maurici National Park, or kayaking near the warm beaches of San Sebasti&#38;aacute;n.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Sumptuous Seating to Spain&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Pamper yourself with the&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;you deserve by selecting first or business class flights to Spain with help from FlyFirst.com. As a premium passenger, you&#38;#39;ll access exclusive airport lounges full of appealing services and high-end amenities. Expedited boarding and customs queues are frequently given to premium travelers, making your boarding and disembarking a pleasant, quick experience. On your flight, the pampering continues with five-star cuisine, over-sized leather seats, ample work spaces, privacy screens and bed turn-down service. You&#38;#39;ll land in Spain rested and keen to explore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our knowledgeable travel professionals find the very best deals available on premium flights to Spain and offer you superior service and a variety of travel options. One-way trips, multi-city destinations and last minute seats on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;cheap first and cheap business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;all receive our outstanding discounts of up to 70 percent. To secure your exceptional discounts on first class fares and&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, call us today so that you can be on your way to sunny Spain in no time.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discount Business Class to Europe, Cheap First Class to Spain, Last Minuet Flights</description><keywords>Best Deals Business Class, Cheap First Class Air, Last Minute Deals to Spain, save on business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>72173c56137f40e39b313f76c27fd515.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9800507a35054cf9aa6b331b91b945d8.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>30</blog_id><title> FlyFirst Announces This Summer&#39;s Busiest Airports in The World. Cheap Business &#38; First Class , Save Thousands. Call Us Now </title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-to-Europe</alias><posted>6/30/2013 5:48:29 PM</posted><summary>More than five billion travelers take to the skies each year, with a good many of those passengers heading to airports around the world in the three-month summer season. To help its customers select the best airport for their upcoming summer vacations, FlyFirst, a leader in the first and business class travel industry, recently announced its projections for the summer&#38;#39;s most active airports around the world.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;More than five billion travelers take to the skies each year, with a good many of those passengers heading to airports around the world in the three-month summer season. To help its customers select the best airport for their upcoming summer vacations, FlyFirst, a leader in the first and business class travel industry, recently announced its projections for the summer&#38;#39;s most active airports around the world.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Topping the list as the busiest airport is Atlanta&#38;#39;s Hartsfield-Jackson International Airport. &#38;quot;For more than 12 years running, Atlanta has been the busiest airport in the world, and we expect it to remain the top airport throughout the summer,&#38;quot; explains FlyFirst PR Manager Julia Graft. &#38;quot;The airport is convenient to a variety of vacation spots on the country&#38;#39;s East Coast and is a frequent transition point for U.S. travelers heading to Europe and the Middle East.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Even though it handles a tremendous passenger volume, the Atlanta airport offers excellent on-time flight performance, with 82 percent of its arrivals and 84 percent of its departures adhering to schedule. Infrequent flight cancellations at Atlanta also help summer travelers keep on track.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With good on-time statistics and many flight options, FlyFirst cautions travelers not to automatically avoid busy airports. &#38;#8220;Busy airports like Atlanta usually offer greater route availability, larger capacity and swifter efficiency than their smaller regional counterparts,&#38;#8221; Graft says.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Throughout the summer, Beijing Capital International Airport in China should maintain its rank as the second busiest airport. &#38;quot;Travel to China and the Far East is growing, Graft says, &#38;quot;and FlyFirst expects its summertime travel statistics to remain consistently vigorous.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    London&#38;#39;s system of six active airports actually makes it the world&#38;#39;s busiest airport system, but its Heathrow Airport usually ranks at No. 3 in the list of busy international airports. Not only is London the most-visited city in the world, it offers a variety of convenient links to other vacation spots in Western Europe. Considering all of those factors, FlyFirst expects London&#38;#39;s Heathrow Airport to maintain its spot in the top five busiest airports throughout the summer of 2013.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In recent years, popular Tokyo International Airport and Chicago&#38;#39;s O&#38;#39;Hare International Airport round out the annual list of top five busiest airports in the world, and FlyFirst anticipates they will remain bustling sites throughout the summer. Beyond these top five, however, other airports may become equally busy as families head to favored theme parks, treasured beaches and locales that are more easily reached during warmer months.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Orlando International Airport, already a busy airport, experienced more than 10 percent growth in international travel in the first quarter of 2013. Near popular theme parks such as Walt Disney World, Universal Studios Orlando and SeaWorld, Orlando is convenient to other Florida vacation spots and is a popular summer airport.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Palma de Mallorca Airport in Spain is one of the busiest airports in Europe during the summer. With dozens of resorts, countless beaches, abundant attractions and a vibrant Old Town, Palma de Mallorca is a cherished summer holiday spot for Europeans. Palma de Mallorca Airport also is one of the region&#38;#39;s less expensive airports and offers convenient access to a number of European cities. The airport served more than 22 million people in 2012.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Cheap, Last Minute First Class Fare, Discounted Business Class Fare </description><keywords>Cheap First Class Fare, Save on Business Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class Flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f946bce646fd4cb5910bc59cc24a8873.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>35ce750c83684562a59e6d6d860f3115.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>31</blog_id><title>FlyFirst announces top 5 First Class Lounges. Super Luxury Travel and Cheapest Business Class with FlyFirst. Call Us NOW</title><alias>Discount-Business-Class-Deals-First-Class-Travel</alias><posted>6/30/2013 6:05:00 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst, a leading luxury travel service, today announced its selection of the top five first class lounges in the world. The travel experts at FlyFirst drew on their vast knowledge of the world&#38;#39;s leading luxury lounges
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;FlyFirst, a leading luxury travel service, today announced its selection of the top five first class lounges in the world. The travel experts at FlyFirst drew on their vast knowledge of the world&#38;#39;s leading luxury lounges, feedback from clients and information from industry analysts to develop its list.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;This compilation of the world&#38;#39;s top first class lounges helps us to inform our clients as they are planning their international travels,&#38;quot; says Julia Graft, PR manager of FlyFirst. &#38;quot;Our service is dedicated in providing the largest discounts on luxury travel and the most available travel options, so the list helps our clients make more informed decisions on which lounges and airports offer the greater perks.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Taking the No. 1 spot on the FlyFirst list is Qantas Airways&#38;#39; lounge at the Sydney Airport. Sleek lines, gleaming surfaces, floor-to-ceiling windows and deluxe services are showcased in the flagship lounge. An enchanting living plant wall stretches 98 feet and brings life to the space envisioned by Australian designer Marc Newson. Travelers can luxuriate in the pampering services at the lounge&#38;#39;s Payot Spa, dine on delectable meals or relax in the 20,000 square foot library. The Qantas Sydney lounge offers sumptuous service and a welcoming ambiance that hits just the right note for FlyFirst luxury travelers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;In their quest to capture the luxury market, airlines are spending millions of dollars on on-board seating, contracting with world-renowned designers and chefs and creating over-the-top airport lounges,&#38;quot; Graft notes. &#38;quot;As a result, the airlines that reach the FlyFirst Top Five list are airlines, like Qantas and Lufthansa, that offer the most palatial lounges featuring the finest services and amenities.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Lufthansa, at No. 2, offers so many exclusive services to its Frankfurt first class passengers that its lounge encompasses an entire two-story terminal. Valets greet passengers at the entry, where personal assistants take care of check-in, security and travel details. Once inside the lounge area, travelers relax in supple armchairs, rest on daybeds in quiet rooms and refresh in shower suites. Hot and cold buffets, a la carte meals, an extensive wine selection and cooling cocktails offer enough variety to appeal to every palate, and a fully equipped business center helps travelers conduct last-minute business necessities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A perennial favorite, Qatar Airways is well-known for its refined first class service. Its flagship Doha Airport lounge is housed in its Premium Terminal, exclusive to first and business class travelers. Select passengers avail themselves of personal chauffeurs to the Premium Terminal, where they enjoy a serene ambiance, lounges filled with comfortable armchairs, fine dining, a global deli, cocktails, high tea, spa services and a host of other amenities created to pamper its discerning passengers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Refined elegance and gracious service are the hallmarks of Etihad and British Airways, at Nos. 4 and 5, respectively. At Abu Dhabi, Etihad&#38;#39;s Diamond First Class passengers relish the flawless meals, roomy lounges and business services, while first class passengers at British Airways&#38;#39; Concorde Room are greeted by large, glittering chandeliers and impeccable spa services.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap Business Class flights to Asia,discounted First Class fares,Best Business Class Deals</description><keywords>cheap Business Class flights to Asia,discounted First Class fares,Best Business Class Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>fc39ac67c9b84950a03f6fb07f5f4fe2.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>30b257a94dd04cbfa868e45bf722da32.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>32</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Class Announces top 5 Best Places to Visit in Europe. Save Thousands on Business &#38; First Class</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-First-Europe</alias><posted>6/30/2013 6:23:24 PM</posted><summary>With the summer travel season in full swing, FlyFirst announces its selection of the top five European towns to visit in 2013. Europe&#38;#39;s many vibrant cities, appealing landmarks and exciting recreation spots make it difficult for travelers to decide where to spend their time. To help international globetrotters, the travel experts at&#38;#160;FlyFirst&#38;#160;reviewed European destinations, noting airport and flight access, public transportation availability and compelling attractions, recreation and historic sites.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With the summer travel season in full swing, FlyFirst announces its selection of the top five European towns to visit in 2013. Europe&#38;#39;s many vibrant cities, appealing landmarks and exciting recreation spots make it difficult for travelers to decide where to spend their time. To help international globetrotters, the travel experts at&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business fare to Europe&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;reviewed European destinations, noting airport and flight access, public transportation availability and compelling attractions, recreation and historic sites.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst&#38;#39; Top Five&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/continent/Cheap-Business-Class-to-Europe&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Cheap First Class Fare&#34;&#62;European destinations&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;are world-class cities, each with its own trademark ambiance and rich cultural heritage. Beyond a wealth of historic sites, each Top Five city offers plenty of things to see and experience, whether travelers are there for two days, two weeks or two months.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Fresh off the heels of its successful 2012 Summer Olympic Games,&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/city/Cheap-Business-Class-Tickets-to-London&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap first class flight to London&#34;&#62;London&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;is primed and ready to welcome the world. At the No. 1 spot, London offers the largest airport system in the world, with convenient public transportation links to the city core. With four World Heritage sites, including the Tower of London and Westminster Palace, history buffs delight in London&#38;#39;s bountiful landmarks, castles and bridges. Visitors can explore art at Tate Modern, dine on ethnic dishes in the East End, savor a bird&#38;#39;s eye view of the city aboard the London Eye and enjoy a rousing play in the West End.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Picturesque Frankfurt is No. 2 on the FlyFirst Class list, and offers its own entrancing views and activities.&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/city/Cheap-First-Business-Class-Flight-to-Frankfurt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap last minute to Frankfurt&#34;&#62;Frankfurt&#60;/a&#62;boasts one of world&#38;#39;s busiest airports and provides plenty of public transportation options. Historic architecture in the old Altstadt distict and the medieval R&#38;ouml;mer provide a glimpse into Frankfurt&#38;#39;s illustrious past, while dozens of museums encourage visitors to explore the region&#38;#39;s progression of culture, art, industry and religion. Recreation is abundant in Frankfurt, particularly with its access to the 300-mile Main-Radweg bicycle path along the Main River.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The infamous City of Light is at No. 3, known for its well-planned streets, famed fashion houses, grand architecture and exquisite restaurants. More than 45 million tourists visit Paris each year, touring the Bastille, Versailles, Notre Dame Cathedral and the Tuileries Gardens. Perfumeries, couture apparel and top-of-the-line cosmetics create a shopper&#38;#39;s paradise. The celebrated Louvre is just one of dozens of notable museums scattered throughout the city. Sporting and community events keep Paris aflutter in summer months, including national Bastille Day; outdoor movie festival, Cinema en Plein Air; French Tennis Open and Tour de France.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Gorgeous Zurich, at No. 4, is both charmingly historic and alluringly modern. It is home to one of the best airports in the world and offers one of Switzerland&#38;#39;s largest passenger railway stations. Zurich is one of the continent&#38;#39;s wealthiest cities with bountiful culture, from the Swiss National Musuem and Kunsthaus to the Zurich Museum of Art. Historic guild houses line Munsterhof Square, prehistoric settlements are revealed at Enge Alpenquai and glorious Fraumunster Church overlooks Lake Zurich. With Lake Zurich nearby and the Limmat River traversing the city, countless recreation opportunities keep thrill-seeking tourists satisfied.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Rome, The Eternal City, rounds out the FlyFirst Class list. Visitors relish the city&#38;#39;s copious historic sites, including the Colosseum, Forum, Pantheon, Vatican City, St. Peter&#38;#39;s Basilica and Trevi Fountain. Rome&#38;#39;s city center is easily maneuvered on foot, but there is plenty of public transportation to aid travelers, from metro lines, buses and trams. Families particularly enjoy the city&#38;#39;s Children&#38;#39;s Museum, the Time Elevator, 3D Rewind and the zoo, Bioparco.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The travel specialists at&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;last minute cheap&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;encourage travelers to visit one or more of these Top Five world-class cities for fascinating adventures and enriching experiences. For information about traveling in affordable luxury to these and dozens of other alluring European cities, call FlyFirst at (888)347-7817 or view information online at FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>discount business class, cheap first class, save money discounts flights</description><keywords>cheap business class flight, discounted business cheap, last minute cheap tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>52c62a872f6a4958b1ab9588cbecb616.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0ee26243795f4695b2815accd25a1918.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>33</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Class Announces Airline Traffic Statistic for The Beginning of Summer 2013. Cheap Business Class Flights and Discounted First Class Tickets to Europe. </title><alias>Business-Class-First-Class-Cheap</alias><posted>6/30/2013 6:31:57 PM</posted><summary>With May airline travel statistics trickling in, FlyFirst announced today that it expects the 2013 summer travel season to be very robust and to offer a number of record deals on first and business class flights.Although travel figures for May 2013 include a mixed bag of slight passenger increases counterbalanced by modest decreases, most industry analysts predicted that this year&#38;#39;s summer months would be busy.&#38;#160;FlyFirst, a leading service specializing in reduced-fare first and business class air travel, carefully watches airline and travel trends to better serve its premium clientele.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;With May airline travel statistics trickling in, FlyFirst announced today that it expects the 2013 summer travel season to be very robust and to offer a number of record deals on first and business class flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Although travel figures for May 2013 include a mixed bag of slight passenger increases counterbalanced by modest decreases, most industry analysts predicted that this year&#38;#39;s summer months would be busy.&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.flyfirst.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;, a leading service specializing in reduced-fare first and business class air travel, carefully watches airline and travel trends to better serve its premium clientele.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Summer is traditionally the busiest leisure air travel season of the year,&#38;quot; notes Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst.com. &#38;quot;Airlines were very busy in the summer of 2012, and we expect similar or higher numbers of passengers during the 2013 summer season.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In spite of the high expectations for the coming summer travel season, May 2013 offered varied results for some of the world&#38;#39;s largest airlines. Delta Airlines, Southwest and Lufthansa all showed a slight increase in the number of enplaned passengers in May 2013, with 14.26 million, 12.043 million and 9.377 million passengers, respectively. United Airlines and American Airlines both showed slight decreases in passengers in the same month.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Since the economic recovery began, each summer travel season has shown progress. In 2010, U.S. carriers reported serving 201.4 million passengers from June to August, and in 2011, 204.3 million international and domestic passengers were served on U.S. airlines. In 2012, that number reached 205.3 million passengers. The organization representing U.S.-based air carriers, Airlines for America, forecast that the country&#38;#39;s airlines would serve nearly 209 million passengers in the summer of 2013.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;July is traditionally the busiest month of the summer season, and FlyFirst expects that trend to continue for the summer of 2013. Summer air travel is lightest in the&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/service/firstClass&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Cheap First Class&#34;&#62;first&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;two weeks in June and the last two weeks of August, when American schools are often in session.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Internationally, air passenger traffic has increased in recent years, growing by four percent in 2012,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;In particular, we are seeing significant growth in international travel to the Middle East and Asia, where economies are expanding and the high-end of leisure travel is burgeoning.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;This increased summer demand actually offers good news for travelers&#38;#39; pocketbooks. As international companies seek their own summer holidays, business travel throughout the world drops during the summer months. This decrease in demand for business and first class seats during the summer months leads to a significant drop in prices, opening the way for coach-fliers to afford luxury air travel.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;At FlyFirst.com, we offer some of our very best first and&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://flyfirst.com/service/businessClass&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class&#34;&#62;business class deals&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;to international and domestic destinations in the summertime,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;More unfilled capacity in the luxury airplane sections makes first and business class travel more accessible to a greater variety of budgets.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Currently, FlyFirst is booking luxury travel throughout the summer to a variety of international and domestic destinations at up to 70 percent off published fares.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Flights, business, first, discounted Flights Business Class, Last Minute </description><keywords>best business class deals, cheap first class fares, last minute discounted airlines , save money on business</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8a5b9bf198b6482db754778e6ce77e6e.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>1b362b79f7ef434ca6bf9ad1a5c03983.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>34</blog_id><title>Cheap First Class &#38; Discounted Business Class to Qatar</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flights-to-Qatar</alias><posted>7/1/2013 8:01:14 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Qatar, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Qatar. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;FlyFirst.com offers unparalleled discounts on first class fares and business class tickets to Singapore, saving you up to 70 percent off regular premium fares. With all that you will save on air travel to the Lion City, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty of funds to spend on enjoying Singapore&#38;#39;s exotic adventures.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Singapore.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Journey in style to the exotic land of Qatar with&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;affordable first class flights and discounted business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;from FlyFirst.com. Nearly surrounded by the brilliant turquoise waters of the Persian Gulf, Qatar offers modern cities, a deeply rooted culture and one of the fastest growing economies in the world.&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Capital city Doha offers a cross-cultural experience like no other. With the intensely blue bay as its backdrop, the city exudes modern achievements. Broad-laned roads curve along the coast, lined with palm trees and gleaming skyscrapers designed in a pleasing mix of contemporary glass and Moorish details.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you take in Doha&#38;#39;s modern wonders, escape to the more iconic Middle East views of Khor al Udeid beach, where the tan-colored rolling sand dunes meet the Persian Gulf and offer plenty of relaxation and recreation. Head about 24 miles southwest of Doha to experience the eerie sounds of the Singing Sand Dunes.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Explore the region&#38;#39;s culture and history at Doha&#38;#39;s many museums, such as the Museum of Islamic Art. Sample wares and foods of all kinds at the old, traditional marketplace, Souq Waqif. Travel out of Doha to scout around the famed archaeological dig at Al Zubarah, where an old fort, a once-thriving village and an ancient mosque have been unearthed. End your day with a serene stroll along Doha&#38;#39;s Corniche promenade for an amazing sunset view of the Gulf.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Flights Await in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Begin your sojourn to world-class Qatar in the spacious elegance of first or business class. Your pampering experience begins even before you leave the ground, with exclusive access to privileged airport lounges. Have a bite to eat, mingle with fellow luxury passengers or just relax with spa and salon services at these airport oases. As you enter your first or business class cabin, you&#38;#39;ll be greeted by gracious attendants who are devoted to your every comfort. Meals designed by world-famous chefs, free-flowing drinks, abundant entertainment options and bed turn-down service are just some of the amenities you&#38;#39;ll enjoy on your premium flight. By the time you reach Doha International Airport, you&#38;#39;ll be relaxed and eager to experience all of Qatar&#38;#39;s delights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled savings of up to 70 percent on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty of funds left in your budget to truly explore Qatar. We are leaders in the&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;industry, offering unmatched prices along with first-rate service. Our deeply&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;are available on all travel needs, including last minute flights, one-way tickets and multi-city trips. When you book your trip with FlyFirst.com, you can rest assured that you are getting the very best deal available on&#38;#160;&#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class fares to Qatar&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discount Business Class, Cheap First Class airline, best Deals Business Class</description><keywords>First Class Cheap, Business Class Fare, Last Minute First Class Discount</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>66534622633d432a93f43a3af36c5f88.jpg</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>2daeee3a0a694be1ba6ad6320aa3bf83.jpg</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>35</blog_id><title>New Tips For Cheap International Business Class &#38; Discounted First Class Travel</title><alias>Best-Deals-Business-Class</alias><posted>7/2/2013 6:14:44 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;A record-breaking 59 million international trips were made by Americans last year, and this year is shaping up to be similarly busy. To help Americans travel wisely, the travel experts at FlyFirst offer a few tips for traveling abroad this year.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Plan for airport delays. The current government sequester creates a number of cutbacks in Transportation Security Administration and U.S. Customs forces, leading to longer processing times at airports. Travelers should expect wait times for security and Customs checkpoints to double.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Use smart phones wisely. Travelers should check with cell phone companies to determine what roaming and other charges they may face while abroad. With a little planning, smart phone users can avoid roaming charges by unlocking their GSM-system smart phone and, while abroad, going to a local cell phone store to get a new SIM card and local phone number.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Research the destination. Travelers can avoid many mishaps simply by researching their destination countries. &#38;quot;Understanding the country&#38;#39;s laws, weather, political conditions and travel regulations can go a long way towards an enjoyable trip,&#38;quot; advises Julia Graft, PR manager for&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;first business class tickets&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;. &#38;quot;The U.S. Department of State maintains briefs on more than 200 countries, so it&#38;#39;s easy to get important, up-to-date information on foreign destinations.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Stay in touch. Traveling Americans should stay in contact with the State Department. Americans can submit their travel plans to the State Department&#38;#39;s Smart Traveler Enrollment Program so that the government can contact travelers in the event of a crisis.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Know insurance coverage. Travelers should check with their overseas medical insurance coverage. &#38;quot;Americans abroad should know what to do and where to go for a medical emergency,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;Also, some prescription drugs may not be allowed in the destination country, so travelers should check to see what medication restrictions are in place.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Notify credit card companies. It&#38;#39;s best to notify credit card companies of impending travel so that the companies&#38;#39; fraud monitors don&#38;#39;t inadvertently freeze credit accounts for unusual use.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Go to the local bank. Instead of using the money conversion centers in airports, travelers should go to a bank in the destination country. There, they can be assured of completely accurate exchanges and lower fees.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Avoid identity theft. Credit cards and passports are vulnerable to identify thieves using RFID scanners in busy airports and tourist attractions. Graft warns, &#38;quot;The scanners can pick up vital information embedded in passports and credit cards just by passing in close proximity to the items, so it&#38;#39;s important to keep them stored in a RFID-proof wallet.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Don&#38;#39;t use debit cards. While abroad, travelers should use credit cards rather than debit cards. If a debit card number is stolen while abroad, the traveler&#38;#39;s liability on any fraudulent use is $500, versus $50 for most credit cards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With a little bit of planning and research,&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap last minute flights&#34;&#62;international travel&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;can be full of exciting adventures and interesting experiences. For more help in planning a trip abroad, consult with a knowledgeable travel company.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap International Business Class Tickets, Discounted First Class Fare, Best Deals Business Class</description><keywords>Business Class Travel, Cheap First Class Flights, Discounted business fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>27154fe211e546759d26445641e18b21.jpg</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ca231bb51fc7442aa4b05836699a93af.jpg</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>36</blog_id><title>The Best Price on Last Minute Business Class Flights &#38; Discounted First Class Fares  </title><alias>Cheap-Last-Minute-Business-Flights-Discount</alias><posted>7/3/2013 8:01:53 PM</posted><summary>Cheap Last Minute&#38;#160;Business Class flights, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The travel experts at FlyFirst want to dispel the common myth that&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;first class fares discount business class&#34;&#62;last-minute&#60;/a&#62;, business class and first-class travel costs can&#38;#39;t fit into a tight budget. As the busy summer travel season approaches, FlyFirst experts offer their tips for securing inexpensive last-minute and business class flights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;First, less expensive last-minute flights are more readily available to those travelers who do their research. Some airlines offer getaway specials or last-minute flights on their individual websites. American Airlines, for instance, offers getaway deals for the next weekend to both international and domestic destinations. Similarly, other airlines such as United,&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class tcikets&#34;&#62;Virgin America&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;and Southwest offer website deals, often within a short time frame. Travelers should remember to look at low-cost airlines such as JetBlue and Southwest.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To achieve the best last-minute flight savings, it&#38;#39;s critical to be flexible on the details. Being willing to travel mid-week, early in the morning or late at night and to less-traveled airports may make a significant difference on the overall flight price. &#38;quot;Travelers should look at flying into smaller airports near their destination,&#38;quot; advises Julia Graft, PR manager for FlyFirst. &#38;quot;Oakland International Airport and San Jose International Airport are both great alternatives to San Francisco International and offer equally quick access to Bay Area towns, but they are frequently less expensive.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;When it comes to &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first-class travel&#60;/strong&#62;, there are several ways to save. Those looking to travel within the next few months are in luck, since one of the best ways to save on business class travel is to book travel during the height of tourist season. &#38;quot;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business deals to asia&#34;&#62;Business travel&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;often slows down during the summer months, so prices on business class seats often drop dramatically during that time,&#38;quot; says Graft.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Using a travel concierge site like FlyFirstis helpful, as well, since those sites often provide &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; of up to 60 percent off retail prices, they negotiate flight ticket prices for travelers and offer price match guarantees.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For best prices, travel to more business-focused cities rather than tourist destinations, since there are usually more &#60;strong&#62;business-class&#60;/strong&#62; seat offerings to business capitals. &#60;strong&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; to Melbourne are significantly cheaper than flights to Sydney, and traveling &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; to Milan is less expensive than traveling to Rome.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Getting creative on travel itineraries is also important. To save the most on business-class seats, travelers should be willing to use connecting flights or even switch airlines at a connecting point, particularly for international travel. &#38;quot;The key here,&#38;quot; Graft notes, &#38;quot;is to do plenty of homework to find the best deal on business travel. The rewards and savings can be well worth the time.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;quot;Traveling last-minute or via business class, doesn&#38;#39;t have to break the bank,&#38;quot; Graft concludes. &#38;quot;If travelers follow these simple tips, lower cost last-minute and business class airfare is easily accessible even for pleasure travelers.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Best Business Class Deals, Discounted First Class Fares, Cheap Business Class , last minute flights</description><keywords>Last Minute, first class, cheap business class, first class tickets, first class flights., business class deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>94535d1ad3c34d99b5aaa60e51fc34d9.jpg</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>aee88eb50b7f44a8b1081ad0404e9518.jpg</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>37</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Announces the Top Business Class Seats. Cheap Business Class Fare &#38; Discounted First Class Flights </title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-Cheap</alias><posted>7/9/2013 8:45:51 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;To help guide business travelers in selecting the most comfortable business class seating, the travel experts at FlyFirst announce their top picks for international business class seats.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The quality of airline&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class&#34;&#62;business class&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;seats can greatly affect business travelers&#38;#39; productivity. Most professionals who fly business class do so to work and rest more easily, so it follows that privacy, work space, storage and sleeping comfort are all important factors in selecting business flights. To help guide business travelers in selecting the most comfortable business class seating, the travel experts at FlyFirst announce their top picks for international business class seats.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;New seats that lie completely flat are the new hallmark of quality business class seating. &#38;quot;To do well in this competitive business class market, many airlines, such as Asiana Airlines and Austrian Air, are upgrading their business class cabins to include luxury full-flat seats,&#38;quot; says FlyFirst PR Manager Julia Graft. Austrian Air&#38;#39;s new long-haul cabins, for example, feature full-flat beds with an air cushion system, built-in seat massage and extra storage/work space.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;first class business class&#34;&#62;Cathay Pacific&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    At 82 inches fully extended, Cathay Pacific&#38;#39;s business class seats are some of the longest in the industry. Width extensions offer additional hip support and the storage space provides room for knees while side-sleeping. While upright, a touch of a lever easily moves seats to provide extra comfort while working or visiting with other passengers. Privacy is extended with a cabinet door.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Qatar Airlines&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    A four-year winner of the World Travel Awards for best business class, Qatar Airlines offers its business class travelers a mattress-topped full-flat bed, pajamas and cozy eye shades. Video screens and movie selections are large, USB ports are easily accessible and the food and beverage offerings are first-rate.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Oman Air&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Privacy and comfort are the trademark features of Oman&#38;#39;s business class cabins. The long full-flat seats are enhanced with mattresses and high-quality sheets and duvets. Airbus 330 business class cabins feature just four seats across and high sides for extra privacy. Oman Air earned best business class seat, World Airline Awards.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Virgin Atlantic&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Full-flat beds with down duvets and full-size pillows make Virgin Atlantic&#38;#39;s business class seats a good bet for travelers who want to sleep in-flight. Most of Virgin&#38;#39;s aircraft have business class cabins filled with individual seat pods arranged in a unique herringbone configuration. The set-up provides direct access to the aisle from every seat.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;cheap business class fares&#34;&#62;Singapore Airlines&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Mostly known for its outstanding business class service and first-class dining, Singapore Airlines earned the 2012 World Travel Award for best airline business class. Most of the air carrier&#38;#39;s business class seats are wide and offer comfortable, full-flat seats with mattress toppers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;As with any type of flight, it&#38;#39;s important for travelers to do a little research to find the business class that best fits their particular needs. &#38;quot;Business travelers who are flying during daylight hours may want to select a business class that offers the most work and storage space rather than worry about getting a full-flat bed,&#38;quot; says Graft. &#38;quot;On the other hand, business people who are flying overnight should look for airlines offering the roomiest, most comfortable beds.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Business Discounts, Last Minute Cheap First Discounts Fare, Business Deals</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to Asia, First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7c56e3ab48884c74b57bbe1601d4c18a.jpg</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ea04c7858e9748eca2553d044976fe4e.jpg</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>38</blog_id><title>Discounted First Class Fare &#38; Last Minute Business Class. Top 10 Best Airports in USA</title><alias>Last-Minute-Business-Class-Deals</alias><posted>7/13/2013 4:41:42 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap International Business Class and First Class Tickets. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business travelers&#60;/strong&#62; can benefit from avoiding the busiest U.S. airports and using smaller, regional airports instead, according to new research by the experts at FlyFirst (FF). To help guide&#60;strong&#62; business travelers&#60;/strong&#62; in planning flights, the business travel specialists at FF developed a list of the best, most efficient U.S. airports. The &#38;quot;Top 10 Best U.S. Airports for Business Travelers&#38;quot; list was developed by examining continental U.S. airports&#38;#39; canceled and delayed flight rates within a 30-day period.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;BCA&#38;#39;s top 10 best airports for business travelers are:&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    1. Rochester International (ROC)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    2. Richmond International (RIC)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    3. Buffalo/Niagra International (BUF)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    4. Port Columbus International (CMH)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    5. Memphis International (MEM)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    6. Indianapolis International (IND)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    7. Pittsburgh International (PIT)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    8. Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky (CVG)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    9. Nashville Metropolitan (BNA)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    10. Lambert-St. Louis (STL)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    HONORABLE MENTION*:&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Westchester County (HPN)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Bradley International (BDL)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    Hancock International (SYR)&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    *Ranked on departure data only, no arrival information available.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The airports ranking high on the list were the airports with the fewest delayed or canceled flights. Using the total number of canceled and delayed departures and arrivals for each airport, FF rated the airports with two scores: the canceled-flight score, which is the mean number of cancellations for the past 30 days and the delayed-flight score, which is the mean number of departure and arrival delays.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FF added the honorable mention category to acknowledge the three airports with low rates of delayed and canceled departures. FF could not average the scores or rank the three airports in the overall list because the airports lack arrival statistics.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The No. 1 priority of business travelers is to get to their destinations on schedule. Always focused on the business traveler&#38;#39;s needs, FF develops its &#38;quot;best&#38;quot; and &#38;quot;worst&#38;quot; lists with that top criterion in mind, says FF Marketing Director Julia Graft. That focus applies to the Top 10 Airports list which rates each airport on the issue most important to business travelers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FF is designed to provide the best possible deals for domestic business travelers, which includes determining multiple choices for air carriers, air fares and routes. Similarly, on-time departures, connections and arrivals figure into that analysis of the best options for travelers. Graft points out that the large, obvious airport is not always the best airport. If the destination is the metropolitan D.C. area, for instance, travelers might consider bypassing the crowded Dulles Airport and use Richmond Airport (RIC) instead. For travel to the New York City area, Westchester County Airport is a great alternative to the heavily used and congested JFK, LaGuardia and Newark airports. Travelers to New England should consider using Bradley International Airport near Hartford, Conn., for its simplified access instead of complicated Logan Airport in Boston.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The Top 10 Best Airports list is also useful in determining options for connecting flights. Using smaller Midwest airports, such as Cincinnati (CVG), Port Columbus (CMH), Nashville (BNA) and Memphis (MEM), may save time over busy airports like O&#38;#39;Hare, where delays and cancellations are 10 times higher than at the top FF best airports.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Graft concludes that the FF research shows that bigger airports are not always the best choices, particularly when smaller airports may help travelers save time and deliver them to their meetings and offices on schedule. For that reason, Graft says, FF is pleased to provide the list of top performing airports for the business traveler.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Last Minute First Class Fare, Cheap Business Class Airline Tickets, Discounted Business Fares </description><keywords>Best Business Class, Last Minute First Class Fares, Cheap Business Class Airline Flights, Last Minute First Class Airfare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6cb8453b5e7848a09879e80a1f7ddae0.jpg</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9e722a0665b14d2a92dac951fcfb5d39.jpg</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>39</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare &#38; Last Minute First Class Tickets.  FlyFirst Announces Very Important New Tips and Regulation For Travelers</title><alias>Business-Class-Last-Minute-Flights</alias><posted>7/14/2013 6:34:59 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;last minute business class ticket&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;insists that travelers follow the rules and regulations when flying abroad.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travelers should familiarize themselves with their destinations, both to get the most enjoyment out of the visit and to avoid known dangers. Travelers should also be aware of restrictions on items that may be taken overseas (see &#38;#8220;Bringing Medications or Filling Prescriptions Abroad,&#38;#8221; below) and even on items that may be brought into the U.S. upon return (see &#38;#8220;Customs and Import Restrictions,&#38;#8221; below). More information resources follow:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The Consular Information Program&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The Consular Information Program consists of three main components that provide information to the American public about travel to specific countries: Country Specific Information, Travel Warnings and Travel Alerts. The U.S. Department of State issues fact sheets called Country Specific Information on over 200 countries. The sheets contain information on entry requirements, crime and security conditions, and areas of instability, road safety and other details relevant to travel.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The Department of State also issues Travel Warnings and Travel Alerts.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel warnings are issued when the State Department recommends deferral of travel by Americans to a country because of civil unrest, dangerous conditions, terrorist activity and, in some cases, because the U.S. has no diplomatic relations with the country and may have great difficulty in assisting Americans in distress. Travel Alerts are issued as a means to disseminate information quickly about terrorist threats and other relatively short-term or transnational conditions that could pose significant risks to American travelers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;How to Obtain Country Specific Information, Travel Warnings and Travel Alerts&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Country Specific Information,Travel Warnings and Travel Alerts are updated regularly and are accessible through the State Department&#38;#8217;s travel information website. For specific questions regarding an emergency involving an American citizen overseas, contact the Office of Overseas Citizens Services at (202) 647-5225&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are three ways to access Country Specific Information,Travel Warnings and Travel Alerts:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;On the Internet:&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://travel.state.gov/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#62;http://travel.state.gov&#60;/a&#62;.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    By Fax: on a fax machine, dial 202-647-3000 and follow the voice prompts.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    By Telephone: dial (888) 407-4747 from within the U.S., or, from overseas, (202) 501-4444 . These numbers are available from 8:00 a.m. to 8:00 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday (except U.S. federal holidays).&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Background Notes&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Background Notes are factual publications that contain information on countries with which the United States has diplomatic relations. They include facts on each country&#38;#8217;s land, people, history, government, political conditions, economy, and relations with other countries and the United States.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.iflyfirstclass.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;discounted cheap business and first class deals&#34;&#62;FlyFirst&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;hopes that that information will help travelers arrange and be prepared for next trip.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst team is attentive to every aspect of your travel needs, working in conjunction with our customers to ensure the business or first class travel itinerary is completed on time and on budget.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class Flights, First Class Discount, Last Minute Business Fare </description><keywords>Business Class Cheap, First Class Airline Flights, Discounted Fares Business Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f4a410bed2dd49389f24114ef242c9c8.jpg</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>227613191ac04b8295628facd3145ab2.jpg</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>41</blog_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights to Singapore, Best Deals on First Class. Save Thousands on Cheap Business Class Tickets. </title><alias>Last-Minute-Cheap-Business-Class-to-Asia</alias><posted>7/16/2013 4:19:33 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;FlyFirst, a leading &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62; specialist, announced today that premium flights to the island nation of Singapore are now significantly reduced. FlyFirst&#38;#39;s new fare deals apply to luxurious first class flights and spacious &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets &#60;/strong&#62;to Singapore, pending availability. The discounted fares offer savings as high as 70 percent and are valid on flights booked by August 26, 2013, for travel anytime.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The savings are most significant for &#60;strong&#62;first class travelers&#60;/strong&#62;, who enjoy fares to The Lion City for as little as $4,260. That pricing translates into a savings of more than $8,000 on most published &#60;strong&#62;airfares to Singapore&#60;/strong&#62;; regular first class fares to New York City and San Francisco range from $12,800 to $13,100.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;strong&#62;First class travelers&#60;/strong&#62; delight in consummate comfort, with services frequently including complimentary transfers to and from the airport, exclusive access to choice airport lounges, on-board meal service designed by acclaimed chefs, bed turn-down service and designer amenities. With &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, passengers also appreciate expedited queues that reduce frustrating airport wait times.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Equally compelling deals are available for amenity-rich business class fares. FlyFirst now offers fares as low as $3,480, pending availability. A regular business class flight from New York City to Singapore is $6,980, so the FlyFirst fare saves travelers more than $3,000. Business class travel regularly includes access to well-appointed airport lounges, expedited boarding queues, on-board personal entertainment systems, high-end cuisine and spacious seats designed to accommodate working and resting.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst&#38;#39;s new, reduced fares are &#60;strong&#62;available&#60;/strong&#62; on a variety of top airlines, including the highly acclaimed Singapore Airlines. Consistently ranked in the top three best airlines in the world, Singapore Airlines offers a variety of upscale amenities. Its new &#60;strong&#62;first class cabins&#60;/strong&#62; showcase extra-wide seats that convert to the largest beds available, a fresh and extensive gourmet menu and the sky&#38;#39;s widest personal LCD screens for on-demand entertainment.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;We are thrilled to offer these new discounts on premium travel to Singapore,&#38;quot; says Julia Graft, FlyFirst PR manager. &#38;quot;An increasing number of people are traveling to the country for business and pleasure, and these new FlyFirst fares make it affordable for travelers to make the 19-hour flight to Singapore in the luxurious comfort of first and business class.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Opportunities abound for those who travel to &#60;strong&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62; and the Malay Peninsula. One of the original Four Asian Tigers, Singapore boasts the fourth largest financial center in the world, a vibrant shipping industry, more than 7,000 international corporations and the fifth busiest shipping port in the world. As a result, business and corporate travel to the island nation is at an all-time high.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Singapore also attracts millions of pleasure travelers to its city-state each year, enticed by its dynamic casino resorts, plentiful shopping and robust medical tourism industry. &#38;quot;Our new business and first class fares to &#60;strong&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62; are especially appealing to pleasure travelers who might ordinarily travel in more-crowded coach class,&#38;quot; Graft says. &#38;quot;The deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62; open luxury travel to an entirely new group of travelers, even families with children who would benefit from the extra space and services.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more information about FlyFirst&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62; to &#60;strong&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62; and other international destinations, contact FlyFirst by telephone at (888)347-7817 or online at www.FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discounted Last Minute To Singapore, Cheap First Class Airline Tickets, Cheap Business To Asia, Cheap Business Class</description><keywords>First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class, Discounted Business Class Fare, Cheap Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7fb3a2f65a1344e78a30eb281a4b30bb.jpg</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>baf882e91fed46dc8f288cb4f4879ad8.jpg</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>42</blog_id><title>Discounted Deals on Last Minute Business &#38; First Class Fares, Cheap First Class Fares</title><alias>Last-Minute-Business-Class-Flight-Deals</alias><posted>7/19/2013 10:00:14 AM</posted><summary>Cheap Business Class to Asia, Last Minute First Class Tickets,&#38;#160;FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Last minute luxury airfare&#60;/strong&#62; to Asia and Europe just dropped to incredible levels, reports FlyFirst, a leading premium travel provider. Today, FlyFirst announced the new discounted airfare for &#60;strong&#62;last minute travel&#60;/strong&#62; in &#60;strong&#62;business and first class&#60;/strong&#62; cabins booked by August 26, 2013, as available.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;These new last minute deals on &#60;strong&#62;first and business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; are available at the perfect time,&#38;quot; says Graft. &#38;quot;International travel is escalating and families are searching for deals on summer travel. Offering deals like these on last minute flights is especially helpful for families trying to fit in a trip before most North American kids head back to school.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Travelers heading to Asia at the spur of the moment can expect to pay as little as $3,370 for business class and $4,430 for first class. Regular business class fares to popular Asian destinations can range from $6,980 to as much as $21,000. Ordinary first class rates to Asia vary from $13,800 to about $27,000, thousands of dollars more expensive than the newly released discounts at FlyFirst.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Asia, already a frequent destination for business travelers, is quickly becoming a popular vacation spot for North American pleasure travelers. Japan; Southeast Asian countries such as Myanmar, Cambodia and Lao and South Asia&#38;#39;s India and the Maldives all report significant increases in international arrivals at their respective airports, according to the&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://www.pata.org/press/pata-2012-was-a-record-year-for-asia-pacific-tourism&#34;&#62;Pacific Asia Travel Association&#38;#39;s&#60;/a&#62;&#38;#160;March 7 report on 2012 travel. &#38;quot;Whether our customers are traveling to Seoul, South Korea, to attend to business interests, or to Thailand to explore inviting beaches and roam historic sites, the new discounts offer new opportunities for travel,&#38;quot; says FlyFirst Public Relations Manager Julia Graft.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;strong&#62;Last minute European deals&#60;/strong&#62; are just as significant. While regular business class tickets to Europe hover in the range of $6,000 to $8,000, FlyFirst&#38;#39;s new last minute deals offer &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; as low as $2,840. Similarly, under the new discount sale, first class travelers to Europe can expect fares to come as cheaply as $3,570.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Always a popular &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; and pleasure destination for Americans and Canadians, Europe is the top destination for U.S. travelers. More than 18 percent of all U.S. international travel was made to Europe, according to the&#38;#160;&#60;a href=&#34;http://tinet.ita.doc.gov/view/m-2012-O-001/index.html&#34;&#62;U.S. Department of Commerce Office of Tourism &#38;amp; Travel Industries&#60;/a&#62;. The next closest destination was the Caribbean, with 10.6 percent of the market share.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Frankfurt, London, Paris, Barcelona and Amsterdam are all top European destinations for business travelers and vacationers alike. Each city is home to a vibrant business district, operates robust financial centers and offers a large international airport. Each also features stellar landmarks, historic sites and attractions that appeal to visitors from around the world.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Although several airlines announced recent drops in first class and business class ticket prices, some came under fire because the tickets required advance purchase of at least 60 days. That&#38;#39;s not the case on the latest round of summer sales at FlyFirst, since the newest &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; are available for last minute luxury flights.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more than eight years, FlyFirst has offered unparalleled deals on &#60;strong&#62;first and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; of all kinds, from last minute and one-way trips to multi-city destinations. For more information about &#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62; luxury &#60;strong&#62;flight deals&#60;/strong&#62;, contact FlyFirst at (888)347-7817 or www.FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Last Minute Business Class Tickets, First Class Last Minute, Cheap Business Class Fare, Discount Best Deals Flight</description><keywords>Discounts, Flights, Cheap Flights Business, First Class Airfare Cheap, Cheap Business Class Airfares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>9a00bd1f1f834a84a5a227a1ba0ca4da.jpg</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>b8da74811f7e43b7a3aec49ebde78a7d.jpg</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>43</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flights to Seoul. Last Minute First Class to Seoul</title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-Cheap-to-Seoul</alias><posted>7/20/2013 5:03:51 PM</posted><summary>Luxury travel specialist FlyFirst announced today that it is offering newly Luxury travel specialist FlyFirst announced today that it is offering newly&#38;#160;discounted first&#38;#160;and&#38;#160;business class flights to Seoul, South Korea. With prices for first class fares at about $4,370 and business class fares at about $3,280, the new discounts will save travelers thousands of dollars on&#38;#160;luxury flights&#38;#160;when booked by August 26, 2013, on flights any time.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Luxury travel specialist FlyFirst announced today that it is offering newly Luxury travel specialist FlyFirst announced today that it is offering newly &#60;strong&#62;discounted first&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class flights to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62;, South Korea. With prices for first class fares at about $4,370 and business class fares at about $3,280, the new discounts will save travelers thousands of dollars on &#60;strong&#62;luxury flights&#60;/strong&#62; when booked by August 26, 2013, on flights any time.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Julia Graft, public relations manager for FlyFirst notes, &#38;quot;These are some of the &#60;strong&#62;best luxury fares&#60;/strong&#62; we have seen in a long time. We are delighted to be able to offer the new discounted business and &#60;strong&#62;first class fares to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62; to our customers.&#38;quot;&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Some of FlyFirst&#38;#39;s best deals of the season are available on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62;. The &#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst cost as little as $4,370, as available; &#60;strong&#62;regular first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; from the United States to &#60;strong&#62;Seoul&#60;/strong&#62; can rate as high as $27,103. Those &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; translate into potential price savings of about $22,000.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The pinnacle of luxury flight, &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; often provide travelers with ground transportation, invitation to some of the world&#38;#39;s most accommodating airport lounges, salon or spa services, extensive seasonal and regionally flavored dining menus, deluxe bed turn-down service and myriad other pampering benefits.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For those who prefer traveling in &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;, the deals are equally economical. Passengers can purchase business class tickets for as little as $3,280, availability permitting. Ordinary &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from the United States to Seoul can cost as much as $21,687 when booked through other travel services.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    While not as lavishly accessorized as first class travel, business class passengers often receive benefits nearly as extensive as &#60;strong&#62;first class&#60;/strong&#62;. Many &#60;strong&#62;special business class&#60;/strong&#62; airport lounges offer buffets, refreshments, fully-equipped business centers, entertainment areas and serene rest zones.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;FlyFirst is proud to offer the &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;luxury flights to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62; on some of the world&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;best airlines&#60;/strong&#62;,&#38;quot; says Graft. &#38;quot;Both Korean Air and Asian Airlines are based in Korea and frequently earn high marks at the annual World Airline Awards. Both airlines are known for outstanding service and deluxe cabin accommodations.&#38;quot;&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Korean Air placed in the top 10 for the best first class seats and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; in last month&#38;#39;s SkyTrax World Airline Awards. &#60;strong&#62;Korean Air&#38;#39;s first class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers on certain flights enjoy the top-of-the-line Kosmo Suite seats. The Kosmo Suite offers enhanced privacy in a spacious pod outfitted with over-sized seats. The footrest and back support can be adjusted to any angle at the touch of a button and converts to a completely flat bed to promote restful sleep on long flights. An on-demand entertainment system features a large 23-inch LCD monitor and premium BOSE headset. All of the incredible first class seats are designed to help passengers make the most of their 11 - to 14-hour flight time to Seoul.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The new deals on premium travel to Seoul are available through FlyFirst, one of the leading business and first class travel specialists. For more information about the special pricing to Seoul, luxury travel or first and business class flights to other international destinations, contact FlyFirst by telephone at (888)347-7817 or online at www.FlyFirst.com.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Seoul Business Class, Last Minute Flights To Seoul, First Class To Seoul, Discounted Deals Business Class</description><keywords>Seoul, Cheap Business Class, Last Minute Flights, First Class AirFares, Cheap Flights Business</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>d89d9a8bf2874a2e9ce563ee8431a506.jpg</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d431a66bdf4c401ab3d91555a43224db.jpg</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>44</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight to Germany, Save on Discounted First Class to Frankfurt</title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-Germany</alias><posted>7/21/2013 8:31:24 PM</posted><summary>Luxury flights from the United States to&#38;#160;Germany&#38;#160;are now available at significantly lower prices. FlyFirst, a leading&#38;#160;luxury travel service, announced today that it will offer new&#38;#160;discounts&#38;#160;on&#38;#160;first and business class flights to Frankfurt, Munich, D&#38;uuml;sseldorf and Berlin. Although the&#38;#160;discounted travel&#38;#160;can occur at any time, flights must be booked by August 26, 2013. Discounts are subject to availability.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Luxury flights from the United States to &#60;strong&#62;Germany&#60;/strong&#62; are now available at significantly lower prices. FlyFirst, a leading &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel service&#60;/strong&#62;, announced today that it will offer new &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;first and business class flights to Frankfurt&#60;/strong&#62;, Munich, D&#38;uuml;sseldorf and Berlin. Although the &#60;strong&#62;discounted travel&#60;/strong&#62; can occur at any time, flights must be booked by August 26, 2013. Discounts are subject to availability.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With the newly released &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, spacious &#60;strong&#62;business class seats to Germany&#60;/strong&#62; are as little as $2,680. &#38;quot;We are elated to offer these new discounts to travelers around the world,&#38;quot; says FlyFirst Public Relations Manager Julia Graft. &#38;quot;In comparison, ordinary &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; from Los Angeles to Frankfurt can run as high as $7,403. Many of our &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; and vacation travelers try to stick to a strict flight budget, so we are thrilled to be able to offer the space and service of &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; for about a third of the regular cost.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In luxurious &#60;strong&#62;first class&#60;/strong&#62;, travelers can expect to receive similarly &#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62; through August 26. Regular &#60;strong&#62;first class airfare&#60;/strong&#62; from Los Angeles to Frankfurt on popular &#60;strong&#62;Lufthansa&#60;/strong&#62; can cost as much as $8,077. Through its new, limited-time sale, first class fares to &#60;strong&#62;Germany&#60;/strong&#62; can be as low as $3,640.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;Whether travelers choose the &#60;strong&#62;business class discounts&#60;/strong&#62; or the deeply &#60;strong&#62;reduced fares on first class to Germany&#60;/strong&#62;, they can expect to receive exceptional services and amenities throughout their premium travel experience,&#38;quot; notes Graft. The new deals are available on a variety of top airlines, including Germany&#38;#39;s award-winning Lufthansa.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;quot;Many of our passengers who choose &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; aboard Lufthansa are in for a real treat,&#38;quot; Graft says. Last month, Lufthansa earned several awards for its &#60;strong&#62;first class&#60;/strong&#62; accommodations, including first place in &#60;strong&#62;best first class&#60;/strong&#62; lounge from SkyTrax&#38;#39; World Airline Awards. &#60;strong&#62;First class&#60;/strong&#62; travelers to or through &#60;strong&#62;Frankfurt &#60;/strong&#62;enjoy a completely separate first class terminal offering chauffeur ground transportation and valet service; a personal assistant; lounges with armchairs, sofas and &#38;quot;relax&#38;quot; chairs; quiet rooms with daybeds; abundant cocktails, a buffet and an a la carte menu; fully equipped office units and assistance through security lines. The company also earned second place for its first class dining experience and placed in the top five for best first class cabins and &#60;strong&#62;best first class seats&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;strong&#62;Business class travelers&#60;/strong&#62; also receive their share of incredible comforts and amenities on international flights to &#60;strong&#62;Germany&#60;/strong&#62;. Passengers in business class can expect to enjoy more spacious on-board seating, personal on-demand entertainment systems, stellar cuisine and a variety of reserved airport lounges, depending on the airline they choose and their destination airport.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    FlyFirst has specialized in providing lower-cost international and domestic travel in luxury classes for more than eight years. Once a company dedicated to serving government officials, highly placed executives and celebrities, FlyFirst recently opened its services to the general public.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more information about &#60;strong&#62;discounted business and first class flights to Germany&#60;/strong&#62; and other European destinations, contact FlyFirst by telephone at (888)347=7817 or online at www.FlyFirst.com.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Cheap to Germany, First Class to Germany,Last Minute Business Class to Germany. Cheap First Class Airfares</description><keywords>Business Class Ticket To Germany, First Class Flight, Cheap Business Class Airfares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>242f0dd83fcb4fa997f754fb991b1604.jpg</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0585eac705824e7699bd8a91db817bb2.jpg</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>45</blog_id><title>FlyFirst Offers Unbeatable Business &#38; First Class Tickets Price for INternational Travel </title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-First-Deal</alias><posted>7/25/2013 9:14:13 AM</posted><summary>Finding a&#38;#160;last minute flight tickets&#38;#160;can be a real challenge, if you do not know where to look. If you act quickly and conduct precise research, you can easily find a service provider of&#38;#160;cheap business class flight&#38;#160;tickets. You can be assured that they do not charge additional rate for the &#38;ldquo;last minute&#38;rdquo; deal, but levy the same rates that help you and other travelers save a considerable amount of money.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Finding a &#60;strong&#62;last minute flight tickets&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#160;can be a real challenge, if you do not know where to look. If you act quickly and conduct precise research, you can easily find a service provider of &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; tickets. You can be assured that they do not charge additional rate for the &#38;#8220;last minute&#38;#8221; deal, but levy the same rates that help you and other travelers save a considerable amount of money.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The service providers are devoted to offer their customers reduced-fare first class and business class tickets on all major airlines. Opting for their assistance can help you locate best deals on luxury international flights to exhilarating destinations. &#60;strong&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; constantly transport travelers to and from locations like Singapore, Hong Kong and Seoul, to name a few. Deep discounts are available on these flights for one-way, round-trip, last-minute, round the city and multi-city trips. You can enjoy premium travel by simultaneously saving a considerable amount of money on &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; tickets.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The number of passengers who take flights has increased with each passing day. Even their preferences have changed, as some have promoted themselves from traveling in economy class to the business class. The rate on tickets available for the latter option is a tad expensive than the former one. However, overall comparison shows that you are saving a good amount of money on your expenditure by finding a reputed service provider. Traveling choices have drastically changed and individuals are becoming price sensitive. By conducting a detailed research, they can easily locate &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets that give them good value for money.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;International carriers are constantly competing to gain the top spot among air commuters and improve their reputation. This has led to the massive availability of &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; tickets. Once you get your hands on these tickets, you can enjoy your traveling experience in a much roomier and amenity-filled flight in the comfort of the &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;. The crew staff provides uplifting refreshments, sophisticated cocktails, mouthwatering cuisine and appetizing snacks for all passengers. The &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; even have massage functions that allow you to take care of your muscles while on the flight. Restful sleeping is also possible. The amenities that you find on these flights will definitely provide you a cherishing experience.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;It is important for you to know that there are many service providers that offer assistance with &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. They share good relations with several airlines that move passengers from one location to another. If you desire to experience the luxury of traveling in first class, make sure that you conduct the essential research. You can find a variety of complementary deals that can help you save more on the flight tickets. The exclusive service of finding &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; tickets is easy to use and can be undertaken instantly. In case of any queries regarding the flights or the rates charged on the tickets, feel free to contact the customer service professionals. The experience will be worth the money.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>First Class Fares, Discounted Business Class Airline, Best Deals to Asia, Last Minute Business Class Fares </description><keywords>First Class Deals, Last Minute Class Fares, Cheap Flights Business, Discounted First Class Fares </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b6d080cfb17746b19cb8e63a6d085fb3.jpg</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>73c8cf4c95a74d09a0808517685fde81.jpg</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>46</blog_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights, Best Deals on First Class. Save Thousands on Cheap Business Class Tickets. </title><alias>First-Class-Cheap-Business-Fare</alias><posted>7/29/2013 7:08:40 PM</posted><summary>Statistically speaking, air travel is the safest mode of transport available. This is evident in the marked increase in the number of people flying every day. One of the main reasons seems to have been the amenities provided by&#38;#160;business class flights&#38;#160;at rates which were not imaginable before. The whole concept of this class began with the introduction of long tedious commercial flights
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Securing Business Class Flights at Low Rates&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Statistically speaking, air travel is the safest mode of transport available. This is evident in the marked increase in the number of people flying every day. One of the main reasons seems to have been the amenities provided by &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; at rates which were not imaginable before. The whole concept of this class began with the introduction of long tedious commercial flights. Planes that covered a distance across the globe needed to be at their best and providing the best services to their passengers. This was because long hours of journey can get many people irritated and restless. This eventually leads to an unhappy journey with a promise to never fly again. With the introduction of facilities like TV, Wifi, recliner beds, on board alcohol and many others, this class picked up pace to the extent that everyone wanted it. The big demand made the prices shoot up, only affordable to relatively well-off passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Times have changed since and securing cheap &#60;strong&#62;business class flights &#60;/strong&#62;is now not that difficult. Several travel agencies online provide you with the best deals available. Finding such airlines is no hard task and a quick research on the web can take you to a world full of discounts. Many companies across the web provide you with services such as &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights. &#60;/strong&#62;Many a times, in case of emergency, people need to leave as soon as possible. However, this means paying almost double the actual rates. Companies have found an alternative method and now provide for emergency tickets at almost the same rate. This has in fact become a growing trend. Booking tickets late, to get the best deal is often used as a strategy to secure empty seats at less than the original cost.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Air travel has become very common, from children to adults all have or want to take a flight to some part of the world or country. With the price of &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; falling as low as some of the &#60;strong&#62;Cheap First Class Ticket, &#60;/strong&#62;air travel has surely become a luxurious experience. Businessmen today have corporate ties with airline companies. They pay on a yearly basis to make their executives reach different places around the globe conformably. Satisfaction of your own employee guarantees instant success and travel agencies that offer low rates are a way to achieve this.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With a little bit of tact, regular vacationers have mastered the art of getting &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; at a very reasonable rate. These tactics may include last minute bookings, choosing a lesser known airline, choosing the right seats, waiting for the right season for the vacation amongst others. All you need to do is log in online and do a little research. Fill in the details for your expected departure and arrival date and destination. With a good algorithm in place, most well coded sites will automatically give you a list of affordable airlines to choose from. So go ahead and book your cheap air tickets now.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Flights to Asia, Last Minute First Class Fares, Cheap Discounted Fares .</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class, First Class Fares, Cheap Ticket Price, Last Minute First Class Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>163958633a974ff99422b5d2ad4e1618.jpg</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>89b9825fbdaa4742838b4144402f3255.jpg</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>47</blog_id><title>Best Deals on Business Class, First Class Discounted Fares on International Flights.</title><alias>Deals-Business-Class-Fares-Cheap</alias><posted>7/30/2013 8:52:05 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers Cheap First Class Tickets &#38;amp; Disocunted Business Class Fares.&#38;#160;Travelling is an activity indulged in by every individual. The busy hectic working schedule often leaves no time for personal life. When it comes to travelling, it is important that you opt for best transport. With so many transport services such as air, land, water, nothing can beat the services offered by air.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Travelling is an activity indulged in by every individual. The busy hectic working schedule often leaves no time for personal life. When it comes to travelling, it is important that you opt for best transport. With so many transport services such as air, land, water, nothing can beat the services offered by air. They are considered as the perfect and effective means when it comes to reaching your preferred destination on time without any delay. However, the rising prices have curbed people from travelling by air. Have you ever thought about travelling by air at reasonable prices? Does it sound too good to be true? But it is now possible with the help of&#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; Cheap Business Class Flight&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;You must have noticed that many people go from one place to another for business trips. Every &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; looks forward to expand for more development and you will see many businesspersons on the go every time. To cater to the needs of the business, there is &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business Class Flight&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;, which helps you to travel comfortably at reasonable prices possible. &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; are considered as the best, cheapest and comfortable means of travelling. The reason being, they help you to travel to various places at affordable prices tickets. However, the ever-increasing prices of the tickets have kept people away from opting for air transport. Business class amenities begin before you even step on the airplane.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Every person wishes to travel first class. However, it is not every person&#38;#8217;s cup of tea as the tickets are expensive and not everyone can afford it. It offers all the facilities you would ever need while traveling. Your elite experience to first class travel starts once you enter the airport doors. From the tranquility of cascading water walls to the thrill of hobnobbing with other high-end travelers over a martini, most airlines strive to make their first-class airport lounges the best around. If you are still wondering, where will you find these &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; tickets, think again, as they are easily available online.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;There are many providers online that offer cheap and affordable &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;First Class Ticket&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;. The main aim of these providers is to offer reduced fare list and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; on all domestic as well as international flights. They also provide the best deals on luxury &#60;strong&#62;international flights&#60;/strong&#62; to exciting destinations, including &#60;strong&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;Hong Kong&#60;/strong&#62; and Seoul. Apart from this, they also offer deep &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on all types of flights, which consists of one-way, round-trip, &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;cheap Last Minute Flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;, round-the-world and multi-city trips. This helps an individual to enjoy premium travel with affordable prices. They leave no stone unturned to ensure you enjoy your flight completely. They also take care of all your corporate or holiday travel needs. It does not matter what your corporate travel needs are, they will take care of the arrangements as inexpensively and conveniently as possible so that you can concentrate on your business, not your travel plans. You can also track flights with them. You can request quote by providing necessary information. Surf the relevant website for further details on the services.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap first class fares, business class airline, discounted business class airline, last minute flight </description><keywords>first class, business classm cheap flights, business class disount, first class ticket</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cb36ae92745a49d3a8a1959109590e19.jpg</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5e95d3d81a6146e18f174a690bd414c7.jpg</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>48</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class and First Class Tickets Online. Best Deals Last Minute Flights. </title><alias>Last-Minute-Business-Class</alias><posted>7/31/2013 8:03:29 PM</posted><summary>Many websites provide you with services for booking&#38;#160;cheap business class&#38;#160;tickets. These online service providers are directly tied up with the airlines. As there are many business group that travel on regular basis with different airlines, these websites strive to provide them with&#38;#160;cheap&#38;#160;business class&#38;#160;and first class tickets.&#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class and First Class Tickets Online&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Many websites provide you with services for booking &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets. These online service providers are directly tied up with the airlines. As there are many business group that travel on regular basis with different airlines, these websites strive to provide them with &#60;strong&#62;cheap&#60;/strong&#62; &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. Whether it is one way, round trip or multi-city trip, heavy discounts are available for the customers. Along with business class, they provide you with &#60;strong&#62;cheap first class ticket&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can save a considerable amount of money on your trip. The first class includes all the elite and luxurious services at much &#60;strong&#62;discounted rates&#60;/strong&#62;. The deluxe services start from the time you enter the airport. All superior quality services are included that will keep you relaxed throughout your journey.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Many passengers have begun shifting from economy class to the business class in order to experience these top notch services. They travel on regular basis which is why many companies provide them with &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; offers. As they are able to save lots of money on travel with all the provided benefits, they are able to spend money on other luxuries when they reach their desired destination.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Other than &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, the websites also provide you with car rentals and hotel services to make your stay easy and comfortable. As these websites provide their services in the top major countries, they are able to provide customers with luxurious hotel and car facilities. You need to enter the mandatory details according to your requirements in order to get the best deals.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The customer support team is accessible round the clock and help you with details about &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. As they are connected with all the airlines, they provide you with &#60;strong&#62;cheap&#60;/strong&#62; &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. If you want first class travel experiences, then research well on the internet, as there are many websites providing you with these services. You can compare the deals that they offer and choose the one that suits your requirements the best.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The facility provided to the first class travellers is totally elite and high class. They are hospitable to the passengers and cater to all their requirements. The food and refreshments that are provided are the best. Once you enter the flight you are greeted with a glass of champagne. The cuisine is inspired by top chefs and changes on a daily basis. There are lot of entertainment options available where you can pass your time. If you have urgent work you can comfortably access your laptop as there is extra personal space available to relax or work. The best thing about first class travelling is its gives you your space, amenities and services to spend your travel time in a memorable way. The post landing services are also exclusive as your bags are the first to arrive on the express immigrations. Also complementary executive car services are available to your destination.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Discount business class, First Class Airline Tcikets, Best Deals Business Class</description><keywords>First Class Airfare, Cheap Business Class Flights, Last Minute Deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>31b9dd53c9094a1da55bb62577f80007.jpg</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ff6bbdfab46b44789dd581b42538bdb8.jpg</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>49</blog_id><title>The Significance Of Choosing The Right Carrier For All Business Class Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Last-Minute-Flights</alias><posted>8/4/2013 8:43:35 PM</posted><summary>It is common for&#38;#160;business travelers&#38;#160;to board flights several times in a month. Planes are considered the safest modes to reach any destination in the world.&#38;#160;Business class flights&#38;#160;have in fact tripled since the concept first got introduced. Airline service providers have started banking on the enormous demand created by the business travelers all around the world.&#38;#160;Cheap business class&#38;#160;tickets can now be afforded by all the travelers. The facilities provided in the business class are similar to those provided to first-class travelers. In comparison, first class tickets are far more expensive.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;It is common for &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;business travelers&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; to board flights several times in a month. Planes are considered the safest modes to reach any destination in the world. &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; have in fact tripled since the concept first got introduced. Airline service providers have started banking on the enormous demand created by the business travelers all around the world. &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; tickets can now be afforded by all the travelers. The facilities provided in the business class are similar to those provided to first-class travelers. In comparison, first class tickets are far more expensive. Majority of the flyers who travel for business prefer business class for the bargain deals provided by many prominent airliners. There are numerous benefits which a business traveler can fetch, apart from the discounts they get from their respective airline companies.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A business class travel can help one taste the most appropriate food and range of services which an economy class ticket does not provide. A business traveler need not compromise on the quality of services after he has purchased the &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; ticket. Passengers traveling business class also get priority check-ins, which an economy flight traveler cannot enjoy. Several conferences and consultations are held in different parts of the world. Many visit foreign destinations for sake of site visits and attending seminars, amongst other matters of commercial significance. Constant traveling can be very frustrating for any traveler. In order to make it more convenient for business travelers, several airline companies strive to make one&#38;#39;s trip sophisticated and comfortable. These companies depend on repeat customers for enhancing their business worth; that is why business travelers are given lot of freebies along with the privilege to board &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; can make the traveler feel the pleasure of experiencing superior quality. The feel of sophistication rings in the sense of achievement in every traveler&#38;#8217;s mind. There are several benefits attached to &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, and it is not just food, drinks and &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; that bring a smile on the traveler&#38;#8217;s faces. Who doesn&#38;#8217;t like to be pampered and the affection which several airliners bestow on their customers is amazing. Business travel can have the seats recline up to 180 degrees for its passengers to completely lie down and relax. There is an LCD panel behind every seat with individual headsets attached to it for providing entertainment to the clients. The flight personnel are more caring and provide one with all comforts and essentials.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Business flight fares are offered at a discounted rate on consistent basis for frequent flyers. &#60;strong&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; can be sought from several airliners on the internet. But it is pertinent to browse through several sites to find out the exact information of the airline company providing exact services. A bit of research and keeping a watch for the deals being offered by the airlines will ensure that you fly in comfort and at less cost.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Cheap Business Class, Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class Flight Ticket, Cheap Last Minute Flights </description><keywords>Cheap Business Class, Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class Flight Ticket, Cheap Last Minute Flights </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7107608d4de449dfa83f51bf8defad12.jpg</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>fd5895158a394b5c8bf9bf732bd57b5b.jpg</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>50</blog_id><title>Get Business Class Flight Tickets &#38; Save Thousands. </title><alias>Business-Class-Cheap-Deals</alias><posted>8/5/2013 5:17:20 PM</posted><summary>Every person wants to have comfortable and enjoyable traveling experience. It can give immense satisfaction to be at ease during the travel. Hence, many people are interested to get their hands on affordable air flight deals. This presents the opportunity to reach their destination without spending heavily. With the rising inflation, it is essential to be careful and keep a check on the expenses.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Every person wants to have comfortable and enjoyable traveling experience. It can give immense satisfaction to be at ease during the travel. Hence, many people are interested to get their hands on affordable air flight deals. This presents the opportunity to reach their destination without spending heavily. With the rising inflation, it is essential to be careful and keep a check on the expenses. The right &#60;strong&#62;deal&#60;/strong&#62; will make the journey from one city to another pleasant. A person needs to get in touch with a reliable website to meet their &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; or vacation tour needs. This can make a huge difference in saving money on the air travel. Many &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; professionals are eager to get the &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class ticket&#60;/strong&#62;. It helps to fulfill their trip requirements within the limited budget.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are companies that take pride in offering the &#60;strong&#62;best deals business class&#60;/strong&#62; to the corporate firms. With the help of corporate account, it is possible to cater to the frequent traveling necessities. An organization can hugely benefit from the corporate account with the proper arrangement of trip. The expert can manage the long or short distance necessities with great proficiency. It can definitely prove to be useful in planning the tour. It gives the chance to manage the entire trip conveniently and economically. This enables to stay away from the unwanted fuss of checking the availability and booking of the tickets. An individual will feel relaxed as it is handled by skilled personnel.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The corporate account has been helpful in receiving the &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; ticket of major airlines. This enables to get the best possible solution for the short or long distance travel. It will be useful for traveling within the United States. In addition, the &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; offers will prove useful for other destinations such as Seoul, Hong Kong, or Singapore. According to the recent survey, the reliable source will be instrumental in saving substantial amount of money. It is a feasible option as compared to traditional method. With the efficient flight consolidator database, people can expect to get an attractive deal according to their convenience. Apart from this, the team of experts is dedicated to offer outstanding service. They will handle the transportation and lodging arrangements. People can rely on them to acquire exceptional and economical solutions.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are many incidents where an individual needs to go on a trip immediately. This is where the option of &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; comes to help. People will be delighted with the ease in the booking procedure. It can result in saving significant amount of time and without paying any undesired extra charge. A client can get luxurious &#60;strong&#62;cheap first class ticket&#60;/strong&#62; to experience memorable air travel. The car rental reservation and discounted hotel accommodations will be truly remarkable. This is bound to make the trip cost-effective and wonderful. The professional and timely service will exceed the expectations of the client. Experienced staff can offer relevant information to clear any kind of doubt. It will help to receive best price on the ticket for an unforgettable air travel experience.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class, Cheap Last Minute Flights, First Class Tickets Disocunt Fares</description><keywords>Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class, Cheap Last Minute Flights, First Class Tickets Disocunt Fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0be41f68825d4ccc8716171e3ec3d7f6.jpg</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7f215610bfb2417d8b627e12dc911fd1.jpg</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>51</blog_id><title>Cheap Business Class- An Affordable Option to Travel with Luxury </title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-Specials</alias><posted>8/8/2013 8:57:31 AM</posted><summary>Millions of people travel the entire world every year. Some do it for work while for other it is simply their love of travelling and exploring new and different places. Whatever, may be the reason, the bottom line remains that people use the airways as their choice medium of transport. Air transportation was always considered as an expensive medium, and in the current economic scenario, the expensiveness has increased all the more. People who rely on air travel exclusively, for them it becomes essential that they search for&#38;#160;cheap business class&#38;#160;flights. Purchasing cheap tickets is the best option by which they can save those few bucks that they might otherwise spend on buying expensive tickets. &#38;#160; &#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Millions of people travel the entire world every year. Some do it for work while for other it is simply their love of travelling and exploring new and different places. Whatever, may be the reason, the bottom line remains that people use the airways as their choice medium of transport. Air transportation was always considered as an expensive medium, and in the current economic scenario, the expensiveness has increased all the more. People who rely on air travel exclusively, for them it becomes essential that they search for &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; flights. Purchasing cheap tickets is the best option by which they can save those few bucks that they might otherwise spend on buying expensive tickets. &#38;#160; &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are lots of companies that offer affordable &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. They offer reduced fare on first and business class seats for all domestic and international flights. Individuals can explore exciting offers on luxurious international tickets to destinations including, Singapore, Hong Kong and Seoul. Special discounts and offers are also available on all types of flights; one-way, round-trip, &#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62;, around the world and multi- city trips. Apart from &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets, these companies also offer easy and convenient bookings of affordable hotels, car rental and ground transportation services. &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The biggest advantage of reserving &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flight&#60;/strong&#62; from these websites is the amount of services that they offer. On booking, people get a unique id which they can use to access entertainment areas, well equipped &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; centers, chic bars and delectable edibles at the first class airport lounge amenities. Individuals can also get valuable tips on their destination city from the helpful lounge concierges and can avoid the lengthy coach security lines. Some of the lounges even employ luxurious cars to transport clients from the lounge to their flight area.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The benefits of booking&#60;strong&#62; cheap business&#60;/strong&#62; &#60;strong&#62;class &#60;/strong&#62;tickets from these companies does not stop at the airport lounge. Once the plane lands at the preferred destination, individuals can enjoy express immigration or custom services. These companies provide executive car service to the hotel, home or the meeting place. All of these services are affordable and come with an easy to use travelling plan. People can save up to 70 percent on their first class expense to any destination on the world&#38;#8217;s best airlines.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Booking &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets is also easy. Majority of such companies have their websites which have details on the various services offered by them. For booking, all one has to do is simply select the option from the drop down box, including the destination, departure date, type of seat, number of people, name, telephone number and email id. People can easily book one way, round trip or multi city tickets.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Some of the websites even provide the option of &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. They have certain seats which are already reserved for it. Individuals are required to make the payment once they make their purchase. Payments can be done through debit or credit card or through internet banking. These websites are legally approved and are authorized to provide their services. This ensures transparency and credibility in their working.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>cheap business class, business class flights, cheap business class flight, cheap last minute flights</description><keywords>cheap business class, business class flights, cheap business class flight, cheap last minute flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ada243d1a42b448dae722428c5e41a72.jpg</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>8d45f453f959498f85cce0aef866f801.jpg</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>52</blog_id><title>Tips To Get the Best Deals on Business Class Flights</title><alias>Best-Business-Class-Fares</alias><posted>8/9/2013 3:56:44 PM</posted><summary>Travelling has is its own reasons attached to it. Some do it for pleasure, some for relocation and some for business. This has led to the formation of different classes in tickets available for air travel. People travelling for business usually book&#38;#160;Business Class Flights&#38;#160;as they are specially designed for business individuals who travel frequently for various reasons. When this class was initially introduced it was termed to be an alternative for first and business class. It was different from the regular travel arrangements and the areas included quality of food, seating, drinks, ground service and other amenities.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Travelling has is its own reasons attached to it. Some do it for pleasure, some for relocation and some for business. This has led to the formation of different classes in tickets available for air travel. People travelling for business usually book &#60;strong&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62; as they are specially designed for business individuals who travel frequently for various reasons. When this class was initially introduced it was termed to be an alternative for first and business class. It was different from the regular travel arrangements and the areas included quality of food, seating, drinks, ground service and other amenities. Now people are always searching for &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets as they are affordable and provide the best of arrangements. Almost every airline has &#60;strong&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62; scheduled on regular basis and they are always pre booked considering the demands.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Some of the flights are even booked 2 to 3 months prior to the travel date and major business providers have dedicated departments for such arrangements. While looking for a &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class Flight&#60;/strong&#62; there are some basics that must be followed to get the best deal. The first basic to get the tickets at low rates is that they must be books as early as possible. The &#60;strong&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62; are usually booked on emergency basis but they are also available for booking months in advance. There are travel agencies that have complete knowledge of the booking procedure and book the &#60;strong&#62;Cheap First Class Ticket&#60;/strong&#62; in advance so that they can be sold at a higher price later. The price margins may vary depending on the agency and this is the second trick that can be used to get the tickets at lower rates. All the travel websites list a number of &#60;strong&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62; that can be directly booked from their online portals.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Some popular websites are always listed among the top searches of search engines and the rates can be compared by visiting them. It is usually difficult to find &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Last Minute Flights&#60;/strong&#62; at lower rates as they are sought by many people. Time is the key to get the &#60;strong&#62;Best Deals Business Class&#60;/strong&#62; as the prices are high at the last moment bookings. There are some cancellations that are also done at the last moment and the travel websites have updated information on the bookings. These bookings are updated every minute and they are also a final alternative for people who do not get economy class tickets. These portals have tickets available for every class but business class tickets are more in demand as they are a better alternative to first class. Except for a few amenities, all the luxuries are available in this class and the rates are also low.&#38;#160; The rates of different portal must be compared to get the lowest deal but the user must also compare the features which are usually same for many airlines. The bookings can be directly made through the portals and they also have a toll free number for detailed personalized assistance.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Best Deals Business Class Flights, Busienss Class Flights, Cheap Business Class, Business Class Flights, Last Minute First Class Airfares </description><keywords>Best Deals Business Class Flights, Busienss Class Flights, Cheap Business Class, Business Class Flights, Last Minute First Class Airfares </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cd413ffe8ab54ba09142a553d52f0ea3.jpg</alias><content_id>52</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>426bbd4618494b84a2e8aaf4838ee353.jpg</alias><content_id>52</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>53</blog_id><title>How to Get Last Minute Business &#38; First Class Flights at Discounted Rates </title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-Discount</alias><posted>8/10/2013 5:19:51 PM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Air travel has seen a tremendous boost in the recent years and there is a high demand for flight tickets from various counties. This demand goes very high during festival seasons and their prices also go high owing to the non-availability of flights. This demand is further aggravated by unexpected climatic conditions which may lead to cancellation of certain flights. People usually book such flights at the last moment and the rates are very high owing to the less availability. There are a few portals that offer discounts on such flights and they give &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class&#60;/strong&#62; flight tickets are rates that are lower than others. Such websites are operated and handled by expert travel agents who have complete knowledge of all the operational airlines and do real time monitoring to get the available tickets and provide them at discounted rates.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;These portals offer special services for frequent flyers and corporate visitors who need the tickets more frequently. They also provide tickets at affordable rates in case of emergency to make sure that the customers are satisfied with the service and keep coming back to them in the future. The portals offer simple selection options and skip unnecessary details to help the user find the lowest fare for any destination. The three main options that have to be selected first include the type of trip which can be round, one way or multi city. Some people are also concerned about the class and first try to find &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class&#60;/strong&#62; flights and compare the price with others. This is followed by the departure and the destination city which can be easily selected using the drop down menus.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The next thing that must be specified is the departure date and the return date in case of round trip. The number of people must also be specified as special discounts are provided for students and families. The user also has to mention the name, telephone number and email address which is optional but it is advised to provide these details for future benefits. These travel portals also organize competitions and lucky draws and free tickets or additional discounts are given out in prizes. A unique feature that is observed in such portals is that the user can mention additional comments in the suggestion box and get exactly what he or she wants. Special discounted flights to hot destinations are listed on the home page. They also provide tour packages which organized and designed with the help of local travel agents.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;They have contacts with all the major airlines that operate thousands of flights on a daily basis. The users search is cross verified with the different availabilities and all the available alternatives are listed with their details. Some people have also posted testimonials about the quality of service that they got and how these portals helped in case of emergencies. They also have a toll free number which can be used to gather additional details.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>last minute business class, cheap first class fares, business class deals cheap, best deals busienss class</description><keywords>last minute business class, cheap first class fares, business class deals cheap, best deals busienss class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>940ce6a49d4e4dd7a9a8c4e0bf6c3bd3.jpg</alias><content_id>53</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>f88058f29f844e8a99d519e835293ad7.jpg</alias><content_id>53</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>54</blog_id><title>Booking Discounted Business Class Flights Online is Easy </title><alias>Last-Minute-First-Class-Ticket-Cheap</alias><posted>8/11/2013 12:41:27 PM</posted><summary>People travel for corporate meetings as well as to explore places. Hence, they all look for good deals that help them book their flight tickets. First class will cost a lot and travelling by economy will be a bit uncomfortable and there are chances of exhaustion. Most of them do not like travelling by economy class and find comforts missing. Hence, for comfort and to make the trip better many&#38;#160;Business Class Flights&#38;#160;are on offer. The best thing about these flights is that it offers all facilities but at an&#38;#160;affordable price.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;People travel for corporate meetings as well as to explore places. Hence, they all look for good deals that help them book their flight tickets. First class will cost a lot and travelling by economy will be a bit uncomfortable and there are chances of exhaustion. Most of them do not like travelling by economy class and find comforts missing. Hence, for comfort and to make the trip better many &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Business Class Flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; are on offer. The best thing about these flights is that it offers all facilities but at an &#60;strong&#62;affordable price&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The main highlight of business class is its seating. They need to be comfortable and hence there are different types of seating which include recliners, angled lie flat, fully flat bed, staggered fully flat bed, among others. If one wants the best deal, booking should be done in advance. This will help save money and also the person booking the tickets will get the option of getting their preferred seat. &#60;strong&#62;Business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; are making it easier for the travellers to travel with convenience. Entrepreneurs travel for many purposes like conferences, meeting, site visits, consultations and reviews. Initially it is exciting but travelling frequently makes it frustrating and so they look for flights that provide comfort.&#38;#160; There are number of companies that deal in airline tickets and travelling. But now this is available online. There are websites that help people compare the fares, book tickets and much more. They also have their tie ups with hotels hence provide one with car services too. An individual can also book &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; as normally other flights allow last minute bookings only if the customer pays extra. Because of cheap business class tickets many businessmen prefer traveling by these fights. Several airline companies have made it very easy and cost effective for people to travel either domestic or international. &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There are many advantages of &#60;strong&#62;business class fights &#60;/strong&#62;like superior quality food and drinks, better comfort zone, cost efficient, congestion free travel and comfortable seats. Hence, all these benefits add up to making the journey full of ease. They offer discounts to frequent travellers giving them &#60;strong&#62;best deals business class&#60;/strong&#62;. The airport lounge of these flights are the best; one enters the world of luxury with refine and attentive services. There are many websites dealing in booking of these flight tickets. These websites have tie ups with big airline service providers like Delta, Emirates, Cathay Pacific, British Airways, United, Lufthansa and Virgin Atlantic among others. They provide the details of different airlines offering &#60;strong&#62;business class flights &#60;/strong&#62;along with the fares. But one must make sure that the website is reputed and trustworthy as there are many unreliable sites. Hence, one must make it a point to read the reviews and testimonials of other customers and then decide on taking up the services. In case of any queries one can call the customer care number mentioned or log on to the website and have a chat in the chat room of the website.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class Fares, Discounted First Class Airfares , Last Minute Flights</description><keywords>Business Class Flights, Cheap Business Class Fares, Discounted First Class Airfares , Last Minute Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bb156eb43b4a44faa0e9ee47ceec024e.jpg</alias><content_id>54</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>21730f4062cb485da3a7780490ec8db0.jpg</alias><content_id>54</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item><item><blog_id>55</blog_id><title>First Class Tickets now at Lower Prices</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Flights</alias><posted>8/23/2013 11:59:01 AM</posted><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, save thousands on last minute Business Class tickets. Best deals on Business Class. &#38;#160;Special fares on Business and First Class tickets. Discounted First &#38;amp; Business Class airline tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class travel deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;People have become very conscious about their lifestyles. They desire to live a luxurious life and their standard of living is changing rapidly. There are many people who travel by flights; although it is very expensive. And there are many people who crave for traveling in flights. But due to the high price they cannot afford it and give up hope of fulfilling their desire. Keeping this in mind, companies have come up with discounts on every ticket. They provide you with best &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;deals business class&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; and &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;cheap first class ticket&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;. Traveling in luxury brings in the feeling of richness and royalty along with comfort. There are many agencies that provide you with discount services. They have connections with leading airline companies. You can choose any airline service you prefer and find the best deals on offer.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you go through these agencies, they provide you with various facilities along with the discounts. The facilities provided in first class are:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;If you book a first class ticket they tend to give you 40-50% discounts. Along with it, they provide you with lounges for relaxing. They will take you to one of the best airport lounges.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;They also provide entertainment areas, business centers, chic bars, a calming massage, salon service and refreshing shower, luxurious cars to transport you from the lounge to your flight and many more. All these facilities are more than what you get in a basic facility.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;When you are in the flight, you get to have food made by one of the best chefs in the world. They provide you with five star amenities around you.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Once you reach the destination, from there you get car transportation till your hotel or wherever you desire to go.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The facilities provided in &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; are:&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Once you reach the airport they provide you with lounges along with, refreshments, cocktails, snacks and cuisines.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Business class travelers have special airline lounges for them. They also provide business lounges or conference rooms.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;In flight you get food and drinks along with recliner seats so that you get to rest, massage to feel relaxed, and storage facility.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li&#62;Once you reach your destination you get a complementary chauffeur or ground transportation services from the airport. They drop you to your desired destination.&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you have to go abroad for an urgent meeting or work and you have not booked the tickets, you need not worry. These days you get &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. You can get or book tickets anytime and you get heavy discounts on the tickets you purchase. There are many leading airline companies that are vying the customers by providing &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/strong&#62; tickets at a very affordable price so that your traveling becomes hassle free and fits well within your budget. You can contact such agencies by visiting their official websites. You can get the desired information there in detail.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><seo><description>chep flights, business class disounts, first class airfares, last minute business, cheap flights, first, business class, flights, dicount</description><keywords>chep flights, business class disounts, first class airfares, last minute business, cheap flights, first, business class, flights, dicount</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>3f2bf2c7ec3f461189e3181a2f561dbb.jpg</alias><content_id>55</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5120063dcb4d4f0b9d13629c5b3d75d4.jpg</alias><content_id>55</content_id><title>null</title><queue>0</queue></image></images></item></items>