<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><city_id>14</city_id><country_id>8</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Hong Kong</name><title>Cheap Business Class &#38; Discounted First Class Fares , Save Thousands to Hong Kong</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-to-Hong-Kong</alias><summary>Cheap Business Class to Tokyo, Disocunted Fisrt Class Tickets, Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights to Tokyo
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Hong Kong.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book&#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Mystical Orient or Thriving Western City?&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Hong Kong is a delightful study of merging cultures, economies and lifestyles.&#60;br /&#62;
    Architecture, new and old, is Hong Kong&#38;#39;s most notable contrast. More than 1,000 high-rise buildings tower over the city and surround Victoria Harbour. Majestic mountains are a calming backdrop to the skyscrapers, mixing nature with modern development. Spectacular lights illuminate the night sky as The Center&#38;#39;s neon show marks the end of another day, while the Symphony of Lights music and laser show plays across 44 Hong Kong buildings to set the stage for another night of pulsing discos and nightclubs.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Hong Kong&#38;#39;s historic buildings are low-tech but no less grand than the mighty skyscrapers. Testaments to the city&#38;#39;s long-time religious freedoms, Hong Kong is full of ancient temples and churches. Ohel Leah Synagogue, Hung Shing Temple and Lin Fa Temple are tucked among the city&#38;#39;s skyscrapers, but head away from the city&#38;#39;s tallest buildings to see the stunning traditional Muslim architecture of Kowloon Masjid.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Victoria Peak offers gorgeous views of the city, harbors and Lamma Island. The trip to The Peak is an adventure in its own right aboard the funicular railway Peak Tram.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Travel in World-Class Style to a World-Class City in Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your Hong Kong adventure with a first-rate travel experience courtesy of Fly First&#38;#39;s affordable first class fares and awesome business class deals. With all that the vibrant city has to offer, you&#38;#39;ll want to arrive ready to work and play, and there&#38;#39;s no better way to ensure that than to travel in luxurious comfort. From the moment you embark on your trip, you&#38;#39;ll have access to top-of-the-line amenities and services. From refreshing services at exclusive airport lounges to the spacious comfort of business and first class cabins, your every need will be served.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Save bundles of money on &#60;strong&#62;business class deals to Hong Kong&#60;/strong&#62; with FlyFirst.com. Big &#60;strong&#62;last minute discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on premium travel are just part of our extensive services. One-way, around-the-world, multi-city and round-trip journeys all receive our industry-leading &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, saving you as much as 60 percent on airfare. Our expert travel professionals are available to assist you with all your travel needs to ensure that your trip to Hong Kong is flawless. When you book with Fly First, you book with confidence and the knowledge that you are receiving the best last minute discounts and &#60;strong&#62;greatest business class deals&#60;/strong&#62; available.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>5270</first_class_price><business_class_price>3840</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minute Cheap Business Class To Hong Kong, Cheap First Class, Business Class AirFares, Flights, First Class Airfares</description><keywords>Cheap Business and affordable fares to Hong Kong, Last minute business class deals,Flights, First Class Airfares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0f4fd08f3c5f4a84aaccc1b45b4efc50.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class to Hong Kong</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ac3c61103f9e40ed8ee9dbc732a4c14a.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fare to Hong Kong</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>9998df4cc4ea4027b925eaa5672d39e9.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class to Hong Kong</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>15</city_id><country_id>32</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Osaka</name><title>Cheap Deals On Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Osaka, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save Thousands </title><alias>Last-Minute-Cheap-Business-Class-to-Osaka</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Osaka, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Osaka. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Osaka.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry, Entertainment and the Edo Period&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A thriving metropolis lures thousands of business travelers to Osaka each year. In a city where the daytime population out-steps the nighttime population by more than one million people, Osaka is truly a working town. Its metropolitan area includes the cities of Kyoto and Kobe, making it the world&#38;#39;s seventh largest metropolitan economy.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Its notable electronics industry is secured with headquarters of many technology giants, including Sharp, Sanyo and Panasonic. The city&#38;#39;s economic success is beautifully showcased by the Umeda Sky Building&#38;#39;s twin towers connected by a rooftop bridge and Floating Garden. For business and pleasure travelers, the sky bridge is a great location to take in extraordinary views of the city and relish the wonder of Japan.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    More technological wonders are on display in Osaka&#38;#39;s Dotonbori Bridge district. Noted for its conglomeration of electronic signs to rival New York City&#38;#39;s Times Square and its infamous giant mechanical crab, Osaka&#38;#39;s entertainment district is lively and diverse. It&#38;#39;s the perfect spot to end a day of traveling, working or sightseeing.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The country&#38;#39;s premier rice-trading post during the Edo Period, Osaka earned the nickname, &#38;quot;The Nation&#38;#39;s Kitchen.&#38;quot; While rice-trading no longer dominates the city&#38;#39;s economy, the city&#38;#39;s reputation for world class cuisine continues the legend. The city&#38;#39;s numerous casual and fine dining restaurants and countless street vendors are great spots to re-fuel for your Osaka travels.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap Business and First Class Luxury Travel&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the long flight to Osaka pleasant and productive by traveling in the comfort of premier airline cabins. With incredible discounts on FlyFirst.com business class tickets and first class fares, you can enjoy stellar airport lounges, spacious and plush airplane seating and exquisite meals at 60 percent less than conventional luxury fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;We specialize in providing first-rate travel planning and &#60;strong&#62;unbeatable pricing&#60;/strong&#62; to bring you the very best services in the industry. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you know you are getting the &#60;strong&#62;greatest deals&#60;/strong&#62; around, along with stellar customer service from FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s experienced travel professionals. Whether you have a complicated trip to plan or are just looking for &#60;strong&#62;great last minute deals&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com offers the&#60;strong&#62; lowest available prices on first class fares and business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; to Osaka.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4990</first_class_price><business_class_price>3870</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted First and Business Class Tickets To Osaka, Flights, Destination, Tracker Visa, Corporate account, First Class Airfares</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class , Cheap First Class, First Class,Flights,Destination, Business Airfare, Last Minute First Class, Last minute business class airfare, business class airline, discounted airline fares, business class tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>24eab91cab7e4c6986e8e950a7ff4292.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fare to Osaka</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>4a9f3540f9ff4c309cf7725614d4e46c.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class to Osaka</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>523f88ca713841aaa3fc2220807c5c73.jpg</alias><content_id>15</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class to Osaka</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>16</city_id><country_id>26</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Seoul</name><title>Cheap Deals On Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Seoul, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save Thousands</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Ticket-to-Seoul</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Seoul, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Seoul. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Seoul.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Reveal the Soul of Seoul&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Although it&#38;#39;s known more for its status as a modern international city and technology center, a wealth of history, art and cuisine thrives in Seoul. Whether you are in town for business or pleasure, make time to visit the heart of Seoul, the Gyeongbokung Palace. Seoul was built around this 14th century Joseon royal seat and it bears the marks of the intervening centuries, including Korean War bullet holes. Four other impressive Joseon Dynasty palaces make up the legendary Five Grand Palaces and are not to be missed.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Ancient dynasties and rulers have given way to today&#38;#39;s ruling class of Seoul, the booming technology and electronics industry. For business professionals traveling to Seoul, the opportunities here are colossal. Seoul is home to some of the world&#38;#39;s largest and most successful electronics firms, participating in a national economy that is ranked No. 4 in the world. Be poised to make the most of your opportunities in Seoul by traveling in the restful comfort of luxury. With FlyFirst.com&#60;strong&#62; first class deals,&#60;/strong&#62; the airfare will leave you with enough funds to truly enjoy the city&#38;#39;s exciting activities.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    After a busy day working or a fun-filled day of touring, head up to the top of N Tower. The cable car ride to the top is thrilling and the observation deck offers jaw-dropping views of the city from 1,200 feet above sea level.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Soothing Sojourn to Seoul in Cheap Business and First Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Business or pleasure, alone or with family, your journey to Seoul is made more pleasant in luxurious first or business class. With all that the dynamic city has to offer, traveling in deluxe accommodations ensures that you will be rested and set to explore Seoul&#38;#39;s many attractions.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As premium passengers, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy immeasurable service from the minute you reach the airport. Graciously appointed airport lounges offer a respite from the masses as well as a bounty of delicious refreshments to start your long journey. On board your flight, your every wish will be catered by attentive staff members serving five-star meals. You will have plenty of room to work, sleep and relax so that you have the energy to take on Seoul when you land.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Every travel request and itinerary is treated to the same stellar Fly First service and discounts, whether you need multi-city flights or &#60;strong&#62;last minute seats&#60;/strong&#62;. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you know that you are accessing the &#60;strong&#62;best discounts available&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets and the greatest first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; around.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4860</first_class_price><business_class_price>3830</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap Business Fares and First Class Tickets To Seoul, last Minute Business Class Fare, First Class Fare</description><keywords>First class airlines, Flights, Tickets, Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares business</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1771b11952b845669fc3c431ac456791.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap First Class To Seoul </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>5e0687eddffa4eeeb65f43f37d72cd63.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Business Class To Seoul </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>bda1247e9c5e4a60b1331a6138431318.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class to Seoul </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>17</city_id><country_id>33</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Kuala Lumpur</name><title>Discounted Business Class Airfares &#38; First Class Flights To Kuala Lumpur, Cheap Last Minute Flights.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-KualaLumpur</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Kuala Lumpur, we specialize on last minute business class airfares, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Kuala Lumpur. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Kuala Lumpur.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Diplomats, Financiers and Hindu Deities&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With its prospering financial markets, diplomatic missions and treasured landmarks, Kuala Lumpur is the sixth most popular world destination. For &#60;strong&#62;business travelers&#60;/strong&#62;, the city is home to most foreign embassies, a burgeoning service sector and a growing hub of global Islamic financing. This showpiece of finance and economic progress is evident in the city&#38;#39;s many high-rise buildings and its iconic, record-setting Petronas Twin Towers. For a quick break between business meetings, the twin towers offer a stunning view of the city, as does the 1,381-foot Kuala Lumpur Tower spire.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Home to the Malaysian king&#38;#39;s official residence, Kuala Lumpur has a relatively short history that is best explored through its many buildings and open spaces. View the site where the country shed its British colonial flag in 1957 at Merdeka Square, or get a feel for the town&#38;#39;s pioneers at its Chinatown on Petaling Street. First-rate shopping, endless museums and an energetic nightlife bring extra entertainment to your exotic Kuala Lumpur voyage.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Natural and religious wonders are located throughout the sprawling city. Delight in the Moorish architecture of Jamek Mosque, officially opened by the Sultan of Selangor in 1909. Explore the astonishing Batu Caves, guarded by an expansive shrine and a 140-foot tall gilded statue of the Hindu deity Murugan. Hindu drawings, statues and shrines are sprinkled throughout the site&#38;#39;s three main caves and many smaller caves. While on site, enjoy one of the 160 rock climbing routes among the caves and the surrounding mountainside.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;In the Lap of Luxury Travel in Cheap Business Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the long-distance flight to Kuala Lumpur enjoyable aboard the comfort and style of first and business class air travel. The deluxe services begin even before you embark on the plane, with extravagant airport lounges featuring salon and spa services, complimentary meals and comfortable lounge areas. Once you board your airplane, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy five-star meals, spacious seats, bed turn-down service, ample work space and services catered to your needs.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s exclusive services, you&#38;#39;ll have access to deep &#60;strong&#62;discounts on luxury airfare&#60;/strong&#62;, whether yours is a &#60;strong&#62;last-minute business trip&#60;/strong&#62; or a well-planned vacation. Enjoy up to 60 percent off published rates on &#60;strong&#62;business class airfares and last minute first class airfares&#60;/strong&#62; so you can relish all that the tropical Kuala Lumpur offers.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>5190</first_class_price><business_class_price>3810</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minute First Class Deals, Business Class Airfares,Cheap Business Class Fares To Malaysia, Discounted Airlines Ticket, Tracker Visa Insurance</description><keywords>last minute business class fares, discounted airlines deals, first class deals, international business class fares, cheap business class to Asia, Cheap first Class to Australia, Cheap Business class to Europe</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>130bad876dce4fa98eac74176131ca22.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Discounted Deals on Business Class Fares </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>470fea79a571429a9c73c0ce0c6faf50.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Save Thousands in Business Class Cabin</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>f7495cc33d964cab87e6ee77c084a368.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flights to Kuala Lumpur </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>18</city_id><country_id>9</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Singapore</name><title>Cheap Flights in Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Singapore, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Fares-to-Singapore</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Singapore, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Singapore. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Singapore.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Opportunity, Glamor and Culture&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Singapore&#38;#39;s 63 islands are a bounty of opportunity, both for business travelers as well as vacationers. For those journeying to the Lion City for business, you have much to explore. A robust shipping industry, more than 7,000 multinational companies and the world&#38;#39;s No. 4 largest financial center are just a few of Singapore&#38;#39;s features. Its port is the fifth busiest in the world, and that vitality brings with it a host of supporting and ancillary businesses and opportunities. As an original member of the Four Asian Tigers, Singapore continues its tradition as an economic powerhouse.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    World-class casino resorts, high-end shopping, fascinating cultural museums and grand historical architecture are just a few of Singapore&#38;#39;s many delights. For those seeking elective medical treatments outside the U.S., Singapore&#38;#39;s medical tourism industry is thriving due to its modern facilities and highly-trained physicians.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Begin Your Journey With Premium Travel in Cheap Business &#38;amp; Discounted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the most of your flight time to spectacular Singapore with the spacious seating, fine dining and personal fully equipped work spaces on board your premium cabin. With our FlyFirst.com deals on everything from luxury last minute flights&#60;strong&#62; to first class fares, you&#38;#39;ll be able to enjoy the flight without worrying about a large price tag.&#38;#160;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Business and first class opulence begins even before you reach your airplane. Once you arrive at the airport, you gain access to exclusive lounges with delectable dining, salon and spa services, plentiful entertainment and relaxing lounge areas. The deluxe service continues throughout your flight, delivering you to &#60;strong&#62;Singapore&#60;/strong&#62; rested, refreshed and able to enjoy all of Singapore&#38;#39;s pleasures.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With our incredible savings on &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62;, you have every reason to enjoy the tremendous amenities of first and business class travel. Whether you are planning to attend a conference in Singapore months in advance or you suddenly need to travel for a spur-of-the-moment meeting, FlyFirst can coordinate your trip from start to finish, all while offering airfares at up to 60 percent off conventional ticket prices.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Our travel professionals are available to make your trip to Singapore a flawless experience that you will treasure for years to come. Take advantage of our discount &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; and enjoy reduced-fare first class flights today.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>5240</first_class_price><business_class_price>3760</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Business Class Airline Tickets to Singapore ,Flights, Destination, Class Airfares, First Class, cheap first class fares</description><keywords>Cheap Discounted Airline fares to Amsterdam,Flights, Destination, Class Airfares, Cheap business class to Singapore , Last Minute First Class Ticket Cheap to Asia, First Class Flight to Frankfurt, Business cheap first class seats</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>3f68a8a785884059a2cc141887eb3493.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Airfare to Singapore </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c2c112b1fd69437db6cc7279eb060ccd.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class to Singapore </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>bfab22454d12450ba354cd41791e4a67.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight To Singapore </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>19</city_id><country_id>28</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Amsterdam</name><title>Cheap Flights in Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Amsterdam, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Amsterdam</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Amsterdam, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Amsterdam. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Amsterdam.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Travel to Amsterdam in luxury with fantastic first class deals and discount business class flights that will save you nearly 60 percent on airfare, courtesy of FlyFirst.com.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The ABCs of Amsterdam: Art, Bicycles and Canals&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The wealthiest city in the world during its 17th-century Dutch Golden Age, Amsterdam still benefits from the succinct city planning of that era. The Amstel River ends in the center of town and connects to four half-rings of canals that end at the IJ Bay. These canals make traveling through Amsterdam simple and convenient, reduce the number of cars on the road and give the city its quaint atmosphere. Bicycling is a way of life here, so consider renting a bicycle to tour around town when not traveling by boat.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Architecture and history buffs delight in Amsterdam&#38;#39;s plentiful historic buildings. From its oldest, Oude Kerk, constructed in 1306 to its modern VanGogh Museum, travelers can spend days roaming the town investigating its charming buildings.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Eight iconic windmills still inhabit Amsterdam. Touring all eight windmills, including the 1725-built De Gooyer Windmill, is a fantastic way to spend an afternoon.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A cultural melting pot, Amsterdam celebrates its many sides in more than 50 museums, including its most famous: the Rijksmuseum and the Stedelijk Museum. For more recent history, visit the house where Anne Frank, her family and the Van Pels hid from Nazi police.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    True to its professed social tolerance, Amsterdam allows local coffee shops to sell small amounts of cannabis to those who are at least 18 years old. The city also allows legal prostitution, conducted in a controlled manner and in designated areas. The town&#38;#39;s most visited red-light district is De Wallen.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Luxury in Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Long flights to Amsterdam can be pleasurable and affordable with FlyFirst&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discount business class flights and stellar first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;. Your extravagant experience begins at the airport with entree to select airport lounges featuring countless amenities and comforts.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Once on your airplane, the pampering continues with cushy seats, delectable dishes designed by world-famous chefs, plentiful entertainment, ample work space and privacy screens. The result of flying first and business class is that you arrive in beautiful Amsterdam feeling rested and able to explore the city&#38;#39;s many faces.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com offers stellar service and access to unpublished airfares. These unpublished airfares allow us to offer you travel savings of up to 60 percent off rack prices. Simply call us or use our travel database, and we will provide you with the best &#60;strong&#62;first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;most-reduced business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; available.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3470</first_class_price><business_class_price>2460</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minute Business and First Class airfares ,Flights, Destination, Class Airfares, cheap First Class Deals, Last Minute First Class Ticket Cheap to Asia, First Class Flight to Frankfurt</description><keywords>First Class Discounted to Amsterdam,Flights, Destination, Class Airfares, First Class airfare to Middle East, Cheap Discounted Airline fares to Amsterdam, Cheap business class to Singapore , Last Minute First Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4fcd1b50c8ae4134a1bd7082c7702fc6.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Flights to Amsterdam</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9cbe0c7b51704607a46fc1dba99a8c2d.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Amsterdam</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cea840b3d5094bd1b2d6f6902957235c.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>20</city_id><country_id>22</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Auckland</name><title>Best Business Class Deals to Auckland , Save Thousands on First Class Fare</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Tickets-to-Auckland</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Auckland, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Auckland. Best Business Class deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Auckland. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Volcanoes, Bungies and Pristine Beaches&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Warm, sunny days and ancient traditions highlight the embracing energy surrounding New Zealand&#38;#39;s largest city. Nestled between two vital harbors, one leading to the Tasman Sea and the other to the Pacific Ocean, Auckland is well-placed for industries relying on shipping and for tourists looking for plentiful water recreation.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Auckland features dozens of thrills for travelers, including guided walking tours of the area&#38;#39;s volcanoes led by descendants of the local Maori. Adventurers can walk where molten lava once flowed in the large lava tubes on Rangitoto Island, just a half-hour ferry ride from Auckland.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A thrill-seeker&#38;#39;s paradise, New Zealand is the home of bungy-jumping, which remains a popular activity for travelers ready for a little excitement. Jump from the Auckland Bridge or plunge from the Sky Tower&#38;#39;s 630-foot tall platform to get your adrenaline flowing, and experience stellar views of the city and harbors.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Once you&#38;#39;ve conquered the mountains, volcanoes and bungy cords, enjoy live Polynesian music, dance, local crafts and foods at the Saturday morning Otara Flea Markets. It&#38;#39;s a great spot to mix with local Kiwis and see the real Auckland. For a relaxing afternoon, bicycle along Tamaki Drive&#38;#39;s waterfront or dine at any of the celebrated Viaduct Harbour/Princes Wharf district restaurants.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The area&#38;#39;s plentiful and stunning beaches offer rest and recreation just moments from downtown Auckland. For tranquil solitude, try Wattle Bay in Awhitu on Manutau Harbor, or for novelty, sink your toes in the black-sand beaches of Muriwai.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Tranquil Cities Call for Tranquil Journeys&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your refreshing trip to Auckland with a relaxing, &#60;strong&#62;premium flight&#60;/strong&#62;. It won&#38;#39;t cost you an arm and a leg with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s budget-friendly &#60;strong&#62;business class fares and first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;. Even better, your escape to Auckland will begin and end with a roomy, amenity-filled flight to pamper even the most discerning passengers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Pleasure or &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62;, simple itinerary or complicated needs, FlyFirst.com offers expertise and unbeatable savings for all travel requests. With savings of up to 60 percent off published airfares, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy sitting in the lap of &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; on your long flight to Auckland, knowing that &#60;strong&#62;you paid less&#60;/strong&#62; that the passengers around you. Whatever your travel needs, we are pleased to offer you stellar &#60;strong&#62;savings on first class deals and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; so you can arrive on the island in comfort and style.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4370</first_class_price><business_class_price>3840</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted First and Business Class, Class airfares,Corporate account, best business class deals to Auckland </description><keywords>business class airline, discounted airline fares, business class tickets,, flight tracket visa, First class airlines, Flights, Tickets, Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares to Auckland</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f42def6b6d22470c9296922f4fa011b7.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Best Business Class Deals </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>dcdef42848584b9e8f5d38cb0da39c9e.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Airfare to Auckland </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>47b1648410834003938cd00f14fe49b1.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Specials </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>21</city_id><country_id>12</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Bangkok</name><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Flights to Bangkok &#38; Discounted First Class Fares</title><alias>Best-Deals-Business-Class-to-Bangkok</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Bangkok, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Bangkok. Best Business Class Deals.Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Bangkok. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Make your odyssey to gorgeous Bangkok, Thailand, in deluxe splendor with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;deeply discounted first and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Vibrant Cultures, Vital Industries, Vivid Colors&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Although it&#38;#39;s been decades since Thailand was known as Siam, the country&#38;#39;s cherished historic cultures and landmarks remain, and there&#38;#39;s no better place to experience those treasures than in the booming city of Bangkok.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The third most popular tourist destination in the world, Bangkok is set on the Chao Phraya River delta. It&#38;#39;s home to many awe-inspiring, colorful Buddhist temples, including Wat Arun on the river&#38;#39;s west bank. Wat Arun&#38;#39;s impressive 230-foot spire is one of Bangkok&#38;#39;s most notable landmarks and is intricately brilliant architecture. Bangkok&#38;#39;s largest temple, Wat Pho, features a vivid red and yellow exterior and an extraordinary 154-foot, gold-plated reclining Buddha. Whether you are traveling for business or for pleasure, the temples&#38;#39; amazingly detailed designs and sacred nature are not to be missed.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With all of its meaningful historical sites, it&#38;#39;s easy to forget that Bangkok is a thriving metropolis. Home to dozens of regional headquarters for multinational companies, Bangkok is a Southeast Asian center of industry and finance.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As a modern city, Bangkok brims with all the amenities and adventures you would expect of a major international hot spot. Abundant shopping centers surround the city&#38;#39;s Siam Square, as do most of Bangkok&#38;#39;s many high-rises and skyscrapers. Although infamous for its red-light district, Bangkok has a dynamic, legal nightlife scene. After a busy day of sightseeing or meetings, unwind a little and take in the exciting nightclubs in the Patpong district and along Khaosan Road.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make the Trip to Bangkok in Comfort Business Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Don&#38;#39;t exhaust yourself on the long flight to Bangkok. Instead, conserve your energy by traveling in the appealing &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; of first or business class. You&#38;#39;ll relish the services at exclusive airport lounges, and you&#38;#39;ll bask in the luxurious experience of premium airplane cabins. Roomy enough to stretch out and work, your seating is designed to encourage peaceful sleep and productive flight time. You&#38;#39;ll arrive in Bangkok exquisitely rested so you can enjoy the city&#38;#39;s many delights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our 60 percent savings on &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel airfare&#60;/strong&#62; is delivered to you with professionalism and the utmost concern for your travel needs. We offer these &#60;strong&#62;incredible savings&#60;/strong&#62; on all types of travel, from last minute trips to complicated multi-city destinations. When you &#60;strong&#62;book with FlyFirst.com&#60;/strong&#62;, you book with confidence, knowing that you are receiving the very best &#60;strong&#62;discounts available&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today to secure your terrifically &#60;strong&#62;reduced business class fares and last minute flight deals&#60;/strong&#62; so you can travel to Bangkok in tranquil comfort.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>5380</first_class_price><business_class_price>3940</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Fares in Business and First Class, cheap first class airlines tickets, last minute business class flights</description><keywords>Cheap business class to Singapore , Last Minute First Class Ticket Cheap to Asia, First Class Flight to Bagkok, Business cheap first class seats, business class airfare to Asia, Cheap last minute fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>14625e68091b4e12a99afc112ac9065e.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Bagkok</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c8b4743578134cd697be2c006e174e0a.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cfa47ece9d9b4b47ba336bb55e600574.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Flights to Bangkok </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>22</city_id><country_id>16</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Barcelona</name><title>Cheap First Class Fares &#38; Discounted Business Class Flights to Spain</title><alias>Best-Business-Deals-to-Barcelona</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Spain, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Spain. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Spain. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll pay less than half the price of published airfares and enjoy the full range of luxury, opulence and comfort of business and first class cabins.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Warm Nights, Soft Breezes, Late-Night Nibbles&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The turquoise waters of the Mediterranean brush up against the shores of brilliant Barcelona and help to make the city one of the most popular destinations in Europe. Whether Barcelona is your starting point for a gorgeous Mediterranean cruise, a locale for conducting business or the chosen spot for your family vacation, Barcelona&#38;#39;s allure includes a robust economy, stunning architecture and a vibrant nightlife.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Business or pleasure, alone or with others, your excursion to Barcelona can be a fanciful adventure. By day, enjoy the glamorous city&#38;#39;s architectural wonders, world-class cultural endeavors or sun-drenched beaches. A decadent afternoon siesta leaves you refreshed and ready to enjoy the global city&#38;#39;s vivid nightlife, whether it will be wandering from one tapas bar to the next or taking in a performance at one of the city&#38;#39;s many theaters.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A trip to Barcelona isn&#38;#39;t complete until you&#38;#39;ve relished the architectural masterpieces of Antoni Gaudi. Spread throughout town like a historical treasure hunt, Gaudi&#38;#39;s most famous edifices include the Sagrada Familia, the Park G&#38;uuml;ell, Casa Vicens and Casa Mil&#38;agrave;. On your tour of Barcelona&#38;#39;s magnificent buildings, enjoy the 17th-century Montju&#38;iuml;c castle, perched on a 500-foot escarpment overlooking the harbor; the gorgeous Basilica of La Merc&#38;egrave;; Pla&#38;ccedil;a Reial and Barcelona Cathedral.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;A Journey as Memorable as the Destination&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your long flight to Barcelona pleasurable aboard the premium cabins of the world&#38;#39;s best airlines. FlyFirst.com makes your first and business class flights economical, offering you the ultimate in-air adventure.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    As a first or business class traveler, your luxury vacation begins at the airport with exclusive access to various extravagances at choice airport lounges. On board your flight, your every need is met with spacious, comfortable seats; full-flat beds with turn-down service and five-star dining. It&#38;#39;s an idyllic way to begin and end your trip to Barcelona.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com makes it convenient to access &#60;strong&#62;affordable luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62;, whether you require a complicated itinerary, multi-city destinations or &#60;strong&#62;one-way tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. All travel requests are treated with the same proficient service and range of&#60;strong&#62; discount &#60;/strong&#62;options. Simply call our expert travel professionals or use our quick travel database to find the very &#60;strong&#62;best deals&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares and first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; to charismatic Barcelona.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3680</first_class_price><business_class_price>2340</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Business Class Airline Tickets to Barcelona,Destination, First Class Airfares, Cheap First Class Airline, last minute business class</description><keywords>Cheap Tickets and Discounted Fares  , Last Minute First Class Air Fare to Barcelona, Affordable Business Class , affordable first Class tickets, save money on business class airfare, save money on First Class Tickets, cheap business class travel deals </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0352cc1dd92a4a1eab9b04ab7a54b7a3.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Best Business Class Deals </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c52f32486f834325bab5c18a61ce90c0.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flight to Spain</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>5b52041a61884f98afc1b2857ca1d1ff.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Last Minute Business class Tickets </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>23</city_id><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Brisbane</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights To Brisbane, Cheap Last Minute Flights.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-to-Brisbane</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Brisbane, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Brisbane. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Australia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;With savings of up to 7&#60;/span&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;0 percent, it&#38;#39;s more economical than ever to travel in luxury to Brisbane and other exciting destinations.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Come for the Thrills&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Brisbane River winds its way through much of the beautiful, walkable city. Skyscrapers in Brisbane&#38;#39;s central business district ascend from the river bank, creating an unforgettable skyline and a brilliant sight for nighttime river cruisers. It&#38;#39;s a bustling downtown, too, supporting the largest economy between Singapore and Sydney and a robust natural resources boom. The city brims with distributions hubs for global electronics companies, making Brisbane a frequent destination for international business travelers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In addition to its stellar river access, Brisbane lies between Moreton Bay and the Great Dividing Range, forming the perfect trifecta for adventurers. Animal lovers adore the Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary, where snuggling with a koala is encouraged, and visitors can feed kangaroos and wallabies. For bigger thrills, climb the 260-foot Story Bridge and rappel down, kayak or sail along Moreton Bay, take a Tree Top Walk along nine suspension bridges, cycle along the Riverwalk or climb the towering rocks of Kangaroo Point.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Those looking to expand their cultural horizons delight in the grand architecture of ANZAC Shrine, the Customs House, Albert Street Uniting Church and Parliament House. The town&#38;#39;s notable live music scene includes opera, symphony orchestra and many performing choirs.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    From adventure and outdoor activities to local theater performances and plentiful shopping, there&#38;#39;s something for everyone in Brisbane. Even if you are stuck in meetings during the day, there are plenty of nighttime cruises and performances that allow you to enjoy Brisbane&#38;#39;s many thrills.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Choose Comfort in Business Class &#38;amp; Discounted First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Why make the long flight to Brisbane in anything other than comfortable business class or deluxe first class? FlyFirst.com offers many amazing &#60;strong&#62;discounts on business class tickets and first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; that make your trip affordable and enjoyable. As select passengers, you have access to premium airport lounges, salon and spa services, complimentary fine dining, spacious airplane seating and bedding and a variety of other &#60;strong&#62;luxurious services&#60;/strong&#62;. All these conveniences ensure that you arrive in Brisbane with the energy to embark on adventures in work and in play.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com is staffed with knowledgeable, experienced travel professionals who are dedicated to finding the &#60;strong&#62;best deals&#60;/strong&#62; and the most convenient itinerary for your Brisbane trip. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you book with the confidence that you are getting the best deals available on &#60;strong&#62;first class fares and business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4780</first_class_price><business_class_price>3930</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Tickets to Brisbane, Cheap Business class flights,last minute business class fare</description><keywords>affordable first Class tickets, save money on business class airfare, save money on First Class Tickets, cheap business class travel deals, cheap first class deals travel, cheap flights travel deals, Business travel, First Class Travel</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>10b4e2f048d741e2bb06e69a68a394f1.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flights</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>fb569e69a27d482da5eab78c005fb226.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Business Class Tickets to Brisbane </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a3d49fd46ad2487aaad096802098ae6d.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Airfare </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>24</city_id><country_id>31</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Brussels</name><title>Cheap Deals On Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Brussels, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save Thousands </title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-to-Brussels</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Brussels, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Brussels. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Brussels. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll make your entire trip a memorable, relaxing journey from start to finish and save up to 60 percent on airfare in the process.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Politics and Palaces&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Enjoying the gorgeous city of Brussels is simple, regardless of whether you are traveling to the city for business or pleasure. Once a 10th-century fortress, Brussels is now a hot spot for European politics, a bastion of finance and industry and a premier cultural icon.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A world center of international organizations, diplomatic missions, North Atlantic Treaty Organization headquarters and a number of leading European Union institutions, Brussels receives thousands of business travelers. Brimming with numerous headquarters for multinational corporations, Brussels is also a center of financial institutions and various industries.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Grand and majestic buildings are spread throughout the city and are terrific examples of its august past and present. From the Royal Palace of Brussels to the famous Manneken Pis fountain, Brussels has plenty to offer travelers from all walks of life.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With its many guildhalls, the Breadhouse and Town Hall, The Grand Place is one of the city&#38;#39;s most iconic landmarks. At night, the square is illuminated with hundreds of lights and a vibrant social scene. For astonishing architecture and spiritual enlightenment, head to St. Michael and Gudula Cathedral or Basilica of Koekelberg. The basilica is the world&#38;#39;s fifth largest church and presents the world&#38;#39;s largest Art Deco edifice.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Cultural pursuits in Brussels are plentiful, with more than 100 museums and various performing arts centers and a glorious opera hall. More modern landmarks include The Atomium, an enormous replica of an iron crystal housing various exhibits and a nighttime illumination of nearly 3,000 lights.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury from Start to Finish in Discounted Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your brilliant trip to Brussels with a luxury flight courtesy of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s amazingly low first class flight fares and reduced-price &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. Beginning with deluxe and exclusive airport lounges and ending with plush, premier accommodations aboard the world&#38;#39;s best airlines, your trip will be filled with spectacular services, delectable cuisine and spacious seating.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Knowledgeable travel professionals and an easy-to-use website are just two of the perks to using FlyFirst.com. In addition to outstanding service, we offer &#60;strong&#62;unparalleled discounts on premium flights&#60;/strong&#62; of every type. From &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; to one-way trips, we provide savings of up to 60 percent off published airfares. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll have the confidence that you are paying the very lowest first class fares available so you can enjoy Brussels&#38;#39; many gorgeous features.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3740</first_class_price><business_class_price>2530</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minute Business Class Deals, Cheap First Class Deals, Cheap Business Class airfare. </description><keywords>Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares, last minute business class fares, discounted airlines deals, first class deals, international business class fares, cheap business class to Brussels</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ba082980857043668f34676f056686ab.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Cheap First Class To Brussels </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>df9f38869ecb46289f287b4eab36e525.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>f7ccb86cf7cf4f909073db9396a04aca.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class to Brussels </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>25</city_id><country_id>19</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Frankfurt</name><title>Affordable Business Class Flights &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets to Frankfurt </title><alias>Cheap-First-Business-Class-Flight-to-Frankfurt</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Frankfurt, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Frankfurt. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.

    &#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Germany. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Make your long flight to Frankfurt pleasurable with the deep discounts on first class flights and half-priced business class fares from FlyFirst.&#38;#160;You&#38;#39;ll save a great deal of money, and you&#38;#39;ll enjoy all idyllic amenities of first-rate air travel.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Pristine Landscaping, Booming Business and Rich Heritage&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There is so much to see and experience in Frankfurt that you will appreciate arriving in the restful comfort of first class travel. With its robust industrial, commercial and financial markets, Frankfurt is filled with modern skyscrapers alongside many historic cultural sites. Colorful blooming plants that surround public thoroughfares, public buildings and private homes, gives the city a uniquely welcoming and pristine ambiance.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Travelers who are in Frankfurt for &#60;strong&#62;business appreciate&#60;/strong&#62; the city&#38;#39;s role as the largest financial center in continental Europe and the headquarters of the European Central Bank. Its world-leading financial institutions, countless skyscrapers, burgeoning industries and location on the Main River give Frankfurt its nickname of Mainhattan.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Cultural delights are abundant in Frankfurt, from dozens of museums to the Archaeological Garden&#38;#39;s ancient Roman settlement remnants. Gothic and medieval architectural treasures are scattered throughout Frankfurt. Favorite sites include Saint Bartholomew&#38;#39;s Cathedral, R&#38;ouml;merberg Square and its buildings that have served as City Hall for more than 600 years and Eschenheim Tower.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Enjoy the Luxury of First and Business Class Flights&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your journey to Frankfurt in comfort with help from FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar first class deals and deeply discounted business class flights. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy exclusive entree to select airport lounges where you&#38;#39;ll receive refreshing spa services, a bountiful buffet of food, refreshments, entertainment and an opportunity to mingle with other luxury travelers over cocktails. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll relax in plush leather seats, doze peacefully in flat beds and cushy comforters, dine on exquisite meals and enjoy enough space to work comfortably.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our expert travel professionals offer you unparalleled service and a variety of travel options to best suit your needs. Whether you require a &#60;strong&#62;last minute flight&#60;/strong&#62;, a &#60;strong&#62;one-way ticket &#60;/strong&#62;or need to coordinate traveling to multiple cities, our travel professionals provide you with the same great service and the same terrific discounts. With FlyFirst.com, &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62; won&#38;#39;t bust your budget, and it won&#38;#39;t take forever to plan. Simply give us a call or use our quick online travel database to find out just how &#60;strong&#62;affordable&#60;/strong&#62; your trip to Frankfurt can be. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you book with the confidence that you are receiving the very best deals available on&#60;strong&#62; first class tickets and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3430</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minute Business Class Airline
    Ticket,First Class Airline Flight To Frankfurt, Frankfurt Business Last Minute First, Tracker Visa, Corporate Account, Business Class Airfares</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class Flight, Last Minute Business Class Ticket , tickets cheap fare, Tracker Visa, Corporate Account, Business Class Airfares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0e6ce3221e7742b9804d9647d4ec577d.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fares to Frankfurt</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>25cb9c94035340a9b6902227a4d7fe57.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>First Class Last Minute </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a8f02e21d1b94beda2d8bcd1b5daee2a.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class to Frankfurt</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>26</city_id><country_id>13</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>London</name><title>Cheap Business Flights &#38; First Class Tickets To London, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Tickets-to-London</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to London, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to London. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.

    &#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to London. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Experience the ultimate trip to London with FlyFirst&#38;#39;s affordable business class flights and first class fares, and you&#38;#39;ll save nearly 60 percent off published airfare so that you can experience the old and the new in London.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The River Thames, Big Ben and Treasured Gems&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For more than two millennia, London has been the touchstone of development, beginning as a Roman settlement and growing to the established, but not stagnant, global city of today. Its ever-changing progress is highlighted in its influence in finance, industry and culture and is showcased in the recent opening of The Shard, the 72-skyscraper that forever changed London&#38;#39;s skyline.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Even with exciting new skyscrapers, London retains its charming historical buildings and features. Big Ben, Tower Bridge, Buckingham Palace, Trafalgar Square and St. Paul&#38;#39;s Cathedral are fascinating, both for their history and their exquisite architecture. Throughout the London area, visitors are presented with Georgian and Tudor castles, Gothic palaces, majestic cathedrals and Victorian manses, creating contrast and unity in the eclectic metropolis that is London.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Culture abounds here, too, with sparkling gems of creativity such as delectable five-star restaurants, high-end shopping boutiques, famed theatrical productions, enchanting museums and a vivacious music scene. All are attractions to be experienced by both business and pleasure travelers and offer terrific entertainment at the end of the day.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Almost Fit for a Queen with Discounted First Class Ticket&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all that London has to offer and experience, making the long flight to jolly old England in comfort and style is a wise choice. Blissful first and business class journeys begin at the airport with exclusive lounges featuring serene lounges, scrumptious food and refreshment, refreshing spa services and an opportunity to socialize with other luxury travelers.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Premium airplane cabins continue the white-glove service with culinary masterpieces, pampering bed turn-down service and all its&#38;#160;accouterments, lushly padded seats and ample work space and storage. All of these services are created to meet your every need and assure that you arrive in London rested and set to enjoy the big city.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Premium flights to London don&#38;#39;t require a royal budget when you use the amazing discounts offered by FlyFirst.com. Regardless of your needs, &#60;strong&#62;our luxury travel deals&#60;/strong&#62; are available on all types of flights, from one-way and round-trip fares to last minute and complicated flights.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Call us today to get started on planning your dream trip to London. Our expert travel professionals are standing by to find you the very &#60;strong&#62;best unpublished prices on business class flights and first class deal&#60;/strong&#62;s so that you can enjoy London to the fullest.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3740</first_class_price><business_class_price>2490</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First Class Tickets to London, Cheap Business Class flight to London, Last Minute Tickets, Cheap Flight To London, First Class Fares</description><keywords>First Class, Cheap Flights,Deals,Business Class To London, Last Minute Business Cheap, Affordable Fares, Cheap Flights, Airfare Sale</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>156870bec43b48828a04cafc5099d2c6.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>Cheap First Class to London</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ea5d3552722d4502a9386e6ea8e25f1a.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>bdab038dfe3b47bda52cce971e5806bc.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>First Class Ticket to London</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>27</city_id><country_id>32</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Tokyo</name><title>The Best Business Class Price &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets to Tokyo</title><alias>Cheap-First-Business-Class-Flight-to-Narita</alias><summary>Discounted Business Class to Tokyo. Last Minute First Class Tickets. FlyFirst Offers Ubeatable Prices in First Class.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;Arrive at Narita International Airport in style with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s incredible business and first class deals on last minute flights. Save 60 percent on published luxury airfares so you can spend some extra time in Japan to discover the beauty of both cities.&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Serene Narita&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;If you are flying to &#60;strong&#62;Tokyo&#60;/strong&#62; for business or vacation, chances are good that you will land in the town of Narita. It&#38;#39;s home to the Tokyo area&#38;#39;s major international airport and is used by more than 35 million passengers each year. Before you head over to Tokyo, though, take a few hours to explore Narita&#38;#39;s charming sights.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The Great Main Hall, an 18th-century three-story pagoda and a modern 190-foot Great Pagoda of Peace are just a few of the notable showpieces of Naritasan Shinshoji Temple. The sacred 10th-century Shingon Buddhist temple is an extremely large complex, replete with bubbling fountains, springtime cherry and plum blossoms, an impressive main gate, incredible architecture and an expansive park. Daily Goma ritual amulet&#38;#160;burning, frequent festivals and seasonal ceremonial Sutra of Great Wisdom chantings keep the temple&#38;#39;s spiritual nature alive and offer Westerners a glimpse of cherished religious rites.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Bustling Tokyo in Business Class Flight and Discolunted First Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Just a quick 35-mile high-speed rail trip away, Tokyo isn&#38;#39;t just Japan&#38;#39;s financial and cultural capital, it holds similar significance in the international arena as well. Along with London and New York, Tokyo is viewed as a world economy command center. It is the world&#38;#39;s largest metropolitan region, and it&#38;#39;s home to 51 Fortune Global 500 businesses. Its local brands are popular around the world and span all industries, from Hello Kitty to Honda and from Sanyo to Sony.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Business and pleasure travelers delight in experiencing &#60;strong&#62;Tokyo&#60;/strong&#62;&#38;#39;s nightlife after a long day of work or sightseeing. Dining in Tokyo is a delectable treat as it is home to more Michelin-rated restaurants than any other global city, even Paris.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Adventures in Tokyo are plentiful. Take an invigorating walk across the gorgeous Rainbow Bridge, wander through Ueno Park&#38;#39;s many museums or head out to the volcanic Izu Islands to visit Fuji-Hakone-Izu National Park.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your long flight to Narita as relaxing as possible by traveling in the comfort of premium cabins. Our FlyFirst.com &#60;strong&#62;discounts are available&#60;/strong&#62; whether you are seeking &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; or planning your trip well in advance. FlyFirst.com offers you the confidence that you are getting the best fares available and the highest level of service. Call our travel professionals today to receive our &#60;strong&#62;best business and first class deals to Narita&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4950</first_class_price><business_class_price>3780</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Business and First Class Flights Cheap to Narita, Narita First Class fares, Last Minute First Class airline flight</description><keywords>Cheap First Class, First Class, Business Airfare, Last Minute First Class, Last minute business class airfare, business class airline, discounted airline fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e14f57686eac4fc581fc4a5d425ad5d9.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class To Narita</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>f8b0461163f244458f13129dc209aa4d.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>First Class Tickets to Narita</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>fba49743a5254d0c8f9bc83c1e526fcd.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare to Narita</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>28</city_id><country_id>20</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Paris</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights To Paris, Cheap Last Minute Flights.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-to-Paris</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Paris, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Paris. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;History, Haute Couture and Hors d&#38;#39;Oeuvres&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;A trip to Paris isn&#38;#39;t complete without a visit to the city&#38;#39;s most remarkable sites such as Basilique du Sacr&#38;eacute;-Coeur and Cath&#38;eacute;drale Notre Dame. Cruise down Voie Triomphale, leading you through some of the city&#38;#39;s most interesting landmarks along the famed Champs Elys&#38;eacute;es and beyond. Beginning at Mus&#38;eacute;e du Louvre, travel through the Tuilleries Gardens, the obelisk at Place du Concorde, the Arc de Triomphe du Caroussel, and on to the Arc de Triomphe in Charles de Gaulle Place. At the very northwest end of Voie Triomphale is the majestic Grande Arche de la Fraternit&#38;eacute;.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Explore the city&#38;#39;s many works of art housed in world-famous museums such Mus&#38;eacute;e du Louvre and Mus&#38;eacute;e d&#38;#39;Orsay or any of the 100-plus Paris museums. Decorative art, manuscripts, aerospace and miniatures are just a few of the items displayed in Paris museums.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Famously admired for its high fashion and acclaimed fashion weeks, Paris is home to a number of shopping districts. It&#38;#39;s back to the Champs Elys&#38;eacute;es for high-end shops such as Louis Vuitton and Guerlain as well as more moderately priced stores such as Nike, Sephora and H&#38;amp;M. Exclusive cosmetics, apparel, perfumeries and home interior stores line Avenue Montaigne, Fuaubourg Saint-Honor&#38;eacute; and Boulevard Haussmann.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    To refresh after a day of touring and shopping, enjoy some of Paris&#38;#39; legendary cuisine. Whether you choose a baguette or pastry from a classic bakery, an informal snack at a sidewalk cafe or a multiple-course meal at a Michelin-ranked restaurant, delectable food is a serious pursuit in Paris.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Treat Yourself to the Luxury of Discounted First Class and Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;As a first or business class traveler, you have an exclusive invitation to some of the world&#38;#39;s best airport lounges. Start your trip with a little pampering at the airport with delicious refreshments, relaxing spa services, bountiful entertainment, ample workspace and assistance from devoted concierges. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy large leather seats, high-end meals, plenty of storage and bed turn-down services. All this ensures that you arrive in Paris feeling relaxed and able to enjoy the city&#38;#39;s treasures.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At FlyFirst.com the &#60;strong&#62;luxury of premium travel&#60;/strong&#62; is affordable, with savings of up to 60 percent off regular rack rates. Our travel professionals offer unrivaled service and the deepest &#60;strong&#62;discounts around&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today to plan your dream trip to Paris aboard luxurious half-price &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets and first class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3670</first_class_price><business_class_price>2590</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Airline Flight, Cheap Flights to France, Cheap Airline Business class fares to Paris</description><keywords>Cheap Tickets, Airline business cheap tickets, Airlines discounted, cheap airfares, last minute business class fares, discounted airlines deals, first class deals, international business class fares, Cheap Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>deb35d09d99f45bfa8de24051206a8d5.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Ticket To Paris</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>90efdf6f5f7a4c26a2cdef416f921818.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Business Class Flight To Paris</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c91c8119c55a4b3eb8b40bea74a85743.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Discounted Business class Flight</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>29</city_id><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Perth</name><title>Cheap Flights in Business &#38; First Class Airfares To Perth, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save up to 70%</title><alias>Discounted-Business-Class-Fares-to-Perth</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Perth, we specialize on last minute business class Airfares, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Perth. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Perth. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Make your long-distant flight to Perth in luxury with FlyFirst&#38;#39;s half-price business class flights and deeply reduced first class fares. The steep savings and premium amenities will make your journey to Perth enjoyable so that you can roam Western Australian with energy and money to spare.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Beacons, Beaches and Bells&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The City of Light, as it came to be known in 1962 for its illuminations visible to astronaut John Glenn in orbit around the earth, is a beacon to many travelers. Its international airport is just 20 minutes from Perth&#38;#39;s downtown, and its port is thriving.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Closer to East Timor and Indonesia than Sydney, Perth is an urban center in vast Western Australia and serves as its capital and financial, educational and cultural centers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Although its high-rise buildings lie on the shores of the Swan River, the Indian Ocean surf is not far away. Nearly 20 idyllic beaches surround Perth, from Scarborough&#38;#39;s vibrant surf scene to the crystal-clear water of Cottesloe Beach.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Roam Kings Park, the world&#38;#39;s largest inner-city park. Delight in the mellifluous ringing of the Swan Bells, the world&#38;#39;s largest musical instruments. Snorkel and swim in nearby Rottnest Island. Sip delectable homegrown vintages in Swan Valley. Ride a camel along the surf of Cable Beach or frolic with pods of wild dolphins in Rockingham. For the ultimate adventure, head east to experience the vast beauty and wildlife of the Outback. Perth is brimming with activities and abundant natural beauty just waiting to be explored.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Style on the Trip of a Lifetime in Discounted Business Class Airfares&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the long journey to Perth a comfortable one with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s discount first class tickets or reduced-fare &#60;strong&#62;business class airfares&#60;/strong&#62; on the world&#38;#39;s best airlines. Exclusive airport lounge access is just the beginning, although an impressive experience in its own right.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Your premium airline seating is plush leather and roomy enough to spread out to relax or work. Meals are designed by world-famous chefs, and the beverages are free-flowing. Bed turn-down service includes a sumptuous down comforter, crisp pajamas, lovely pillows and flat, mattress-topped beds. With &#60;strong&#62;premium seats&#60;/strong&#62;, your flight time will be restful, productive and comfortable.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our expert professionals and deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted premium flights&#60;/strong&#62; are just the beginning of our industry-leading services. Whether you require a one-way ticket, last minute flight or a complicated itinerary, we offer you the same stellar discounts of nearly 60 percent off published airfares. When you book your trip to Perth with FlyFirst.com, you book with the confidence that you are saving substantially on sumptuous &#60;strong&#62;first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and amenity-filled &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4630</first_class_price><business_class_price>3780</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Business Class Ticket To Perth, Cheap Airfare to Perth in First Class, Business class ticket, Cheap Flight to Perth </description><keywords>affordable first Class tickets,save money on First Class Tickets, cheap business class travel deals, cheap flights travel deals, Business travel, First Class Travel, cheap discounted business class travel, Cheap Flight to Perth</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>16c7e2d79232488599863849850b86ce.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Seats </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>a39c513639f346d1857ef1bb2c59aae1.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>First Class Flights</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a9bcc7728609433381a245cecda01a24.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>Last Minute Business class to Perth </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>30</city_id><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Sydney</name><title>Cheap First Class Flights To Sydney , Discounted Business Class Flights</title><alias>Cheap-First-Business-Class-to-Sydney</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Sydney, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Sydney. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;With these 60 percent savings on luxury flights, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Oz rested and ready to conquer the city&#38;#39;s many delights.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Teeming Streets, Towering Waterfalls and Turquoise Seas&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Even business travelers get a thrill when making the trip to Sydney. Opportunities abound in the world&#38;#39;s 7th most economically important city. Its plentiful multinational corporations regional headquarters and leading Australian companies are buoyed by the city&#38;#39;s busy shipping port and a very convenient international airport. Fortunately for those secluded in meetings all day, Sydney&#38;#39;s after-hours activities are just as exciting as its daytime attractions.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    At night, delight in the city&#38;#39;s fine dining, Sydney Harbour cruising and high-end shopping in Double Bay, or take in a show at the famed Sydney Opera House. If you are lucky enough to be in town at the end of May or early June, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to a special illumination, laser, music and creativity festival, Vivid Sydney. Many of Sydney&#38;#39;s buildings are alight during the festival, including illuminated images on Sydney Opera House&#38;#39;s architectural &#38;quot;sails.&#38;quot;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Tour some of the city&#38;#39;s most treasured buildings such as Parliament House, St. Andrews Anglican Cathedral, Sydney Opera House and Sydney Tower. Meander through Royal Botanical Gardens or head west to enjoy the magnificent waterfalls and hiking canyons of the Blue Mountains.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The Luxury of Business and First Class to Sydney&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Start experiencing the glitz and&#38;#160;glamour&#38;#160;of Sydney before you even embark on your plane. As first and business class travelers, you gain exclusive entrance to some of the world&#38;#39;s best airport lounges. Relax before and between your flights with complimentary refreshments, buffets, dining, entertainment, various spa and freshening services and business center services. Grab a cocktail to hobnob with other high-end travelers and enjoy access to immigration and customs desks reserved purely for luxury clients.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Aboard your airplane, you&#38;#39;ll sink into plush leather seats with plenty of elbow room and work surfaces, dine on five-star meals, relax with complimentary adult beverages and enjoy bed turn-down services. The end result is an incomparable experience that is the fitting beginning to a sophisticated trip to Sydney.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Last minute first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; receive the very same &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; and services of complicated trips with multi-city destinations at FlyFirst.com. Regardless of your travel needs, we offer the greatest &#60;strong&#62;discounts on luxury travel to Sydney&#60;/strong&#62; and other exciting ports-of-call. From bargain business class fares to affordable first class tickets, FlyFirst.com helps you book your trip with confidence and ease, all the better to enjoy an impeccable sojourn to Sydney.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4590</first_class_price><business_class_price>3560</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First class airline tickets, Business Class Last Minute Fares, First and Business Cheap to Australia, Cheap Class flight to Australia</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class Flight, Last Minute Flights, Business Class, Cheap Flight, Cheap Airfare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>4d6b352d010f40ad85c9198889b0236f.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Cheap First Class to Sydney </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7f882e38e1244fa6bc88a1dc15440523.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class To Sydney</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>9a0cafb592c24a2e8a039257340ea181.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>First Class Cheap To Sydney</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>31</city_id><country_id>18</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Rome</name><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights to Rome, Discounted First Class Tickets </title><alias>Business-Class-Flight-Rome</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Rome, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Rome. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Rome. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size:14px;&#34;&#62;The flight to Italy can even be part of the sumptuous experience when you travel in the lavish luxury of &#60;strong&#62;affordable first class seats and discount business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Ruins, Runways and Religion&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With a dozen renowned cities and even more small, charming villages, Italy offers a variety of locales and attractions to suit every interest. In the center of the country, Rome invites visitors to revel in ancient wonders such as the Colosseum and the Forum. Michaelangelo&#38;#39;s Piazza del Campidoglio is just a 15-minute stroll from the Colosseum and home to the magnificent basilica Santa Maria in Aracoeli, Palazzo Senatorio, Palazzo Nuovo and the Tabularium. Dozens of museums, fountains, statues and cathedrals are spread throughout Rome, offering plenty of activities for travelers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;For world-class fashion shows and stellar shopping, trendsetters trek to Milan, the world&#38;#39;s celebrated fashion capital. While many visitors are occupied with the shopping in cosmopolitan Milan&#38;#39;s Fashion Quadrangle, others spend some time enjoying the city&#38;#39;s various historic sites. From the majestic white marble spires of the Gothic-era Duomo cathedral to the acclaimed performances at La Scala opera house, Milan is a perfect blend of modern culture and history.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Italy also offers countless delights for the senses. Drama, mystery and intrigue flourish at Carnivale in Venice. Elaborate costumes and intricate, surreal masks make the festival a unique experience in an already-enigmatic city. For a taste of the country&#38;#39;s famed vintages, head to Italy&#38;#39;s Tuscany region where the sun is warm, the hills are gentle and the locals are welcoming. Limoncello liqueur and dramatic seaside cliffs draw visitors to southern Italy&#38;#39;s Amalfi Coast, while abundant recreation takes travelers to Italy&#38;#39;s northern regions and the Italian Alps.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Travel Offers Pampering Comfort in Discounted Business and First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Every trip is better when it&#38;#39;s made in the posh style of first and business class flights. Services and amenities are specifically designed to help you make the most of your flight time, from spacious work surfaces and electronic access to seats that convert to flat, plush beds. Even better, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy the services of exclusive airport lounges before, between and after your flights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on first class flights to Italy and receive spectacular service from our expert travel professionals. Whether you need affordable &#60;strong&#62;business class seats on last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; or deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class ticket&#60;/strong&#62;s on a multi-city trip, you can rest assured that you are receiving the very best possible deals. Call us today to access our stellar deals on first class seats and business class fares to intriguing Italy.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3890</first_class_price><business_class_price>2760</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First Class Trips To Rome, Business Class Fare to Rome, Cheap Airfares, Cheap Airline Tickets</description><keywords>Cheap Deals in Business and First Class Flights, cheap airline tickets, First Class Airline Tickets cheap</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>2c2e4a3f69be428a80e73a64f4498126.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Airline Ticket</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9a0354f89b3b40eea594e33ca7d76e48.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>7a823b2f3c984c45ae0c345d92e898ff.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Cheap First Class To Rome</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>32</city_id><country_id>8</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Shanghai</name><title>Cheap Business Class &#38; Discounted First Class Fares , Save Thousands to Shanghai</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-Shanghai</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Shanghai, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Shanghai. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;With the tranquil atmosphere and &#60;strong&#62;ultimate service of first and business class&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Shanghai completely refreshed and set to enjoy the metropolis&#38;#39; many delights.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Finance, Fashion and Confucius&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;China&#38;#39;s largest city and fifth-ranked global city, Shanghai is a major international finance center, drawing millions of visitors each year. With interests in technology, shipping, media, culture and fashion, business travel to the megalopolis is vigorous, making FlyFirst.com business class flight deals even more critical.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Tourists to Shanghai will delight in Shanghai&#38;#39;s fashion districts, including the 600-plus shops along Naning Road and twice yearly Fashion Week activities. Plentiful museums, historic districts, river cruises and landmarks make for vigorous tour itineraries.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A melting pot of architecture, Shanghai&#38;#39;s The Bund rests along the Huangpu River bank, 26 buildings of mixed 20th century styles. For decades, The Bund was the quintessential icon for Shanghai. Today, it&#38;#39;s nearly one-mile stretch houses neo-classical, Beax-Arts, gothic revival and Art Deco buildings along one of Shanghai&#38;#39;s most popular tourist destinations.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The broad range of temples devoted to various faiths is a testament to the city&#38;#39;s tolerance for diverse religions. A tourist favorite, City God Temple, is a Taoist temple located in the Old City, featuring remarkable altars, traditional architecture and various shops, pavilions and tea gardens. While on your excursion, visit the Confucius temple Wenmiao or the Buddhist temples Jing&#38;#39;an and the Jade Buddha. Islamic faith traveled to Shanghai in the 13th century and the Songjiang Mosque is a perfect blend of Chinese and Islamic architecture.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury for Less in Discounted Business Class Cabin&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Spend your 12- to 15-hour flight to Shanghai in a relaxing, spacious environment aboard premium airplane cabins. While booking through FlyFirst.com can save you up to 60 percent on regular and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, you will receive all the usual exclusive services and amenities. From deluxe airport lounges to on-board five-star cuisine and white-glove service, you&#38;#39;ll spend your flight time resting, working in comfort and sleeping peacefully.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At FlyFirst.com your every comfort is our priority. From quick, professional service to access to the biggest &#60;strong&#62;business class flight deals&#60;/strong&#62; and stellar &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com helps you book with confidence.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4920</first_class_price><business_class_price>3670</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>last minute first class fares to shanghai,china,
    Cheap Airline Tickets, Business Class Discounts, Cheap First Class Airline</description><keywords>Cheap Airline Tickets, Business Class Discounts, Cheap First Class Airline, Cheap fares, Cheap First, Business Class, Last Minute, Shanghai Business</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8fd398ba9f88476192662ddcae0f61e9.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Best Business Class Deals to Shanghai</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>4b78c6be506942eb8835cd9f236e4f1d.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>275a81d34b604f63b443be9240d1e8b5.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Seats To Shanghai </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>33</city_id><country_id>10</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Zurich</name><title>Affordable First Class Fares &#38; Deeply Discounted Business Class Flights to Zurich</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-to-Zurich</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Zurich, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Zurich. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Zurich. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;More Than Clockmaking and Divine Chocolates&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Zurich is a gleaming global city with a vibrant financial center and many major international banks and international research centers. As one of Europe&#38;#39;s most wealthy cities, it&#38;#39;s no surprise that gastronomic delights abound in the city. A robust culinary scene features 1,500-plus restaurants and, of course, endless fine chocolate makers. Visitors enjoy world-class lodging, trendy shopping, numerous museums and fascinating art galleries.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Old Town Alstadt holds charming streets that are perfect for strolling, soaking in the Swiss atmosphere and finding stores that are hidden gems. The streets are lined with old cobblestones and the buildings retain their charming old guild signs. Gorgeous Romanesque architecture is found in Zurich&#38;#39;s many churches such as Grossmunster.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Begin or end your day with a trip to the magical Top of Zurich. Trams transport visitors up to the Uetliberg mountain for an incredible view of Lake Zurich and the surrounding city.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;It&#38;#39;s the Journey, Not the Destination&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;For business and pleasure travelers alike, the lengthy flight to Zurich can be made comfortable in the luxury of&#60;strong&#62; first class&#60;/strong&#62; and the spaciousness of &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;. FlyFirst&#38;#39;s stellar &#60;strong&#62;deals on first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;half-price business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; makes a pleasurable flight accessible to all.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    You&#38;#39;ll be pampered from the minute you step into the airport, with an exclusive invitation to select airport lounges. Before and between flights, you can enjoy expansive buffets, cocktails with other high-end travelers, freshening and spa services, abundant entertainment and, often, expedited access to immigrations and customs services reserved for luxury travelers.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Top airlines spare no expense on catering to &#60;strong&#62;first and business class&#60;/strong&#62; customers. Over-sized seats are clad in leather, well-padded and frequently lie fully flat to encourage a good night&#38;#39;s sleep. Meals are designed by today&#38;#39;s top chefs, and great thought and funding is put into state-of-the-art entertainment systems. With all these amenities, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Zurich feeling relaxed and ready to enjoy the city.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At FlyFirst.com, we make flying in luxury affordable. Our access to unpublished airfares translates into savings of up to 60 percent off rack rates. Whether you need last minute flights to Zurich, multi-city destinations or one-way tickets, we offer you the very best prices on air travel. Our expert travel professionals are adept at unearthing the greatest deals around on &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can spend your time and money experiencing the world-class city of Zurich.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3440</first_class_price><business_class_price>2680</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>1</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First Class Airline Flights, Business class Cheap Airline to Zurich, Business cheap fare </description><keywords>First, Business Class, Last Minute Business Class, Cheap Flights, First Class Airline to Zurich, Airline Tickets, Tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7592b5ce36fa4319a6306076c5c285d9.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Best First Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9df44698871c467aae44d047898d8b05.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Business Class Discounts</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>ce43915563944904b0a78258bf006efd.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Affordable First Class Airfare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>34</city_id><country_id>26</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Seoul</name><title>Discounted First Class Airfares And Best Business Class Deals To Seoul</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Fligh-to-Seoul</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Seoul, we specialize on last minute first class aiorfares, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Seoul. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Seoul. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The Luxury of Korean Air&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Korean Air offers posh and private&#60;strong&#62; Kosmo first class suites&#60;/strong&#62; featuring wide, plush seats that are 15 cm larger than most other first class seats. A convenient touch-pad adjusts the seat back and leg support to all angles for maximum comfort, and the state-of-the-art Beyond AVOD entertainment system ensures a pleasurable way to pass the flight time. Its five-star cuisine is a perfect blend of Korean, Japanese, Chinese and western fare to please a variety of refined palates.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;span style=&#34;font-size:14px;&#34;&#62;&#60;strong&#62;The airline&#38;#39;s prestigious services and amenities are frequently awarded by national and international travel organizations. Korean Air&#38;#39;s recent awards include&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;ul&#62;
    &#60;li style=&#34;margin-left: 12pt;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;Best in-flight meal, Mercury Award, International Flight Catering Association&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li style=&#34;margin-left: 12pt;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;Top 10 Best First Class Airline Seats, World Airline Awards&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li style=&#34;margin-left: 12pt;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;Top 10 Best Airline in Asia, 2012 World Airline Awards&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li style=&#34;margin-left: 12pt;&#34;&#62;&#38;#160;Most Innovative Airline, Grand Final, World Travel Awards and&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;li style=&#34;margin-left: 12pt;&#34;&#62;&#60;em&#62;&#38;#160;Travel + Leisure&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;magazine&#38;#39;s &#38;quot;Most Preferred Airline in China.&#38;quot;&#60;/li&#62;
    &#60;/ul&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The FlyFirst Advantage&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With an ordinary booking service, you could expect to pay as much as $12,000 on a&#60;strong&#62; first class flight to Seoul from Australia&#60;/strong&#62;. With FirstClass&#38;#39;s tremendous&#60;strong&#62; first class deals to Seoul &#60;/strong&#62;on Korea Air, you will pay a small fraction of that amount. Even better, those 30 to 70 percent discounts are available on all types of travel to Seoul, from quick, last minute trips and complicated multi-city itineraries to one-way flights and round-trip tickets. Whatever your travel needs, FlyFirst can offer you unparalleled discounts and the comfort and style you expect. In some cases, we can even offer you &#60;strong&#62;first class flights to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62; that are less expensive that economy fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Leave the Planning to Us&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our expert travel advisers deftly unearth the best deals and coordinate all the small details of an international flight to Seoul, saving you precious time and money. Just give us a call toll-free at 800-385-1359 or fill out our online form, then let our knowledgeable travel professionals take care of the details. Call us today so you can save thousands of dollars on our unmatched &#60;strong&#62;first class flight airfares to Seoul&#60;/strong&#62; at FlyFirst.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4480</first_class_price><business_class_price>3360</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Airfares, First Class Tickets Cheap, Cheap Flights, Discounted Airline Deals to Seoul , Korea</description><keywords>Cheap, Business Class, Tickets Sale, Discounted airline fares, first Class cheap. Last Minute Business Class Air, Cheap Flight To Seoul, Korea</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>dd536a8a512f4f618cf0fbc6c147e3bc.jpg</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>First Class Flight Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3d0408d9a17c4ee8a2bff7887d70a3d3.jpg</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>Business Class Flight Deals</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>81c95bea70b24bf89414dd565297f3a5.jpg</alias><content_id>34</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Fares</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>35</city_id><country_id>19</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Munich</name><title>Save Thousands On The Best Business Class Flight Deals &#38; Firs Class Discounts to Munich</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Ticket-To-Munich</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Munich, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Munich. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Munich. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Gleaming and modern, warm and historic, the city of Munich is a treasure trove of Bavarian gems just waiting to be explored. Travel to gorgeous Bavaria in sumptuous luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s remarkable &#60;strong&#62;savings on first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. We&#38;#39;ll save you as much as 70 percent on luxury flights so that you can explore the wonders of Munich to your heart&#38;#39;s content.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Churches, Theaters and Sports Arenas&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;At the center of Munich is the Marientplatz, the heart of old Munich. Here, visitors delight in the historic buildings and grand architecture of New Town Hall and the old medieval city&#38;#39;s gates: Isartor, Karlstor and Sendlinger Tor. The Marientplatz is home to Frauenkirche, ornately beautiful and the inner city&#38;#39;s most famous church.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In fact, Munich houses dozens of stunning, historic churches. Near the Marientplatz, tourists can find the largest Renaissance church north of the Alps at St. Michael&#38;#39;s Church, the domed Theatine Church of St. Cajetan and St. Anna of Lehel, Bavaria&#38;#39;s first rococo church.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Travelers and locals alike revel in the city&#38;#39;s renowned museums and theaters adjacent to Old Town at the Residenz palace complex. Relish a breathtaking performance at the National Theater, the site where several of Richard Wagner&#38;#39;s operas premiered, or enjoy a show at the Residenz Theater. Stroll along some of Munich&#38;#39;s famed royal avenues to see a variety of Bavaria&#38;#39;s other fascinating structures such as The Maximilianeum and Nymphenburg Palace.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Sports and community events are popular in Munich. Take in a game at the ultra-modern Allianz Arena, home to two professional soccer teams: Bayern Munich and 1860 Munich. It&#38;#39;s a special treat at night as the spherical-shaped arena changes colors. For a little taste of the local brew, head to the Hofbr&#38;auml;uhaus am Platzl, one of the world&#38;#39;s most famous beer halls and the site of an immense Oktoberfest celebration.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Luxury to Munich&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;There&#38;#39;s no need to travel in cramped economy coach to a world-class city like Munich when FlyFirst.com can get you there in style with amazing deals on &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. As a premium traveler, you&#38;#39;ll have an exclusive invitation to lavish airport lounges where you can enjoy plentiful high-end amenities. On board your flight, you&#38;#39;ll be pampered with delectable dishes created by world-famous chefs, luxurious seats and high-end service.&#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;br /&#62;
    Our skilled travel professionals are experts at finding you affordable premium airfare and coordinating all of your travel needs. Just give us a call at 888-347-7817, and we will provide you with outstanding savings and stellar service. Call us today to secure your &#60;strong&#62;deals on business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; to the beautiful Bavarian city of Munich.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3470</first_class_price><business_class_price>2680</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Save on First Class Tickets to Munich from FlyFirst.com, Cheap First Class Last Minute Flights, Cheap Fares, First Class Tickets to Munich </description><keywords>Save on First Class Tickets to Munich from FlyFirst.com, Cheap First Class Tickets, Cheap Business Class Fares </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b37c8d30d8c043f7b537b6d4819f32b4.jpg</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>Beast Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cf4ccb9481eb43e4aae8766a42157290.jpg</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>4ddbfe3bcf744615a9a9e8f72327e838.jpg</alias><content_id>35</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>36</city_id><country_id>24</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Moscow</name><title>Best Business Class Deals &#38; Cheap Last Minute First Class Travel To Moscow</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Flight-To-Moscow</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Moscow, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Moscow. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Moscow. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Whether Moscow is just one part of a multi-city trip or your only destination, FlyFirst.com can save you as much as 70 percent on your premium flight.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Venture to Moscow to experience the majestic architecture and appealing intrigue of Europe&#38;#39;s most populous city. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll save thousands of dollars on first class flights and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; to the vibrant city and still enjoy all the full-priced comforts of luxury airline travel. Whether Moscow is just one part of a multi-city trip or your only destination, FlyFirst.com can save you as much as 70 percent on your premium flight.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exotic, Romantic, Historic&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The blending of cultures over Moscow&#38;#39;s many centuries have created a leading metropolitan city that heavily influences the world&#38;#39;s economy, political and cultural scene and industrial fortitude. With more billionaires than any other city in the world, Moscow is a land of opportunity for many and a land of mystery and history for others.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you are traveling to Moscow for pleasure or business, there are a few must-see sites to fit into your itinerary. The colorful and intricate elements of Russian architecture is best seen in St. Basil&#38;#39;s Cathedral and Novodevichy Convent. There&#38;#39;s a wealth of history in the two 16th-century buildings, as well. Other awe-inspiring buildings in the city hearken back to various periods in Moscow&#38;#39;s past, including Cathedral of Christ the Saviour, Tsaritsyno Park and palace, the Triumphal Arch of Moscow and Red Square and the Kremlin.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Stalin-era skyscapers, the so-called Seven Sisters, punctuate the city&#38;#39;s skyline and lead the way to the city&#38;#39;s modern renaissance. They offer terrific views of the city&#38;#39;s landmarks and the Moskva River. While exploring the city&#38;#39;s more modern amenities, be sure to visit its lavish malls, GUM and TSUM near Red Square. They house world-class shops that are infamous for their high-priced merchandise, but are set among amazing architecture and design features. With all that you&#38;#39;ll save on your flight with FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty of money to spare on a few lavish purchases. After a day of shopping, touring or working, the city is filled with high-end nightclubs that make perfect locations for unwinding.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;FlyFirst.com takes the stress out of traveling across the world to exotic destinations like Moscow. Our experienced travel specialists are skilled at finding you the &#60;strong&#62;best first and business class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and coordinating every aspect of your trip. All that you need to do is call us and then sit back, relax and enjoy the luxury of &#60;strong&#62;first and business class travel&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll be able to enjoy your trip even more knowing that you saved up to 70 percent on your airfare and paid less than your fellow travelers. Call us toll-free at 888-347-7817, and you&#38;#39;ll be well on your way to getting tremendous &#60;strong&#62;first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and amazing &#60;strong&#62;discounts on business class seats to Moscow&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4170</first_class_price><business_class_price>3280</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Business Class Airline Fares, Cheap Business, Last Minute First Class to Moscow, Moscow business class deals </description><keywords>Last Minute , Business Class Tickets Cheap to Moscow, Flights, Cheap, deals, Business Class air, Discount, Airline to Moscow</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b2a9ddd4f7fc4f41b0ebb34d3fb946da.jpg</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>Best Business Class Airfares</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>a74f975901304ad5b9fde2535b14168c.jpg</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>968d6eaaaffe4ab791ae59a5e24bea1d.jpg</alias><content_id>36</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>37</city_id><country_id>8</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Beijing</name><title>Cheap Business Class Seats And Savings On Last Minute First Class Tickets to Beijing</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-To-Beijing</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Beijing, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Beijing. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Beijing. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;One of the most populated cities in the world, the city is home to magnificent temples, lush gardens, exquisite architecture and a rich cultural heritage.&#38;#160;From the Forbidden City&#38;#39;s Palace Museum to the gleaming buildings in the city&#38;#39;s Zhongguancun technology center, Beijing is a beautiful blend of ancient tradition and modern advances.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business or Pleasure?&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Dozens of Fortune 500 companies operate in Beijing, making it a popular destination for business travelers. Whether you are destined for China&#38;#39;s answer to Silicon Valley, Zhongguancun, or one of the bustling city&#38;#39;s many industrial complexes, don&#38;#39;t let business keep you from enjoying Beijing&#38;#39;s many delights.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Treat yourself like an emperor and visit the Summer Palace&#38;#39;s 290 acres of temples, parks, tea houses and lake, or view the contemplative grandeur of the Temple of Heaven in Tiantan Park. View Kubla Khan&#38;#39;s palace at Beihai Park, and walk in the footsteps of the ancients along the Great Wall.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;China&#38;#39;s rich culture is evident in Beijing&#38;#39;s many theatrical, artistic and performing arts offerings. Enjoy the city&#38;#39;s breathtaking acrobats at the Chaoyang Theater, a show at the National Center for the Performing Arts or the nightlife and art scene in Beijing&#38;#39;s 798 Arts District.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make the Trip in Luxury and Serenity&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Ensure that you enjoy the ultimate 12-hour flight to Beijing aboard some of the world&#38;#39;s most magnificent &#60;strong&#62;first and business class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. The splendor begins with upscale airport lounges reserved for &#60;strong&#62;business and first class&#60;/strong&#62; passengers. Once on board your luxury cabin, you&#38;#39;ll be attended to with a variety of pampering services. Settle in your comfortably spacious seat and enjoy the posh epicurean delights, entertainment systems, roomy work spaces and indulgent bed turn-down services. By the time you arrive in Beijing, you&#38;#39;ll be rested and ready to delight in the city&#38;#39;s bountiful features.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive FlyFirst Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our services are created with your every comfort in mind. We scour our resources for the best possible &#60;strong&#62;deals on first class&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; business class travel&#60;/strong&#62;. There&#38;#39;s no need for you to research airlines and spend hours on the Internet searching for the most&#60;strong&#62; affordable business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. We take the hassle out of planning your business trip or vacation getaway to Beijing by offering you the very &#60;strong&#62;best deals on first class airfare&#60;/strong&#62; and providing you with a variety of travel options.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Call Us Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We offer two easy ways to get the&#60;strong&#62; best deals on business and first class airfare&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us toll-free or fill out our easy online travel form. We will provide you with available travel discounts and give you the options you need to make your Beijing trip the most productive. With the quality of services and discounts we offer, FlyFirst will have you on your way in&#60;strong&#62; first class to Beijing&#60;/strong&#62; in no time at all.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>5380</first_class_price><business_class_price>3790</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description> CHEAP BUSINESS AND FIRST CLASS FLIGHTS TO BEIJING, Cheap Flights, Business Class Airfare cheap to Beijing, Airline Business Class fares </description><keywords> CHEAP BUSINESS AND FIRST CLASS FLIGHTS TO BEIJING, Last minute Business Class fares and Cheap discounted airline prices, Cheap Flights, last Minute fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b4920a34186d4fe392831d8f41d3be03.jpg</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Airfare</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>67bf667139dd4829a9d885c6aa548989.jpg</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>Reduced Price First Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>8257c3756415419e99ba42a9b889753e.jpg</alias><content_id>37</content_id><title>Best Last Minute Business Class Deals</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>38</city_id><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Adelaide</name><title>Affordable Business Class Flight And Best First Class Deals To Adelaide</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-To-Adelaide</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Adelaide, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Adelaide. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Adelaide. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Journey to south Australia, where the wines are delectable, the beaches are warm and the people are friendly. Your adventure to gorgeous Adelaide can be made in affordable luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s outstanding &#60;strong&#62;deals on first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. We&#38;#39;ll save you as much as 70 percent on premium travel so that you can spend all of your energy exploring Australia&#38;#39;s Fleurieu Peninsula and the Adelaide plains.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Rivers, Churches and Koalas&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Smaller, but no less thrilling and picturesque than Sydney and Melbourne, Adelaide is a vibrant and contemporary city teeming with defense and manufacturing industries. The city reaches from southern Australia&#38;#39;s Gulf of St. Vincent to Mount Lofty Ranges, offering abundant recreation, brilliant scenery and foothills that are perfect for thriving vineyards.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The River Torrens flows through sparkling Adelaide, creating plentiful riverside promenades, parks and trails enticing locals and visitors to bicycle, stroll and jog along the river&#38;#39;s banks. Many of Adelaide&#38;#39;s most beautiful structures are set along the river, as are many of the town&#38;#39;s famed festivals.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Nicknamed the &#38;quot;City of Churches&#38;quot; for its abundant places of worship, Adelaide&#38;#39;s most well-known church is the stunning Gothic Revival St. Francis Xavier&#38;#39;s Cathedral. Other don&#38;#39;t-miss places to tour include Parliament House, Chinatown, Adelaide Botanic Garden and South Australian Museum, where you&#38;#39;ll find the world&#38;#39;s largest collection of Australian Aboriginal artifacts.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Head to the Adelaide Hills for breathtaking views and scrumptious wines. Just east of the city in the Mount Lofty Ranges, is one of Australia&#38;#39;s largest wine regions. It is home to more than 90 wineries producing world-class red and white wines. More than half of the wineries offer tours, tastings and master classes, providing days of entertainment and palate-pleasing adventures for wine lovers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For even more thrilling experiences, head west to Kangaroo Island, where koalas doze in Eucalyptus trees at Paul&#38;#39;s Place Wildlife Sanctuary and pelicans soar above the beaches. Sailing, hiking, fishing and touring the island&#38;#39;s many conservation areas offer both exhilarating and tranquil adventures.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxuriate in the Journey&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Give yourself the pampering experience you deserve by flying to Adelaide in the peaceful &#60;strong&#62;luxury of first or business class&#60;/strong&#62;. From the minute you enter the airport, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to comforts beyond belief. On your flight, you&#38;#39;ll delight in spacious seats, personal entertainment systems and five-star quality meals.&#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;br /&#62;
    These &#60;strong&#62;first class&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; business class&#60;/strong&#62; luxuries are affordable with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s savings. Whether you need to travel at the last minute, or you are embarking on a multi-city journey, FlyFirst.com can save you up to 70 percent. Call us today to secure your stellar &#60;strong&#62;savings on first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can embark on the adventure of a lifetime to Adelaide.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4540</first_class_price><business_class_price>3780</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>1</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Affordable Business Class Airline Ticket to Adelaide, Cheap First Class Flight to Adelaide, Cheap Flights </description><keywords>Affordable, Cheap, Discounted Airline, Business class cheap, First Class Cheap Airline, Discounted Fares. cheap fares to Adelaide </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f1de9f84774543fe89bf3c23c5237785.jpg</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>Best Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cb31d354c3b14de4a10476fab97f5a35.jpg</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Seats</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>39d63eddd6b348cc98da00221cc4ccd9.jpg</alias><content_id>38</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>39</city_id><country_id>6</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>Chicago </name><title>Cheap First Class Fares &#38; Discounted Business Class Flights to Chicago</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Chicago</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Chicago, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Chicago. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Chicago.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;While some of the nation&#38;#39;s best cuisine is featured in Chicago restaurants, Chicago is also known for a few more casual dishes. Famous Chicago-style hot dogs and pizza are must-haves during a trip to the Windy City, so be sure to ask some locals where their favorite neighborhood hot dog or pizza is served.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Why Fly Business or First Class?&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;An average flight to Chicago from Australia can take about 19 hours, so it &#38;#39;s sensible to make the best use of that flight time working, resting and sleeping in comfortable business class or first class. The luxury pampering starts at the airport with exclusive access to private lounges with refreshments and entertainment. Once on your flight, you are given the white-glove treatment with world class meals, plush seating and luxurious bedding. These services ensure you arrive in Chicago relaxed and all set to enjoy the Windy City.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive Flyfirst Service &#38;amp; Discounted First Class Prices&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We offer cheap business class airfares for any number of travel needs. From last minute business class deals to outstanding business class airfare discounts, Flyfirst&#38;#39;s unmatched fares offer 60 percent discounts on regular airplane ticket prices. Our access to unpublished rates allows us to offer you unheard-of business class flight discounts on your luxury roundtrip, one-way or multi-city itinerary.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Call Us Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With our fantastic services, access to cheap business class seats to the world&#38;#39;s best destinations is convenient. Just give us a call toll-free, and our knowledgeable travel specialists will provide you with a variety of travel options. If you choose, you can also receive a quick, complimentary quote by completing our simple online form. Regardless of which method you prefer, Flyfirst offers tremendous business class airfare discounts for your upcoming journey to Chicago.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>1890</first_class_price><business_class_price>1230</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First Class Cheap Flights , Cheap Business Class Fares, Business Cheap Airline deals</description><keywords>FIRST CLASS FARES AND DISCOUNTED BUSINESS CLASS TO CHICAGO, save money with first class, business class, cheap fares, first class tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7013f5fabc8c422c839f77af3705555b.jpg</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>Downtown Chicago &#38; Lake Michigan</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>f47e22e331f74dd2be33cd58bc105d6a.jpg</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>Chicago Theatre interior</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>8720c011107a49e482d3974c7bb8da7e.jpg</alias><content_id>39</content_id><title>Buckingham fountain in Grant Park</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>40</city_id><country_id>6</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>New York</name><title>CHEAP LAST MINUTE BUSINESS AND FIRST CLASS TICKETS TO NEW YORK </title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-to-NewYork</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to New York, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to New York. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to New York.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Take a Bite Out of the Big Apple&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you are journeying to the metropolis for business or pleasure, there is much to experience in New York City&#38;#39;s five boroughs. Even pleasure travelers enjoy taking a trip to the city&#38;#39;s Wall Street financial district for a sense of the nation&#38;#39;s most important financial center.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Art lovers revel in the city&#38;#39;s many leading art galleries and museums, including the Metropolitan Museum of Art and the Chelsea Art District. World-class performances are concentrated on Broadway, home to the city&#38;#39;s 39 largest theatres, and the city&#38;#39;s famous concert centres, such as Carnegie Hall and Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Landmarks throughout the town tell the tale of New York&#38;#39;s and America&#38;#39;s history. From Ellis Island&#38;#39;s role in accepting U.S. immigrants to One World Trade Center&#38;#39;s memorial to 9/11 victims, the history and development of the U.S. is captured in a variety of New York buildings.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The Pleasures of First and Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Flying to the Big Apple can take nearly a day&#38;#39;s worth of hours, so it&#38;#39;s important to ensure that your flight is as comfortable as possible. Business and first class can add a significant amount of comfort to your travel and assure that you reach your destination relaxed and ready to take on Manhattan. As a first or business class passenger, you are welcomed into choice airport lounges before and between your flights. Lounges often feature delectable cuisine, complimentary beverages, fully equipped business centers, state-of-the-art entertainment, relaxing spa or salon services and assistance from knowledgeable concierge staff. On board your airplane, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to roomy seats that convert to plush beds, meals designed by world-famous chefs, ample beverages, private video monitors with entertainment systems and a variety of other pampering services.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive Flyfirst.com Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Regardless of the purpose or timing of your trip, Flyfirst.com offers unrivaled deals on business and first class to New York. From one-way tickets and multi-city destinations to open-ended return dates and last minute flights, we provide luxury travel discounts of up to 60 percent off regular prices.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Call Us Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Accessing deals on &#60;strong&#62;business and first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; is as easy as picking up the phone or clicking your mouse button. Simply call us toll-free, and one of our experienced travel specialists can assist you immediately with travel options and discounts. If you prefer, you can also fill out our online form, and a Flyfirst.com specialist will contact you with a free price quote. Traveling first class to New York doesn&#38;#39;t have to be a chore if you use FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled services.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>1960</first_class_price><business_class_price>1270</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Last Minuet Cheap Airline Flights, Business class Cheap, First Class fares, Discounted Business Class</description><keywords>LAST MINUTE BUSINESS AND FIRST CLASS TICKETS TO NEW YORK, Cheap, First Class, Business class airfare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>367130c4c5b44ccc8ba94b7106109a02.jpg</alias><content_id>40</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Airfare to New York</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>dd36434c524f4070b1ad0eebf5f9b7bd.jpg</alias><content_id>40</content_id><title>Last Minute Business class Ticket to New York</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>795e2d146059446fa6c5a211f9cc4df5.jpg</alias><content_id>40</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Flight to New York </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>41</city_id><country_id>6</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>San Francisco</name><title>Cheap first class travel and huge savings on business class tickets to San Francisco</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-San-Francisco</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to San Francisco, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to San Francisco. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to San Francisco.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;With our incredibly &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;cheap business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll save up to 60 percent and have plenty of energy and money left over to enjoy the city&#38;#39;s bountiful museums, intriguing attractions and extensive activities.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Business and Pleasure Meld in San Francisco&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;San Francisco is famously a blend of various ethnic and cultural neighborhoods united to create a unique and beloved town. Its robust financial district, most famously marked by the TransAmerica Pyramid building, leads to the exciting Embarcadero, where cruise ports, treasured farmer&#38;#39;s market stalls and ample jogging trails offer hours of amusement.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The North Beach area offers scrumptious Italian fare and the city&#38;#39;s ongoing Beach Blanket Babylonmusical revue featuring famously gargantuan hats. Nearby Chinatown charms with silks, imports, engaging street vendors and delicious food. From the bohemian charm of Haight-Ashubury and the gay activism at the Castro to the design centers South of Market and &#38;quot;painted ladies&#38;quot; Victorian homes on Alamo Square, the many neighborhoods are all celebrated parts of San Francisco.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;For activity and cultural exploration, visit Golden Gate Park&#38;#39;s de Young Museum and California Academy of Sciences, or explore the Presidio&#38;#39;s many parks and walking trails offering spectacular views of the Golden Gate Bridge. From San Francisco&#38;#39;s famous Fisherman&#38;#39;s Wharf and Pier 39, take a cruise out to Alcatraz Island to tour the old prison grounds. Finally, don&#38;#39;t miss riding the city&#38;#39;s iconic cable cars to Nob Hill.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Luxury Business and First Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With flight times of about 15 hours, it&#38;#39;s smart to &#60;strong&#62;travel first class&#60;/strong&#62; to San Francisco. Exclusive airport lounges and upscale, pampering amenities on board the airplane mean you&#38;#39;ll reach your destination with plenty of energy to take on the city&#38;#39;s most vigorous activities.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive Flyfirst Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Flying in &#60;strong&#62;luxurious first and business classes&#60;/strong&#62; can be affordable with our stellar &#60;strong&#62;business class flight deals&#60;/strong&#62;. For sudden or unplanned trips, we offer incredible &#60;strong&#62;discounts on last minute business class airfare&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;cheap last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; to San Francisco. If you have some time to plan your trip, even better. Our &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class airfares&#60;/strong&#62; are unrivaled and extend to a variety of travel needs such as one-way tickets, roundtrip fares, open-ended return dates and multi-city trips. Since we specialize in &#60;strong&#62;discount business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, we have access to a variety of unpublished rates that will save you up to 60 percent off regular airline fares.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Call Us Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We make it easy for you to access the &#60;strong&#62;best business class flight discounts&#60;/strong&#62; available. Simply call us toll-free, and we will begin searching for your &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class airline tickets&#60;/strong&#62; immediately. If you prefer to handle travel arrangements online, just complete our quick online form for a free travel quote. Whichever method you choose, Flyfirst will provide you with the deepest &#60;strong&#62;business class airfare discounts&#60;/strong&#62; available so that you can thoroughly enjoy your affordable luxury trip to San Francisco.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>1980</first_class_price><business_class_price>1230</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>last minute airfare deals, first class fares, last minute class first class to San Francisco. </description><keywords>CHEAP BUSINESS AND FIRST CLASS TO SAN FRANCISCO, last minute, business class, airfares, cheap fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>adb1aeb9d70347acac0ab2fe6d847591.jpg</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7ac4c4ca83a946d0936a8509aad302b6.jpg</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>Discounted Last Minute First Class</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>495a71f7cee6469488938dc1fcd7fa07.jpg</alias><content_id>41</content_id><title>Reduced Business Class Airfare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>42</city_id><country_id>6</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>Houston</name><title>Discounted business &#38; first class last minute deals to Houston</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Houston</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Houston, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Houston. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Houston.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;From a vibrant downtown to the gleaming waters of surrounding Puget Sound and Lake Washington, Houston is a jewel of the Pacific Northwest that just begs to be explored.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry, Innovation and Adventure&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Famously known for its leading technology, aerospace and coffee industries, Houston is home to a lively port, one of the largest Internet retailers in the world and a favorite American warehouse retail chain. Its energetic business community makes it an active business destination served by many FlyFirst &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you are in Houston for business or holiday, there are a number of attractions and activities that are not to be missed. Houston Center&#38;#39;s Space Needle is likely the city&#38;#39;s most famous structure and offers a spectacular 360-degree view of the city from a revolving platform. Head over to the city&#38;#39;s beloved Pike Place Market to watch the fishmongers throw the day&#38;#39;s catch into the selling stalls or just shop among the many market vendors.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;After a busy day working or sightseeing, visit any of the Emerald City&#38;#39;s abundant performing arts centers, music venues and nightclubs. Known as the home of the grunge music movement in the 1990s, Houston&#38;#39;s music scene continues to innovate and develop new and exciting bands.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The region&#38;#39;s Native American roots are evident in many of the downtown street vendors&#38;#39; wares, and the town&#38;#39;s early history is cleverly revealed in the city&#38;#39;s underground tours. Kayak along Puget Sound or head out of the city limits to explore the remaining crater of Mt. Saint Helen&#38;#39;s 1981 volcanic eruption at various visitor&#38;#39;s centers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Flights With Benefits In First And Business Class Cabins&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make the most of your lengthy flight to Houston aboard the spacious&#60;strong&#62; luxury of first class &#60;/strong&#62;or &#60;strong&#62;business class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll be treated to exclusive airport lounges, roomy seating, entertainment, epicurean delights, complimentary beverages and comfortable bedding.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive FlyFirst Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The high-end amenities of first and business class don&#38;#39;t have to be expensive. FlyFirst offers a variety of incredible &#60;strong&#62;business class airfare &#60;/strong&#62;discounts that will save you up to 60 percent off regular fares. We access unpublished rates and partner with a variety of travel companies to offer you &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class airline tickets&#60;/strong&#62; for destinations around the world. If your trip to Houston is sudden, no worries. Our services include deep discounts on &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. If you have a little more time to plan your trip, that&#38;#39;s great too.&#60;strong&#62; Cheap business class airfares&#60;/strong&#62; are available for planned roundtrip, one-way and multi-city travels as well as open-ended return date tickets.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Call Us Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our knowledgeable travel specialists are available to receive your toll-free call and can assist you with the &#60;strong&#62;best business class flight deals&#60;/strong&#62; around. If you prefer, complete our quick online travel form for a free quote on &#60;strong&#62;business class airfare deals&#60;/strong&#62; to Houston. Don&#38;#39;t wait, call us today so you can be heading to beautiful Houston in no time.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>1970</first_class_price><business_class_price>1240</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>FIRST AND BUSINESS CLASS FARES TO HOUSTON, discounted airline tickets cheap, first class airfare, business class cheap </description><keywords>FIRST AND BUSINESS CLASS FARES TO HOUSTON, cheap deals, first class fares, discounted business class tickets </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>899d256008704c16b4b7efcb36a1165c.jpg</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>Business Class Deals </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cd5df953ae894b709cfe69f892d51a5f.jpg</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Flight</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>70756b8c63c04bd5aae76de1a1956842.jpg</alias><content_id>42</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>43</city_id><country_id>0</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Dubai</name><title>The Best Travel Deals for Business Class &#38; Cheap First Class Tickets to Dubai</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Dubai</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Dubai, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Dubai. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Dubai.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Your flight to Dubai can be a luscious experience with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s incredible discounts on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. With discounts of up to 70 percent, FlyFirst.com offers you opulent travel at unparalleled prices.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Delicious, Divine and Deluxe&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Dubai&#38;#39;s economic vigor is evident in its manicured streets and abundant skyscrapers. Everything is over-sized in Dubai, from the tallest building in the world at the Burj Khalifa to the world&#38;#39;s largest artificial islands, The Palm Islands. Home to the only seven-star hotel on earth, Dubai offers plenty of high-end entertainment, lodging and recreation in a pristine, yet lush tropical setting.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Given the city&#38;#39;s tendency for immense proportions, it&#38;#39;s not surprising that Dubai&#38;#39;s shopping malls are some of the largest in the world. An experience in its own right, the Dubai Mall holds more than 1,000 shops, more than 160 eateries, a 22-screen cinema, an ice rink and an aquarium.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you&#38;#39;ve had your fill of modern sites, explore the Arabian Peninsula&#38;#39;s history at the old Burj Nahar watchtower, the Hatta Heritage Village and the Dubai Museum. Jumeirah Mosque is one of the area&#38;#39;s largest mosques, featuring exquisite medieval Fatimid-styled minarets and pristine white dome. The old souks, are ideal marketplaces to experience the traditions and culture of Dubai. Fine fabrics, gold and local wares are great finds at the local souks.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Several theme parks offer thrills galore for Dubai visitors, while the area&#38;#39;s nature reserves provide exciting views of waterbirds such as broad-billed sandpipers and flamingos.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Journey From Start To Finish in Discounted Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make your sojourn to Dubai as sumptuous as the visit itself with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s amazing &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. As a premium passenger, you have an exclusive invitation to some of the most refined airport lounges in the world. Aboard your &#60;strong&#62;luxury airplane cabin&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll be escorted to spacious seats, covered in plush, cushioned leather. Settle into your over-sized seat and prepare to be impressed with five-star quality cuisine, state-of-the-art entertainment options and the ultimate in pampering services. Oftentimes, premium travelers also enjoy expedited security, customs and boarding queues.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We specialize in unearthing the very best deals on premium travel, all while providing stellar personalized service. Whether you have a complicated multi-city itinerary or require an open-ended return ticket, we offer the same outstanding discounts of up to 70 percent. To secure your unmatched savings on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, call us today, and we&#38;#39;ll have you on your way to divine Dubai in no time.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4980</first_class_price><business_class_price>3840</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>FLYFIRST DELIVERS YOU TO DIVINE DUBAI IN DISCOUNTED FIRST CLASS FLIGHTS, last minute business class fares, first class deals, airline tickets cheap</description><keywords>FLYFIRST DELIVERS YOU TO DIVINE DUBAI IN DISCOUNTED FIRST CLASS FLIGHTS, cheap flights, business class tickets, first class airline </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>a301cc710da346a2b52ae9adb039ed7c.jpg</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Travel</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>65c04d495e7644e6a898b6e2f613c998.jpg</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>Affordable First Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>f4df597905d84714b5531f9f03b7ebdf.jpg</alias><content_id>43</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Airfare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>44</city_id><country_id>16</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Madrid</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class to Madrid, Save Thousands on Last Minute Tickets</title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-Cheap-to-Madrid</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Madrid, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Madrid. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Modern, metropolitan Madrid is a welcoming, exciting city brimming with activities, charm and history. Travel to Madrid in the ultimate luxury of &#60;strong&#62;first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled savings. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on luxury airfare, leaving you with thousands of dollars in your travel budget to fully explore Madrid and its enchanting attractions.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Palaces, Tapas and Culture&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The capital of Spain, bustling Madrid is the third largest European Union city and the cultural and political center of the country. The city is headquarters for most Spain-based corporations and home to a vibrant European financial center.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Visitors revel in the city&#38;#39;s rich heritage and history at sites like the Almundena Cathedral, built in 1883 on the grounds of a medieval mosque. The cathedral is a majestic symbol of the city&#38;#39;s Catholic roots, with its gilded statue of Madonna and Child and exquisite Gothic Revival architecture. The immense and impressive Royal Palace of Madrid is a stunning 3,418 rooms, many of them on display during tours. There are countless other architectural wonders in Madrid, including the Plaza de Cibeles, featuring the Palacio de Buenavista, Palacio de Cibeles, the Bank of Spain, the Palacio de Linares and a variety of enticing fountains and appealing statues.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Culture abounds here, with the historic Royal Theater, the Golden Triangle of Art, the Royal Botanical Garden and dozens of other fascinating museums. Visitors seeking a thrilling nightlife don&#38;#39;t have to look far in Madrid. Tapas bars, jazz lounges and flamenco theaters are scattered throughout and offer the perfect culmination to a day spent roaming the magnificent. Some of the city&#38;#39;s favorite nightspots are located in the Puerto de Sol, Tribunal and Bilbao districts.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Savor the Journey&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Making the trip to Madrid in the luxury of sumptuous first class seats and business class fares sets the entire excursion up as a delightful experience from start to finish. As a premium traveler, you are pampered throughout the trip, from exclusive entry to amenity-filled airport lounges and bountiful services to on-board seats that recline and swivel to a variety of positions and five-star cuisine. When you &#60;strong&#62;fly first and business class&#60;/strong&#62;, you arrive in Madrid rested and able to explore all of the city&#38;#39;s abundant delights.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our knowledgeable travel professionals are uniquely skilled at finding the &#60;strong&#62;very best rates&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class fares to Madrid&#60;/strong&#62; on preferred airlines. With savings of up to 70 percent on published airfares, FlyFirst.com is an industry leader in finding and offering &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62; at the &#60;strong&#62;best prices&#60;/strong&#62; around. With these incredible &#60;strong&#62;deals on business class fares and first class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy unrivaled comfort and savings to the exciting city of Madrid.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3670</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Madrid Cheap Business Class, Last Minute First Class, Cheap Discounted Fare Business, Best Deals Flights</description><keywords>Madrid Last Minute First Class, Cheap Madrid Business Class, Discounted Business Class Fares, Cheap Flights</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ec4f0dfd65d34a2ca3af7a03c12e435a.jpg</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Madrid</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>daede24d69de42a3a4ac29bda0d4304a.jpg</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>First Class Flight to Madrid</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>3473072b302b47a0a00b7a9b3129c1ab.jpg</alias><content_id>44</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>45</city_id><country_id>21</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>Johannesburg</name><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights to Johannesburg, Discounted First Class Tickets </title><alias>First-Class-Business-Deals-to-Johannesburg</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Johannesburg, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Johannesburg. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Johannesburg. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Affluent, successful and modern, Johannesburg is an engaging, welcoming city with plenty of commerce, activities and attractions to delight all visitors. Trek to appealing Johannesburg in affordable luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply&#60;strong&#62; reduced first class tickets and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. With premium travel, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy sumptuous comfort and service at FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s legendary savings.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Skyscrapers, History and Safaris&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;T&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;his modern city is home to a number of international corporations and financial empires, evident in its many towering buildings. Sentech Tower, Carlton Centre and Hillbrow Tower are just a few of the city&#38;#39;s imposing buildings offering stunning views of the metropolis.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;In spite of its gleaming modern style, Johannesburg offers much more than just towering skyscrapers. Visitors revel in wandering through the Johannesburg Botanical Garden or spending a day enjoying thrill rides, underground mine tours and tribal dancing performances at Gold Reef City.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The city&#38;#39;s rich and complicated history is wonderfully explored at the Apartheid Museum, Harry Pieterson Museum, Constitution Hill and the Mandela Museum. The region&#38;#39;s role in the development of man is displayed just outside of town at The Cradle of Humankind. The site of the Sterkfontein fossil and the richest hominid discoveries in the world, the Cradle of Humankind is a World Heritage Site.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Johannesburg teems with more modern cultural exploits, as well, including lively shopping and art scenes. Visitors delight in the high-end shops at Sandton City and Nelson Mandela Square and the local crafts at the Rosebank Flea Market. Several art museums and performing arts venues call Johannesburg home, including Johannesburg Art Museum and Market Theater.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Located in Africa&#38;#39;s highveld, Johannesburg teems with captivating wildlife. More than 80 lions, including rare white lions, can be seen at the Lion Park near Lanseria Airport. Visitors also enjoy the safari adventures at Krugersdorp Nature Reserve, about 45 minutes from Johannesburg.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Jaunt to Johannesburg in Luxury Business &#38;amp; First Class Cabin&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your African adventures with a world-class travel experience with &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com. From the minute you reach the airport, your every need will be met at choice airport lounges reserved for premium travelers. Here, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy fine dining, refreshing spa services, fully equipped &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; centers and a host of comfortable lounges to rest and relax. On board your flight, the pampering continues with spacious, comfortable seating and exquisite services and amenities.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com is an industry leader in providing the very &#60;strong&#62;best deals available&#60;/strong&#62; on premium travel. Our skilled travel professionals are knowledgeable in all aspects of luxury flights and can offer you the information and options you need to make your trip to Johannesburg productive and fulfilling. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll save thousands of dollars on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares and first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; so that you spend your time and budget on exploring appealing Johannesburg.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4780</first_class_price><business_class_price>3890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap Business Flight to Johannesburg, First Class Deals, Discounted Last Minute Fare to Johannesburg </description><keywords>Cheap First Class, Last Minute To Johannesburg, Cheap Business Class Deals, Discounted First Class Fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>329edea5998142049b190b84242d005c.jpg</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>First Class Tickets to Johannesburg </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>89d05fd673444a6e90a9a97b1810ec58.jpg</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Tickets </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a8d493a87c954f938b7046ee29fd42ee.jpg</alias><content_id>45</content_id><title>Business Class Deals </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>46</city_id><country_id>21</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>Cape Town</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights To Cape Town, Cheap Last Minute Flights.</title><alias>Cheap-First-Business-Class-Flight-to-Cape-Town</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Africa, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Cape Town. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Cape Town. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;World-class beaches, spectacular hiking and alluring shopping await in Cape Town, South Africa. Fly in affordable comfort with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;business class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and reduced last minute flights. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent and receive all of the full price luxuries of premium travel so that you have more time, energy and money to expend in beautiful Cape Town.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Waterfront Wonders, Brilliant Seascapes and Dramatic Cliffs&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Known for its dramatic sea cliffs, majestic Table Mountain and a vibrant harbor, bi-coastal Cape Town has plenty of magnificent sights and activities. Befitting the most popular tourist destination in Africa, Cape Town overflows with attractions, including the Victoria &#38;amp; Albert Waterfront. The waterfront showcases hundreds of shops, the Two Oceans Aquarium and the Nelson Mandela Gateway. Visitors delight in riding the ferries out to Simon&#38;#39;s Town, Robben Island and Hout Bay and touring Kirstenbosch National Botanical Garden.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Beaches of every variety surround Cape Town, from the wide, sandy beaches of the eastern False Bay to the popular surfing beaches along the West Coast. With spectacular sunset views on the Atlantic Coast beaches, Cape Town offers views that rival all others. Visitors especially relish the views to be found along the cliffside Chapman&#38;#39;s Peak Drive between Hout Bay and Noordhoek.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Fascinating Table Mountain, with its richly diverse vegetation, offers plenty of recreation and excitement. Visitors can reach the peak by hiking up the mountain or riding the Table Mountain Cableway. From the upper cableway, tourists enjoy amazing views of the city, the mountain and Robben Island.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make the Most of Your Journey to Cape Town in Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Fly to gorgeous Cape Town in the consummate &#60;strong&#62;luxury of first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; or the spacious comfort of &#60;strong&#62;business class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. From the moment you enter the airport, you&#38;#39;ll be pampered with unrivaled service, including exclusive access to deluxe lounges overflowing with delightful cuisine, cocktails, spa and salon services and fully equipped business centers. Aboard your flight, premium cabins offer supple, roomy seats; meals designed by famous chefs; personal entertainment systems and unmatched service. With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;first class and last minute business class deals&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Cape Town relaxed and able to embark on your adventures.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our skilled travel professionals are knowledgeable in all aspects of premium travel to South Africa, including the airlines and airports that offer the best amenities and most-lauded services. With this experience, FlyFirst travel agents can guide you to the travel options that best fit your particular needs and save you thousands of dollars on &#60;strong&#62;luxury flights&#60;/strong&#62;. With FlyFirst.com &#60;strong&#62;business class deals and first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, your adventure to Cape Town is sure to be a delightful excursion with memories to last a lifetime.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4870</first_class_price><business_class_price>3840</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>First Class Tickets Cheap, Best Deals Business Class To Cape Town </description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets to Cape Town, Cheap Last Minute Business Class, First Class Discounted </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>185e6033592c46b19a595249a125c87e.jpg</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>99561f29ac824f15a88f85e49a32df9b.jpg</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>Best Business Class Deals </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>1d786bef4775446087e0678304c9c8f4.jpg</alias><content_id>46</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fare </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>47</city_id><country_id>30</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Cairo</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class to Cairo, Save Thousands on Last Minute Tickets</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Tickets-to-Cairo</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Cairo, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Cairo. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Cairo. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Adventure and wonder await in the magnificent city of Cairo. Journey to the City of a Thousand Minarets in affordable luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar &#60;strong&#62;first class deals and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent off published fares and enjoy untold luxuries on your way to the desert gem of Cairo.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Pharaohs, Bazaars and Minarets&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;From age-old civilizations to gleaming modern skyscrapers, Cairo is at once both ancient and modern. Set along the life-giving Nile River, Cairo is near many of the compelling ancient pyramids of Giza, the city of Memphis, the iconic Sphinx and the Saqqara Pyramid Complex featuring Imhotep&#38;#39;s step pyramid. Travelers can experience the lifestyle, ingenuity and craftsmanship of ancient peoples at the nearby living history site, Pharaonic Village.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Stunning architecture and religious history are displayed in the city&#38;#39;s many notable mosques. At the center of town, perched on Muqattam Hill in Cairo&#38;#39;s historic Citadel fortress, the Mosque of Muhammad Ali overlooks the ancient city. Many of the city&#38;#39;s mosques are gorgeous examples of 10th and 11th century Islamic architecture, including Al-Hakim Mosque Jame-al-Anwar, Al Azhar and Lulua mosques. All built between 928 and 1015, these mosques showcase marble courtyards, towering minarets and keel-shaped arches.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The city richly offers more modern sites as well, from its &#38;quot;Paris on the Nile&#38;quot; architecture in downtown to its celebrated Tahrir (Liberation) Square. Famed Museum of Egyptian Antiquities encourages visitors to marvel at countless ancient artifacts and mummies, including those found with King Tutankhamun and the most recently discover Hatshepsut.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For a true taste of the city&#38;#39;s lifestyle, board a local felucca (boat) for a sunset cruise of the Nile or shop in the diverse and vibrant ancient bazaar, Khan el-Khalili. Wander through the narrow, winding streets of Old Cairo to browse through the Coptic Museum and Babylon Fortress or admire the architecture and reverence of Egypt&#38;#39;s first mosque, Amr ibn al-&#38;#39;As Mosque. Sip coffee at a sidewalk cafe, puff on a sheesha water pipe or savor the Middle Eastern flavors of kushari rice dishes and fatir pastries at street vendors and local restaurants.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Relish the Trip of a Lifetime in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your journey to Cairo with the splendor and luxury of &#60;strong&#62;first class seats or business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, courtesy of FlyFirst&#38;#39;s deeply&#60;strong&#62; discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll be pampered from the moment you arrive at your departure airport, leaving you with plenty of energy and budget to explore Cairo to its fullest.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The travel professionals at FlyFirst offer unparalleled service and some of the &#60;strong&#62;best discounts on luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62; available. With all that you will save on our first class deals and &#60;strong&#62;reduced business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, your excursion to Cairo will be memorable from start to finish.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4480</first_class_price><business_class_price>3570</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap Business To Cairo, Last Minute First Class Cheap, Discounted First Class Fares, Cheap Flights Last Minute Business  </description><keywords>Cheap First Class Tickets, Discounted Business Class Tickets, Last Minute Cheap </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>35c2270ac6d347aba1aada6c1ae658d0.jpg</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>Cheap First Class to Egypt </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>fc807080353a4d748f8a3c43df841ef1.jpg</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class To Egypt</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>1d091917141848e2a598c87dc722e9a7.jpg</alias><content_id>47</content_id><title>Cheap Deals Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>48</city_id><country_id>18</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Venice</name><title>Cheap Deals On Business &#38; First Class Tickets To Venice, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save Thousands</title><alias>Business-First-Class-Deals-to-Venice</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Venice. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Venice. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Mystery, romance and artistry seamlessly blend together in the stunningly beautiful city of Venice. Voyage to The Floating City in consummate luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar discounts on premium &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy pampering travel at &#60;strong&#62;affordable prices&#60;/strong&#62;, perfectly fitting for a journey to the Most Serene Republic of Venice.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Vaporetti, Venetian Masks and Virtuosos&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Situated on the northeastern coast of Italy in the Venetian Lagoon, Venice is filled with canals winding through its ancient streets. Its Gothic buildings, romantic bridges and absence of cars create a city that seems untouched by modern times. It is Venice&#38;#39;s charming ambiance, overflowing with history and artistry, that draws more than 50,000 tourists a day. Venice is so steeped in history, in fact, that the entire city is a World Heritage Site.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A journey to Venice is an unforgettable adventure. Relish a sunset ride in the city&#38;#39;s vaporetti water buses or gondolas, see Casanova&#38;#39;s jail at the Doge&#38;#39;s Palace or watch a master glass blower create a stunning art piece. Tour Piazza San Marco&#38;#39;s basilica and Campanile, the gilded La Fenice opera house and the famed Rialto Bridge to experience the city&#38;#39;s acclaimed history. Savor spectacular views of the Grand Canal while browsing through the Rialto market or boat to the picturesque island of San Giorgio Maggiore. Enjoy elaborate costumes, local mask artistry and a surreal sense of theater during the city&#38;#39;s famed Carnival, or relax with the glitterati on the luxurious beaches of nearby Lido di Venezia.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Aside from its fine Venetian and Murano glass blowers and magnificent mask makers, Venice has been home to countless artists, leaders and power-brokers throughout its 1,500-year history. As you roam Venice&#38;#39;s enchanting streets, you walk in the footsteps of some of Western civilization&#38;#39;s most important figures, from Marco Polo and Sebastian Cabot to Titian and Antonio Vivaldi.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Create an Unforgettable Journey to Venice&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With Venice&#38;#39;s bountiful experiences, you&#38;#39;ll want to arrive rested and ready to explore. Sumptuous &#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; envelop you in the lap of luxury and deliver you to one of Europe&#38;#39;s most romantic cities. As a &#60;strong&#62;luxury traveler&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to a host of pampering services and amenities, from exclusive airport lounges and chauffeur services to spacious on-board seating, fine dining and free-flowing champagne.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Service&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s experienced travel professionals are intimately versed in the airlines and airports that serve Venice and Europe, providing you with the attention and knowledge you need to make this a remarkable trip. FlyFirst.com travel professionals save you up to 70 percent on the &#60;strong&#62;best business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class fares to Venice&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can revel in all of the city&#38;#39;s many pleasures.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3570</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap First Class Deals, Last Minute Business to Venice , Best Deals Business Cheap, First class Fares, Cheap Business Fares</description><keywords>Cheap First Class Deals, Last Minute Business to Venice , Best Deals Business Cheap, First class Fares, Cheap Business Fares</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7299943ecce94054ae13210eefb9035c.jpg</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title>Cheap First Class to Venice </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>7479437118c64a2487b269009559a869.jpg</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>8241d29ebbf94526ad56b3fa80d57e82.jpg</alias><content_id>48</content_id><title>First Class Fares to Venice</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>49</city_id><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Melbourne </name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class to Melbourne, Save Thousands on Last Minute Tickets</title><alias>Business-Class-Deals-First-Class-to-Melbourne</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Melbourne, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Melbourne. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Melbourne. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Jet away to the brilliant sights, sounds and experiences of Australia&#38;#39;s jewel, marvelous Melbourne. Enjoy tremendous savings on deluxe &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights to Melbourne&#60;/strong&#62; with FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on published luxury airfare so that you have more time and energy to spend in the beautiful Australian city.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Gold, Gardens, Gables and Grapes&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Melbourne is a study of contrasts. Here, enchanting Victorian buildings are shadowed by towering modern skyscrapers and high-rises and well-planned grid-like streets hide small, winding &#38;quot;laneways&#38;quot; filled with funky boutiques. Although the city honors its role in the 1850s Gold Rush, it is a cosmopolitan wonder as the country&#38;#39;s biotechnology and automotive center.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Known as Australian&#38;#39;s garden city, Melbourne overflows with parks, formal gardens and landscaped spaces. Visitors relish the green space, fountains, statues and trees filling Fitzroy Garden and the tropical glasshouse, aboriginal heritage walks and the Melbourne Observatory at the Royal Botanic Garden.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Tourists delight in the city&#38;#39;s numerous Victorian buildings. From Parliament House and the State Library to Melbourne Town Hall and St. Patrick&#38;#39;s Cathedral, the buildings are fascinating glimpses into Australian life in the mid-19th century. The Royal Exhibition Building is a local favorite, constructed for the world&#38;#39;s fare in 1880 and a now a UNESCO World Heritage Site.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Modern buildings offer even more engaging experiences, from the vibrant, immense Australian rules football stadiums to the deconstructionist buildings in bustling Federation Square. While at the Square, take in a film at the uniquely constructed Australian Centre for the Moving Image or marvel at the Square&#38;#39;s unusual shard walls.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Shopping is popular in Melbourne. One-of-a-kind boutiques, charming cafes, appealing restaurants and glimmering galleries line the city&#38;#39;s treasured &#38;quot;laneways&#38;quot; hidden behind the city&#38;#39;s regular streets and offer hours of shopping and dining pleasure.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Enticing beaches surround the eastern coastline near Melbourne, particularly the picturesque St. Kilda, just about three miles from the city. Surfers can find bomboras (big waves) about 50 miles southeast of Melbourne at Rye, Portsea and Sorrento.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;After taking in the city&#38;#39;s countless charms, many tourists revel in a day trip to the east, where the Yarra Valley offers gorgeous vineyards and dozens of wineries offering tastings and tours.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Sophisticated Destinations Deserve Sophisticated Journeys&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Travel in the sumptuous luxury of reduced &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and last minute flights with FlyFirst.com. For a fraction of the regular cost, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy full-price luxuries, including access to exclusive airport lounges, fine dining, free-flowing cocktails and champagne, spacious seating and all of the amenities and services you can imagine.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Save your travel budget for enjoying Melbourne&#38;#39;s bountiful experiences. With FlyFirst.com, you&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on choice &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;, &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can arrive in Melbourne rested and ready to explore.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4890</first_class_price><business_class_price>3940</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Cheap First Class Airline Tickets, Last Minute Business,First Class to Melbourne, Discounted Flights in Business</description><keywords>Cheap Business , First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class to Melbourne, Best Deals Business Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>3598cdb0563c4eb2847728c4030afb9b.jpg</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Melbourne </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>b6f8091c3f5d4232ab6f8890f06bbe03.jpg</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Flights</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>2764c972e4a94e3e81ee0c529e5c576b.jpg</alias><content_id>49</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>50</city_id><country_id>18</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Milan</name><title>Last Minute Business Class Flights to Milan, Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands.</title><alias>Business-First-Deals-Discount-to-Milan</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Milan, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Milan. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Milan. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Explore majestic cathedrals, marvel at famous works of art and experience the haute couture of Fashion Week in the trend-setting city of Milan. Your journey to Milan brims with luxurious amenities with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s outstanding savings on&#60;strong&#62; last minute first class deals and business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll spend up to 70 percent less on your premium airfare, yet enjoy all of the full-price charms of first and business class flights. With FlyFirst.com deals and service, you can spend more of your time, energy and money on enjoying your journey to enchanting Milan.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Milan: A Cultural Mecca For the Centuries&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Italy&#38;#39;s finance, commerce, fashion and interior design industries are centered in Milan. Home to the Italian stock exchange, most of the country&#38;#39;s major banks and the world&#38;#39;s leading fashion designers, the city&#38;#39;s newest gems are the gleaming skyscrapers and cultural centers in the dazzling Porta Nuova Business District. Whether you travel to Milan for business or pleasure, this revitalized district offers plenty of attraction.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In addition to a vibrant business sector, Milan is a mecca for travelers interested in history, architecture and art. More than two million visitors each year explore the city&#38;#39;s treasures, from Leonardo da Vinci&#38;#39;s The Last Supper at Santa Maria delle Grazie to Botticelli&#38;#39;s Madonna of the Pavilion. Grand buildings in Piazzo del Duomo span the centuries. There, the Duomo&#38;#39;s 135 Gothic spires rise above the city and face the breathtaking facades of the Royal Palace, Arengario Palace, and Galleria Vittorio Emanuele II, the world&#38;#39;s oldest shopping mall. Impressive Sforza Castle museums, the historic Arch of Peace and the famed La Scala opera house all offer their own particular delights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;A fashion paradise, Milan is the headquarters for a number of celebrated design houses, including Armani, Dolce &#38;amp; Gabbana, Versace, Valentino, Prada and Gucci. High-end fashion houses and boutiques can be found along such streets as Via della Spiga, Via Manzoni and Via Monte Napoleone.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Fly Fashionably to Chic Milan in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Journey to glamorous Milan in the consummate style of &#60;strong&#62;first and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Premium travelers enjoy amenities at exclusive airport lounges, including abundant refreshments, cocktails, spa services, shower suites, &#60;strong&#62;business&#60;/strong&#62; services and relaxing seating areas. With your FlyFirst first class deals, your in-flight experience includes such treats as extra-large seats that convert to completely flat beds, personal entertainment systems and delectable cuisine. Your first and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats &#60;/strong&#62;offer all the comfort you deserve, delivering you to Milan in the lap of &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;FlyFirst.com travel professionals are uniquely qualified to provide you with unrivaled savings on premium travel. Whether you choose &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; or require &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com is your affordable, luxury ticket to Milan.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3780</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discount Business Class Fare to Milan, Last Minute Cheap Flights business</description><keywords>Cheap Business Class to Milan, Last Minute Business Class Cheap, First Class Flights to Milan, Last Minute First Class Fare Discount </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f90208f50b924ccbba9b1b4ad50d5bd5.jpg</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>0b897792b61e4e3787cd2735ac0952d4.jpg</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Tickets </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>5d308a8e247d40e2b3629bac8c55b17b.jpg</alias><content_id>50</content_id><title>First Class Airline Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>51</city_id><country_id>11</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Taipei</name><title>Best Business Class Deals &#38; Cheap Last Minute First Class Travel To Taipei </title><alias>Last-Minute-Business-Class-Deals-to-Taipei</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Taipei, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel in the lap of luxury to vibrant Taipei without breaking the bank. Book your posh &#60;strong&#62;first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; with FlyFirst.com, and save up to 70 percent on published fares. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy high-end services and amenities at a fraction of the cost.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Towers, Temples and More&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Historic and modern, Taipei offers plenty of attractions for visitors of every age. Modern Taipei brims with skyscrapers, industry and fast-paced entertainment. The second tallest building in the world, Taipei 101, offers dazzling views of the city on its 89th floor and 91st floor observation decks. From there, head to the surrounding Xinyi District for abundant shopping and entertainment. Stores, nightclubs, restaurants and performances fill the district and make it popular day and night.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Find more traditional nightlife at any of Taipei&#38;#39;s many iconic night markets. Perennial favorite Shilin Night Market overflows with food stalls, regional wares and plenty of local flavor. In the daytime, explore the area&#38;#39;s culture at the dozens of notable museums, such as the National Palace Museum. There, you&#38;#39;ll view one of the world&#38;#39;s largest displays of ancient Chinese artifacts, including jades, ceramics and paintings.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Walk in the footsteps of world leaders at the Grand Hotel, one of the largest classical Chinese buildings in the world. The hotel hosted U.S. presidents, British prime ministers, Middle Eastern kings and other world leaders. Philippine leader Benigno Aquino stayed at the Grand Hotel the night before his assassination.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;History and the arts combine at Liberty Square, with the Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Hall, the National Theater and the National Concert Hall. Liberty Square was the site of several pro-democratic rallies in the 1980s and early 1990s credited for hastening democratic rule in the country.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Relish the varied religious history of the area at various temples in the region, ranging from Buddhist and Chinese folk to Taoist faiths. Travel the &#38;quot;Road to Heaven,&#38;quot; Xinsheng South Road, to view some of Taipei&#38;#39;s notable temples and churches, or visit the ornately decorated Mengjia Longshan Temple.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel In Consummate Luxury in First Class Cabin&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Enjoy a serene flight to distant Taipei in the ultimate comfort of business class or first class seats. With premium flights, you&#38;#39;re pampering begins at the airport. Countless services and amenities are available at exclusive airport lounges, offering lavish refreshments and relaxation. In the air, you enjoy untold luxuries and choice services to make your journey endlessly satisfying.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Service and luxury are never compromised at FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll receive the same standard of attention as all other premium travelers, but you&#38;#39;ll pay thousands less for your &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class tickets and first class seats to Taipei&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4640</first_class_price><business_class_price>3470</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Business Class Airline Tickets, Last Minute First Class Fares, Cheap Business Class Flights , Last Minuet First Class Tickets </description><keywords>cheap first class fare, last minute business class airline, first class discounts </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e642e34eba6d403cbd3efeea229964ec.jpg</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Airline Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9b2dc67d0a174f4b8d1036eab998ed94.jpg</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>17909b4ef90b4e3dbeb53ce58222a5dc.jpg</alias><content_id>51</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Fare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>56</city_id><country_id>19</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Dusseldorf</name><title>Best Deals Business Class to Dusseldorf, Last Minute Cheap First Class to Germany. </title><alias>Discount-Deals-Business-Class-to-Dusseldorf</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Dusseldorf, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Dusseldorf. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel in lavish comfort to the picturesque city of D&#38;uuml;sseldorf with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s amazing deals on &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and last minute first class fares. You&#38;#39;ll save thousands of dollars on premium airfare, leaving you with more to spend on exploring the city with the &#38;quot;longest bar in the world.&#38;quot;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Old Town Charm With A Modern Twist&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Set on the Rhine River, D&#38;uuml;sseldorf&#38;#39;s Alstadt district looks as if it was conjured straight from a fairytale book. Quaint cobblestone streets wind through old buildings adorned with colorful flower boxes and trailing ivy. Old-fashioned wrought iron street lamps illuminate the lanes and sidewalk cafes. Here, visitors soak in the Old World ambiance of medieval St. Lambertus Church; the Renaissance town hall, Rathaus; and the old castle tower&#38;#39;s shipping museum. D&#38;uuml;sseldorf&#38;#39;s famed crisp Altbier is served at four of Alstadt&#38;#39;s pubs, brewed on-site in the traditional way. A welcoming river promenade trails alongside the Rhine, perfect for strolling, jogging and skating. Just across from the peaceful promenade, the modern world flavors D&#38;uuml;sseldorf&#38;#39;s &#38;quot;longest bar in the world,&#38;quot; a series of more than 300 lively discos and bars.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Alstadt isn&#38;#39;t the only historic district in town. The Kaiserswerth area holds the ruins of Castle Barbarossa and Florence Nightingale&#38;#39;s old work site, the Deaconess&#38;#39; Institute of Kaiserswerth. Visitors delight in the rococo ornamentation of 18th century Schloss Benrath, the grand dome of the Tonhalle Concert Hall and the city&#38;#39;s plentiful museums and theaters.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    For more modern experiences, visitors head to the Rhine Tower, Rheinturm, where a revolving restaurant and observation deck offer spectacular views. A lighted clock sculpture rests atop the tower, creating the world&#38;#39;s largest digital clock. Shoppers enjoy the countless high-end jewelry and designer apparel shops in the K&#38;ouml;nigsallee/King&#38;#39;s Avenue area. Botanical gardens, bountiful parks, a bustling harbor and the ever-present Rhine River provide ample opportunities for visitors and locals to enjoy the cool climate and verdant landscape that is quintessentially D&#38;uuml;sseldorf.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Create A Fairytale Trip to D&#38;uuml;sseldorf&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Begin your journey to one of Germany&#38;#39;s most beautiful cities in the magical splendor of first class seats and business class cabins. The deluxe service begins with elaborately designed and amenity-filled airport lounges, offering the ultimate in relaxation and refreshment for travelers. In the air, first and business class passengers are treated to delectable meals, abundant beverages, spacious seating, choice bedding and a host of other services to ensure a fairytale flight.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The opulent services of luxury travel are even more enjoyable with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s incredible discounts. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; to D&#38;uuml;sseldorf so that you can indulge in a fairytale trip from start to finish.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3670</first_class_price><business_class_price>2840</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Discounted Business Class to Germany,First Class Tickets, Cheap Last Minute Flights, Cheap Tickets  </description><keywords>Best Deals Business Class Cheap, Last Minute First Class Cheap Fares, Cheap First Class Tickets, Last Minute Business Class </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b3bba6d38bc740ec87a93f0e8552ee87.jpg</alias><content_id>56</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>542d8b49c4ca43a9b9d594aa227264de.jpg</alias><content_id>56</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c84d188d97cc4cbcbc9d7edd1e0bf0b5.jpg</alias><content_id>56</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><city_id>57</city_id><country_id>0</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Copenhagen</name><title>Cheap Business Flights &#38; First Class Tickets To Copenhagen, Fly with FlyFirst &#38; Save up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Deals-to-Copenhagen</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Copenhagen, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets. Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Copenhagen. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Escape to the colorfully charming &#38;quot;City of Spires&#38;quot; in the affordable luxury of reduced-fare &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com. With savings of up to 70 percent, FlyFirst.com helps you fly to beautiful Copenhagen in relaxing splendor without stretching your travel budget. Best of all, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Copenhagen rested and relaxed after a flight that offers all the services and amenities you deserve.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;A Delight For the Senses&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Known for its environmentally conscious practices, Copenhagen is one of the most bicycle-friendly cities in the world. For a true sense of the city, hop on a bike and join the hundreds of other locals cruising past Cophenhagen&#38;#39;s colorful buildings, canals and parks. Whether you are in town for business or pleasure, a cycle through town is an unforgettable experience&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Copenhagen offers bountiful business opportunities, particularly in the biotechnology and life sciences industries. The city is home to more than 300 &#38;quot;cleantech&#38;quot; companies and is headquarters for two of the world&#38;#39;s top 50 biotechnology firms. Shipping, service-oriented companies and countless multinational corporations base regional and international operations in Copenhagen, making it a top destination for professionals.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;The beautiful city offers many historical attractions, including the Marble Church, the iconic Little Mermaid statue and Christiansborg Palace. Marvel at the rococo details of Amalienborg Palace. Relish the vibrantly colored Danish homes of 17th century Nyhavn, the city&#38;#39;s waterfront and entertainment district. Tour some of the churches and spires that give the city its nickname, particularly the famed corkscrew spire at the Church of Our Savior. Wander through the city&#38;#39;s oldest park at King&#38;#39;s Garden and Rosenborg Castle, or mingle with other visitors and locals in Amagertorv square.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Even Copenhagen&#38;#39;s amusement parks are historic. The oldest working amusement park in the world, Dyrehavsbakken pleasure park was created in 1583 and is now home to many rides, restaurants and games. Popular Tivoli Gardens is the second oldest amusement park in the world and offers plenty of thrill rides for the entire family.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;After a day of meetings or city tours, check out Copenhagen&#38;#39;s oft-lauded New Nordic cuisine, rousing nightclubs, abundant microbreweries or its treasured pastry shops.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.2em;&#34;&#62;Make The Journey In First Class Cabin&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst&#38;#39;s unbeatable discounts on &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; make it possible to trek to Copenhagen in ultimate style and luxury. As premium travelers, you&#38;#39;ll have access to reserved airport lounges and their sumptuous services, exquisite in-flight luxuries and spacious, private seats.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;You don&#38;#39;t have to exceed your travel budget to afford premium flights to Copenhagen. FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s skilled travel professionals can save you thousands of dollars on &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can arrive in Copenhagen with energy and money to spare.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3780</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><is_first_class_price_top>0</is_first_class_price_top><is_business_class_price_top>0</is_business_class_price_top><seo><description>Best Discounted Deals Business Class Flight, Last Minute First Class Airline Tickets, Discounted Fares First Class</description><keywords>Cheap First Class,Last Minute Business Fare, Cheap Tickets, Business Class Cheap </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0079e2b1f30b4c2ba4f532ff2f4e741c.jpg</alias><content_id>57</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>1ebb2135c28047378c3f3c238d94a2d2.jpg</alias><content_id>57</content_id><title>First Class Business Class Deals</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>6881208f4a0a4eaebcec4105c5ee6a85.jpg</alias><content_id>57</content_id><title>Last MInute Business Class Airline Tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>