<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Europe</name><title>Cheap Business Class Flights To Europe, Discounted First Class Fares to Europe</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Europe</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Europe, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Europe. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Europe.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Your European adventure awaits, offering warm Mediterranean beaches, thrilling mountain getaways, fascinating prehistoric wonders and sophisticated cultural pursuits. These exciting escapes are affordable when you travel to Europe with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar savings on first class fares and business class tickets. With discounts of up to 70 percent off published rates, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty left over to spend on your European exploits.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Monoliths, Medieval Castles and Menus&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you are traveling to Europe for business or pleasure, the region brims with appealing activities and attractions. From cave paintings at Spain&#38;#39;s Altamira Cave and France&#38;#39;s Lascaux to mysterious monoliths at Stonehenge in England and Carnac in France, Europe is a great place to explore the works of early man. For more recent historical marvels, tour the impressive Alhambra in Spain, Edinburgh Castle in Scotland, the picturesque windmills in Amsterdam and the Colosseum in Rome. Cruise along the Rhine River to see amazing medieval castles and fortresses in &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class ticket&#60;/strong&#62;, or wind your way through the historic canals of Venice to take a step back in time.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Although the region has vast historic attractions, there are plenty of contemporary adventures available. Shop some of the world&#38;#39;s best boutiques in Paris, London and Milan or peruse art and architecture in Bacelona, Paris and Belgium. Wander through breathtaking museums in Switzerland, Italy and France, or ascend to some of the tallest skyscrapers in the area for breathtaking views of celebrated cities.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Above all, make time to sample Europe&#38;#39;s treasured regional flavors, including paella in Spain, chocolates in Switzerland and Belgium, complex cuisine and simple pastries in France and fresh seafood and wine in Italy.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Passage to Europe on&#38;#160;Cheap&#38;#160;Business or First Class Flight&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;With all of these awe-inspiring experiences available, why not make your journey to Europe just as pleasurable? Flying in the comfort and style of first class fares and business class seats can be part of the complete experience with stellar discounts from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy exclusive, inviting airport lounges and expedited airport queues. On your flight, you&#38;#39;ll settle into plush, over-sized seats and dine on high-end cuisine. Your gracious flight attendant offers free-flowing champagne, bed turn-down service and deluxe amenity bags to make your flight peaceful and pleasant.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Our expert travel professionals are skilled at scoping out the very best deals available on premium flights to Europe. These tremendous savings are available on all types of flights to Europe, including multi-city trips, one-way excursions, &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; and open-ended return tickets. Regardless of your travel needs, FlyFirst.com is committed to finding the deepest savings to make your European adventure affordable and luxurious. Call us today to find out how much you can save on &#60;strong&#62;first class fares and&#60;/strong&#62; &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets to Europe&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>3890</first_class_price><business_class_price>2680</business_class_price><seo><description>Last Minute First Class Ticket Cheap to Asia, First Class Flight to Frankfurt, Business cheap first class seats, business class airfare to Asia, Cheap last minute fare, Cheap Tickets and Discounted Fares</description><keywords>Enjoy Europe with FlyFirst.com's Deals on First Class Fares, Cheap Business Class , Cheap First Class, First Class, Business Airfare, Last Minute First Class, Last minute business class airfare, business class airline,</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cd56383f3d0d4507a285cae0f6530de7.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>Chap Business Class, Last Minute First Class Fares</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9090909710e34bd0b07cac4b9f2969f9.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Fares </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>50e9c464417d4650b29d2c16a60921a3.jpg</alias><content_id>1</content_id><title>First Class Last Minute Flights to Europe</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Asia</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Asia, Last Minute Business Class to Asia, Save Thousands on Your Business Class.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Asia</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Asia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Deeply spiritual and historical, modern and worldly, Asia is a continent of intriguing contrasts and exciting destinations. Travel in luxury to the mystical and thrilling Asia with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s stellar deals on first class seats and business class seats. FlyFirst.com will save you as much as 70 percent on premium travel so that you can spend more time and money on exploring the mysteries of the Orient.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Adventure and save on Business Class to Asia&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Whether you are traveling to Asia for business or making the trek of a lifetime, the bountiful beauty of Asia is unbeatable. From the gorgeous beaches of Thailand to the glorious peaks of the Himalayas, Asia&#38;#39;s natural landmarks are both breathtaking and awe-inspiring. These natural wonders are also full of exciting adventures.Save thousands on &#60;strong&#62;Business and First Class&#60;/strong&#62;.Ride elephants along the beach in Phuket, Thailand; chug up the mountainside on the historic Darjeeling Himalayan Railway or snorkel and scuba dive along the coral reefs of the Philippines&#38;#39; Camarine Sur.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    History and spirituality blend here to create an enchanting land full of ancient temples and imposing palaces. Buddhism, Hinduism, Muslim, Sikhism and dozens of other religious faiths were born in Asia, creating a wealth of richly intricate religious center. In South Korea, marvel at the early Golchange megalithic dolmens and Mount Toham&#38;#39;s Bulgaska temple; in Vietnam, revel in the ornate decor of the Cao Dai temples in Da Lat, My Tho and Tay Ninh; in Thailand, glory in the gold-plated 150-foot Buddha at the ancient Wat Pho Temple and in China, visit one of the world&#38;#39;s oldest mosques at Huaisheng Mosque.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Although steeped in beautiful history, the region is also a stunning vision of contemporary development, culture and industry. From the gathering of gleaming skyscrapers in pristine Singapore and Taiwan&#38;#39;s towering Taipei 101 to the cultural delights of Seoul, Beijing and Mumbai, Asia overflows with culture. World-class shopping, fascinating museums, theme parks and impressive landmarks are found throughout some of Asia&#38;#39;s biggest cities, including Singapore, Taipei, Tokyo, Beijing and Seoul. &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class Flights to Asia&#60;/strong&#62;. &#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In a region known for its amazing food, you&#38;#39;ll want to sample the local flavors. Thai, Japanese, Chinese, Philippine and Indian cuisine offer distinctive styles and spices and create an adventure for your palate. Whether you choose to taste the delights in five-star Singapore restaurants or in Thai street markets, exploring the local cuisine can make a trip to Asia unforgettable.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Luxury with FlyFirst.com&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your excursion to alluring Asia in the pampering comfort of first class seats or the efficiency of business class fares. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy gracious and time-saving services, five-star cuisine, lush amenity kits and all of the accouterments you need to make your time in the air productive and restful. Better still, FlyFirst.com brings you all of these first-rate services at discounts of up to 70 percent so that you can save thousands on first class seats, business class fares and even premium last minute flights.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4260</first_class_price><business_class_price>3280</business_class_price><seo><description>Cheap Business Class Flights to Asia, Last Minute First Class Fares to Asia, Cheap Fares</description><keywords>Cheap Business, First Class Fares, Cheap Last Minute Business Class Airline , Cheap Airline Tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>2e10432568924a58ae1f4a6da117686f.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Cheap Business Flights to Asia, Last Minute</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>047cea606c6346d8955fb8235f132268.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>First Class Tickets To Asia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c83df1af3e144a619b7e305de102b82c.jpg</alias><content_id>2</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute To Asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>Australia</name><title>Cheap Business and First Class Flights to Australia, Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class to Australia</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Australia</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Asia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Asia. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Australia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Fossils, Cliff-side Baths and the Great Barrier Reef&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Bountiful beaches, bustling cities and the vast Bush make the land down under an appealing spot for travelers. Even Australia&#38;#39;s modern cities are flavored with the unique character of Australian ingenuity and flair. Iconic Sydney Opera House&#38;#39;s dazzling white sails welcome visitors to the harbor-side metropolis and a world of uncommon adventure. Bustling Melbourne and Brisbane on the east coast, Perth on the west and Darwin on the north teem with robust business districts, wide-open beaches and a welcoming spirit.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Adventuresome travelers relish Australia&#38;#39;s adrenaline-inducing activities such as climbing the Sydney Harbor Bridge, scuba diving the Great Barrier Reef, ascending the steep Blue Mountains aboard the Scenic Cableway and spotting Daintree Village crocodiles. Active travelers don&#38;#39;t miss a chance to surf Australia&#38;#39;s stellar waves, traverse the Blue Mountains&#38;#39; many canyons and hike the Overland Trail.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Riversleigh&#38;#39;s countless rare fossils, Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary&#38;#39;s fascinating wildlife and the exhibits at the Australian Museum offer hours of entertainment for families traveling to the vast nation. Rejuvenate in Newcastle&#38;#39;s ocean baths, including the Bogey Hole baths carved out of the cliffs by convicts in the early 1800s.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Take Advantage of Luxury Travel on Discounted Business and First Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Save your energy for exploring Australia by traveling in the lap of luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s business class deals and reduced-fare first class flights. At the airport, you may enjoy special customs and security queues, privileged entree to high-end lounges and all the refreshing services imaginable. On board your flight, dine on five-star quality meals with free-flowing champagne and make use of your lengthy flight with comfortable beds and expansive work spaces. With business and first class flights, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Australia rested and keen to experience all that Oz has to offer.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our expert travel professionals will save you up to 70 percent on first class flights to Australia and provide you with unrivaled service in the process.FlyFirst specilize in &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#38;#160;At times, we can offer business class deals and cheap first class flights at prices comparable to economy class. We are the industry leaders in luxury travel and offer you peace of mind that you are receiving the very best prices available on premium flights. Call us today or use our simple online form to get a fast, free quote on your unforgettable Australian adventure.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><first_class_price>4890</first_class_price><business_class_price>3670</business_class_price><seo><description>Cheap and Discounted Business Class Airfares, cheap first class airline, cheap first class fares
</description><keywords>AUSTRALIA FIRST CLASS FLIGHT DISCOUNTS, Last Minute First Class Ticket Cheap to Asia, First Class Flight to Frankfurt, Business cheap first class seats, business class airfare to Asia</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8da19f2c07c8460ba2e04de6157b2a96.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>cheap business class to Australia</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>300b10a2c76c4eea8468765f3488d8c4.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>last minute business class to Australia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a23e1109fc6849a0acabef0749dc3f82.jpg</alias><content_id>3</content_id><title>cheap first class to Australia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>