<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?><items><item><country_id>6</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>USA</name><title>Cheap Business Class to USA &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-to-USA</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to USA, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to USA. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to USA.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Massive Waterfalls, Giant Redwoods and the Grand Canyon&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Natural wonders are scattered throughout the U.S., offering beautiful landscapes and awe-inspiring vistas. In the country&#38;#39;s southeastern states, explore the marshy Everglades, relish Tennessee&#38;#39;s exhilarating waterfalls and glimpse the expansive Mississippi River Delta. Head north to discover the grandeur of the Great Lakes and Niagara Falls or journey west to experience the Grand Canyon and the Painted Desert. Wander through forests of giant redwoods in the nation&#38;#39;s West Coast, or venture across the Pacific Ocean to trek up Hawaii&#38;#39;s Diamond Head for jaw-dropping views.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;While natural landmarks abound in the U.S., the country is equally known for its man-made landmarks and attractions. The nation&#38;#39;s cultural jewels create appealing adventures for travelers, from Native American ruins and Alaska&#38;#39;s native Inuit villages to San Francisco&#38;#39;s bustling Chinatown and New York&#38;#39;s Little Italy. World-class museums, vibrant theaters, rich historical landmarks and immense shopping malls create countless opportunities to experience the country&#38;#39;s melting pot character.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Those looking for recreation delight in the nation&#38;#39;s abundant surfing on both coasts, gambling in famous casino districts and skiing the Rocky Mountains. Push it to the limit with a hike up Yosemite&#38;#39;s Half Dome.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Travel For An American Adventure in Cheap Business Class Cabin&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The only thing better than journeying to the &#38;quot;land of the free&#38;quot; in supreme luxury is traveling there in premium style with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class fares and business class deals&#60;/strong&#62;. Your ultimate travel experience begins at the airport with expedited customs queues and exclusive access to renowned airport lounges catering to every comfort. Complimentary refreshments, attentive concierges, salons, spas, entertainment options and business centers make airport layovers rejuvenating and pleasurable. On board your business or first class flight, the luxury continues with ample beverages, stellar meals created by award-winning chefs, pampering bed turn-down service and the devotion of gracious attendants.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;This luxurious experience is affordable with our discounts of up to 70 percent on first class flights and business class seats. Count on our knowledgeable travel professionals to offer unrivaled savings and unparalleled service. FlyFirst.com is a leader in the&#60;strong&#62; first and business class industry&#60;/strong&#62;, offering superior &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on all types of travel, from last minute deals to dramatic savings on one-way, round trip, multi-city and open-ended &#60;strong&#62;first and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today to schedule your ultimate adventure to America, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be enjoying the exquisite luxury of &#60;strong&#62;first and business class&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>2370</first_class_price><business_class_price>3460</business_class_price><seo><description>Cheap Business and First Class Flights to USA, last minute business ticket to USA </description><keywords>Cheap First Class , Business Ticket Deals, Last Minute Flight Busienss to USA</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>db4229d28a9e4c368eb9d9dc8a7b5ad1.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fare, discounted </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>cafbca8fb50249cf88c3e0170d557b29.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>last minute business class flight</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>cd044ec8ec70434c8ec906885b0b7f37.jpg</alias><content_id>6</content_id><title>cheap business class deals</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>7</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name> Australia</name><title>Business Class Flights to Australia, Discounted First Class Fares Save Up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Australia</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Australia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Australia. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Australia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Fossils, Cliff-side Baths and the Great Barrier Reef&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Bountiful beaches, bustling cities and the vast Bush make the land down under an appealing spot for travelers. Even Australia&#38;#39;s modern cities are flavored with the unique character of Australian ingenuity and flair. Iconic Sydney Opera House&#38;#39;s dazzling white sails welcome visitors to the harbor-side metropolis and a world of uncommon adventure. Bustling Melbourne and Brisbane on the east coast, Perth on the west and Darwin on the north teem with robust business districts, wide-open beaches and a welcoming spirit.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Adventuresome travelers relish Australia&#38;#39;s adrenaline-inducing activities such as climbing the Sydney Harbor Bridge, scuba diving the Great Barrier Reef, ascending the steep Blue Mountains aboard the Scenic Cableway and spotting Daintree Village crocodiles. Active travelers don&#38;#39;t miss a chance to surf Australia&#38;#39;s stellar waves, traverse the Blue Mountains&#38;#39; many canyons and hike the Overland Trail.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Riversleigh&#38;#39;s countless rare fossils, Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary&#38;#39;s fascinating wildlife and the exhibits at the Australian Museum offer hours of entertainment for families traveling to the vast nation. Rejuvenate in Newcastle&#38;#39;s ocean baths, including the Bogey Hole baths carved out of the cliffs by convicts in the early 1800s.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Take Advantage of Luxury Travel in Discounted Business &#38;amp; First Class Seat&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Save your energy for exploring Australia by traveling in the lap of luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s business class deals and reduced-fare first class flights. At the airport, you may enjoy special customs and security queues, privileged entree to high-end lounges and all the refreshing services imaginable. On board your flight, dine on five-star quality meals with free-flowing champagne and make use of your lengthy flight with comfortable beds and expansive work spaces. With business and first class flights, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Australia rested and keen to experience all that Oz has to offer.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our expert travel professionals will save you up to 70 percent on first class flights to Australia and provide you with unrivaled service in the process. At times, we can offer business class deals and &#60;strong&#62;cheap first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; at prices comparable to economy class. We are the industry leaders in &#60;strong&#62;luxury trave&#60;/strong&#62;l and offer you peace of mind that you are receiving the very best &#60;strong&#62;prices available on premium flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us today or use our simple online form to get a fast, free quote on your unforgettable Australian adventure.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3470</first_class_price><business_class_price>2560</business_class_price><seo><description>last minute flight to Australia, last minute business class, discounted first class, best business class fare</description><keywords>business class tickets to Australia, business class ticket, First class flight, First class ticket, business air tickets, first class airfare, </keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b7d9c41dbecc44258981fca016ad1ccb.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>first class deals discounted airline prices </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d257f8b55ed74909b072f3aad631d6f8.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>cheap business and first class to australia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>df21cb85ffff44cf91aae845360c2bcb.jpg</alias><content_id>7</content_id><title>last minute business class to australia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>8</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>China</name><title>Cheap Business Class &#38; Discounted First Class to China </title><alias>Last-Minute-Cheap-Business-to-China</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to China, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to China. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Asia. Best Business Class Deals. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h4&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Journey comfortably to the land of the sleeping giant with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s outstanding &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;discounts on first class tickets and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;, saving you up to 70 percent off regular fare prices.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;A Land of Extremes&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With a country this immense, it&#38;#39;s unsurprising that one of its most notable characteristics is its accumulation of highs and lows. At 1.35 billion people, its population is the largest in the world, and it boasts an economy that is expanding more quickly than any other. Its terrain varies tremendously, from the world&#38;#39;s tallest mountain in Mount Everest to the world&#38;#39;s fourth lowest point at the Turpan Depression. Climates vary from frigid glaciers to warm, sunny beaches. With this diversity, China overflows with attractions to enchant travelers of all ages.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In keeping with China&#38;#39;s record-holding nature, the country&#38;#39;s most iconic landmark stretches for more than 13,000 miles. The Great Wall of China, originating in 220 B.C., is a masterpiece of function blended with exquisite form. China is home to part of the thousand-mile wide Gobi Desert and record-breaking 300-mile-per-hour high speed magnetic levitation trains. Its pristine beaches and superlative resorts of Yalong Bay on Hainan Island rival Hawaii for lush palm trees and intriguing wildlife.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;View giant pandas at Wolong National Nature Reserve, sample Shanghai and Beijing cuisine and shop along Nanjing Road. Tour fascinating religious sites such as the Guoging Temple and the 1,300 year old Huaisheng Mosque, one of the world&#38;#39;s oldest mosques. While in Beijing, don&#38;#39;t miss the Forbidden City, home of the Palace Museum and Chinese emperors of the past.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;First Class Luxuries and Cheap Business Class Flights&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;When traveling to a land of such magnitude, it&#38;#39;s fitting to make the trip in the ultimate opulence of plush first and business class flights. You&#38;#39;ll enjoy exclusive invitation to reserved airport lounges with superior services and complimentary edible delights. Sumptuous bedding, five-star quality meals and dedicated attendants highlight the flight experience. Most premium travelers enjoy expedited security and boarding queues and various concierge assistance. All of the luxuries are designed to help you arrive in China as rested and relaxed as possible.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;FlyFirst.com leads the way in providing unmatched discounts on first class flights and business class tickets. Known for first-rate service, our expert travel professionals provide discounts of up to 70 percent off &#60;strong&#62;business and first class fares&#60;/strong&#62;. These stellar discounts apply to first class flights of all types, including one-way, &#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62; and multi-city flights. Call today for a fast quote on your impending trip to China, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be jetting away to China in blissful comfort.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4430</first_class_price><business_class_price>3230</business_class_price><seo><description>business class flight, discount on business class tickets, last minute, first class ticket to China, deals on first class tickets</description><keywords>first class tickets, business class, last minute deal, best business class, business class to China, discounted first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6126a9fcd2d64540ab1fd2d4d1ee56b1.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>discounted business class fare</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>3cbbd1e9ba32476b95c06ffdfbe34c3a.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>last minute first class to asia</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>bae887e83b184bf6ac54141bd0ed6de6.jpg</alias><content_id>8</content_id><title>cheap business last minute deals</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>9</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Singapore</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights to Singapore. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Ticket-to-Singapore</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Singapore, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Singapore. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Singapore.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Contemporary, Cutting-Edge and Culturally Diverse&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Business travelers and holiday-makers relish the opportunities found on Singapore&#38;#39;s 63 islands. The city is filled with economic success, with 7,000-plus multinational companies, a financial center that is the world&#38;#39;s fourth largest and the fifth busiest shipping port on earth. With its vibrant economic advantages, it&#38;#39;s no surprise that Singapore continues its legacy as an original member of the Four Asian Tigers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Exhilarating activities abound for business and pleasure travelers to this lustrous city. It is home to the world&#38;#39;s second largest gambling market, centered around the immense Marina Bay Sands and Resorts World Sentosa. World-class shopping, majestic historic architecture and spellbinding museums offer hours of entrancing entertainment. Don&#38;#39;t miss the awe-inspiring and unforgettable Crane Dance at Singapore&#38;#39;s Resort World, where water and lights create a dreamlike vision of epic proportions. FlyFirst offers c&#60;strong&#62;heap business class to Singapore , last minute first class fares.&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Adventure seekers are occupied with Universal Studios Singapore on the enchanting island of Sentosa and the city&#38;#39;s 50 parks and recreation areas. End your day at the Riverside district, where theaters, restaurants, nightclubs and museums offer unmatched diversions.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Premium Travel Enhances The Experience&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Lengthy flights to Singapore aren&#38;#39;t energy draining when traveling aboard the comfort of first class seats or business class flights. With premium air travel, the luxury begins at the airport with privileged lounges providing every creature comfort and refreshment imaginable. In flight, you&#38;#39;ll dine on meals designed by world-class chefs, sip glass after glass of champagne, sleep on plush mattresses in crisp pajamas and work in spacious accommodations. With this level of opulence, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in gorgeous Singapore relaxed and ready to take on the city.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our unmatched savings on premium travel applies to &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; in nearly all situations. From last minute deals to terrific &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; on one-way, multi-city and open-jaw fares, you can count on FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s expert travel professionals to unearth the very &#60;strong&#62;best deals available&#60;/strong&#62;. As a leader in the &#60;strong&#62;business and first class travel&#60;/strong&#62; industry, booking with FlyFirst.com offers you first-rate customer service and the largest &#60;strong&#62;discounts on first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; around. Call us or submit our simple online form to find out just how much we can save you on your adventure to Singapore.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4580</first_class_price><business_class_price>2840</business_class_price><seo><description>business class deals to Singapore, first class discounted tickets, business class flight tickets, first class seats</description><keywords>business class tickets to Singapore, first class tickets to singapore, best business class fare, discounted airfare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>bf6541ecc3df467a9213e08d4e37637d.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>cheap business flights</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>d8a831c7833048db8ed27d9d63fefc6f.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>first class deals , cheap business class fares</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c1eff13d9e624c18b270147286a0a9e8.jpg</alias><content_id>9</content_id><title>last minute business class fare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>10</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Switzerland</name><title>Last Minute Business Class &#38; Cheap First Class to Switzerland</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-to-Switzerland</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Switzerland, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Switzerland. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Switzerland.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Explore Invigorating Switzerland&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Certainly, Switzerland offers its iconic, world-class chocolates, terrifically accurate timepieces and fresh-from-the-cow cheeses, and you should definitely sample one or all of these perfections. For a truly rewarding trip to the beautiful country, though, move beyond the stereotypes and explore Switzerland&#38;#39;s robust recreation and rich cultural attractions.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The towering Alps dominate much of Switzerland&#38;#39;s landscape and provide ample opportunities to get outside and relish the crisp, fresh air. Hiking, cycling and skiing are favorite pastimes at the famous slopes. While the Matterhorn is the country&#38;#39;s most famous mountaintop, there are countless others to experience. Take a ride on the world&#38;#39;s first revolving gondola to delight in a 360 degree view of Mt. Titlis, or head to Alpnachstad for an even more unique thrill. There, you&#38;#39;ll board the steepest cog railway in the world to ascend more than 5,500 feet at a 48 percent gradient to Pilates Kulm.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you&#38;#39;ve enjoyed the abundant recreation, enjoy some of Switzerland&#38;#39;s more relaxing attractions. Get a peak at Heidi&#38;#39;s World, tour some of the country&#38;#39;s 1,000-plus museums or scout the 44 B.C. Roman settlement August Raurica. Take a step back in time at Stein am Rhein and its looming mountaintop Hohenklingen Castle. Stein am Rhein&#38;#39;s Old Town is fabulously preserved and includes the medieval St. Georgen&#38;#39;s Monastery.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Affluence Is The Hallmark Of Luxury Travel, Travel in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;It&#38;#39;s fitting to travel to one of the world&#38;#39;s wealthiest countries aboard opulent first and business class. As soon as you enter the airport, you&#38;#39;ll be pampered at choice lounges offering everything from complimentary meals and business centers to spa services and entertainment. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll savor champagne with five-star cuisine as you settle in to roomy leather seats. The ultimate bed turn-down service includes fresh pajamas, cushioned mattresses and fluffy pillows. You&#38;#39;ll arrive in Switzerland refreshed and eager to appreciate all Switzerland offers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our unrivaled service leads the industry in providing dramatically &#60;strong&#62;discounted business and first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. Our skilled travel professionals can save you as much as 70 percent, sometimes ticket prices are even less than regular coach fares. Our remarkable &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; apply to premium travel of all types, including multi-city, open-jaw and last minute flights. Call us today or submit our simple online form to find out how much money you can save on your next expedition to Switzerland.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3430</first_class_price><business_class_price>2560</business_class_price><seo><description>best deals on business class, best first class fare, discounted tickets, first class to Switzerland, prices for business class tickets</description><keywords>business class flight, first class flight, savings on business class, savings on first class tickets, business class to Switzerland</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>247b82984cae4f56adb20a0458cef705.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Switzerland</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ae5164181b3c4c4cbd75300fddc64c6d.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Cheap Flights in Business to Switzerland</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>59c3cf6012de4440828b362d444eeda5.jpg</alias><content_id>10</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>11</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Taiwan</name><title>Discounted Business Class Airline Tickets , Save Thousands on Last Minute First Class Flights </title><alias>Cheap-Last-Minute-Flights-to-Taiwan</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Taiwan, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Taiwan. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h3&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Taiwan.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Skyscrapers and Waterfalls&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;One of the original Four Asian Tigers, Taiwan is an economic powerhouse with a long history of European, Chinese and Japanese influences. In Taiwan&#38;#39;s north, Taipei and New Taipei City are gleaming, bustling cities with some of the largest populations in the world. Relish unique views from the 91st-story outdoor observation deck of Taipei 101, one of the tallest buildings in the world. Its iconic design molds modern steel and glass into pagoda-like tiers and is an appealing symbol of the country.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The Taipei area is full of cultural delights, from the grand Chiang Kai-shek Memorial Hall and Fort Santo Domingo to the divine beauty of the Zushi Temple in Sanxia. Fascinating museums are scattered throughout the area, including the Shihsanhang Museum of Archaeology and the Museum of World Religions. Travelers enjoy wandering the paper lantern-lined streets and ending an exciting day at Taipei&#38;#39;s vibrant night markets.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Away from the cities, the country&#38;#39;s mountains are filled with lush forests, thundering waterfalls and sinuous rivers. Take in the serenity of the 11-mile long Taroko Gorge canyon and hike Lalashan Mountain&#38;#39;s many trail. At Lalashan, delight in the region&#38;#39;s abundant peach orchards and 2,800-year-old giant cypress trees.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;At the southern end of Taiwan is its oldest city, Tainan. Stunning temples such as Wufei Temple and Datianhou Temple pepper the city. Visitors marvel at the imposing fortress Eternal Golden Castle and the Chihkan Towers, also known as the Tower of Red-haired Barbarians. Tainan also boasts a lively metropolis with a bounty of night markets and shopping areas.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury You Deserve in Business and First Class Seats&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With all that you want to experience in Taiwan, make the journey there comfortable and restful aboard plush first and business class cabins. You&#38;#39;ll have access to privileged airport lounges featuring countless pampering services and refreshments. On your flight, you&#38;#39;ll settle into soft, leather seats that provide enough room for comfortable dining, working and sleeping. With all these gracious, luxury services, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in Taiwan refreshed and eager to explore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;At FlyFirst.com, you have access to stellar &#60;strong&#62;discounts on first class fares and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Our expert travel professionals offer discounts of up to 70 percent off all types of premium travel, including multi-city trips and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. When you use FlyFirst.com, you are assured that you are receiving the very &#60;strong&#62;best available first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;discounted business class flights to Taiwan&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>5270</first_class_price><business_class_price>3440</business_class_price><seo><description>cheap first class fare, cheap business class to Taiwan, business class travel, first class travel, business class seats</description><keywords>first class deals, business class deals to Taiwan, first class airline, cheapest business class tickets, cheap first class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ad8d0c5761d94c2aa649a87a79410fc2.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fares to Taiwan</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>76d82367265546e9bd0739c7fc313768.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Asia </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>e7476c29a5374b10b27c90346e53aff1.jpg</alias><content_id>11</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class to Asia </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>12</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Thailand</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Thailand &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Ticket-to-Thailand</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Thailand, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Thailand. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;h3&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Thailand.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h3&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Uncover the Mysteries of Siam&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Although Siam has long since given way to the name &#38;quot;Thailand,&#38;quot; the nation&#38;#39;s deeply embedded religions and culture continue to influence Thailand. Experience the country&#38;#39;s rich past, present and future in the hectic city of Bangkok, the world&#38;#39;s third most visited city. For awe-inspiring glimpses of Thailand&#38;#39;s Buddhist temples, trek to intricately decorated Wat Arun and the immense red and yellow Wat Pho. Wat Pho is Bangkok&#38;#39;s largest temple and is known for its gold-plated reclining Buddha that stretches more than 150 feet. Famous for its energetic nightlife, Bangkok also offers lively theater and world-class shopping.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Delightful tropical beaches line Thailand&#38;#39;s coast and surround its many islands. Kayak, parasail or ride elephants along the beach in popular Phuket or settle into the pristine sand and quite beaches of Ko Chang and Ko Lipe.#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Even away from the beaches, Thailand offers a world of breathtaking activities. Hike through stunning nature reserves of Khao Sok National Park or head to Kanchanaburi to see the storied bridge spanning the River Kwai. Ayutthaya is Siam&#38;#39;s original capital and lures visitors to ensconce themselves in the history and tradition of Thailand. As the one-time trading capital of Asia, Ayutthaya housed more than one million residents by 1700 and now is home to the temple Wat Phra Si Sanphet and countless ruins of ancient monasteries.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Make Your Journey Luxurious in Discounted&#38;#160;Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Flights to Thailand are time-consuming, but they can be restful when flying aboard the luscious comfort of first and business class cabins. The luxury begins at the airport with exclusive invitation to reserved airport lounges. The lounges feature refreshing dining, ample entertainment, relaxing spa and salon services, gracious concierge assistance and fully equipped business centers. On board your flight, you&#38;#39;ll relish even more personalized service. From delectable meals designed by world-famous chefs and endless cocktails to elite bed turn-down services, you&#38;#39;ll extol the virtues of first and business class forevermore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you need &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; or &#60;strong&#62;business class deals&#60;/strong&#62; for a multi-city trip, FlyFirst.com offers the same &#60;strong&#62;deep discounts&#60;/strong&#62; of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Our expert travel professionals are dedicated to offering unparalleled service while providing the ultimate discounts. At times, we can even offer first class tickets that are less expensive than economy fares. Call us today to book your amazing deals on last minute flights and first class fares so you can be on your way in comfort and style to stunning Thailand.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4380</first_class_price><business_class_price>3460</business_class_price><seo><description>last minute to Thailand, last minute flight, best last minute business class, business travel, first class travel</description><keywords>sale on business class tickets, airfare sale, business flight, first class cabin to Thailand, best business class cabin, cheap business flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>af0372616d29438a8952524e157f9af2.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Cheap First Class to Thailand</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>52bcb12079b243829ba5be3c9fa5c591.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Flights to Thailand</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>bffd1c6c5a54430a8957607c29a49f7a.jpg</alias><content_id>12</content_id><title>Last Minute Deals to Thailand </title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>13</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>United Kingdom</name><title>Cheap Business Class to United Kingdom &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Ticket-to-United-Kingdom</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to London, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to United Kingdom. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;h4&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to UK.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h4&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;With a history spanning 30,000 years, the U.K. teems with ancient ruins and historic sites. In the north, tour the 5,000-year-old village of Skara Brae, or discover the treasures of Scotland&#38;#39;s Edinburgh and Culzean castles. Soak in the atmosphere of the cliff-side medieval Dunluce Castle in Northern Ireland, or marvel at England&#38;#39;s mystical Stonehenge. England overflows with cultural sites, from St. Paul&#38;#39;s Cathedral and Buckingham Palace to dozens of museums and historic estates.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you&#38;#39;ve explored the region&#38;#39;s history, enjoy some of the world&#38;#39;s most spectacular natural wonders. In Scotland, visit Loch Ness and the Highlands&#38;#39; Isle of Sky, and in Northern Ireland, don&#38;#39;t miss the 40,000 stone volcanic &#38;quot;pillars&#38;quot; of the Giant&#38;#39;s Causeway in County Antrim. Delight in beautiful hikes near the Pistyll Rhaeadr, Wales&#38;#39; tallest waterfall or explore the caves at Cheddar Gorge in England.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you prefer cultural sites or adventures, the U.K.&#38;#39;s variety makes for an unforgettable trip.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Royal Luxury is Yours with&#38;#160;Discounted First Class Ticket&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Treat yourself to the luxury you deserve by flying to the U.K. aboard sumptuous first and &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62; cabins. You&#38;#39;ll have exclusive entree to some of the best airport lounges where you can grab a bite to eat, mingle with fellow elite travelers, wrap up work duties, enjoy a massage or refresh with a cleansing shower. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll sink into wide leather seats that lie flat to encourage restful slumber, free-flowing champagne and meals created by famous chefs. All of these services and amenities will deliver you to the U.K. feeling like royalty.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With our impressive FlyFirst.com &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, you won&#38;#39;t have to pay an arm and a leg for royal service. Our &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; are secured at discounts of up to 70 percent off published rates and ensure you can travel in style. These outstanding discounts are available for all travel needs, from last minute flights and one-way trips to multi-city itineraries and open-ended trips. On top of our unrivaled &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, our knowledgeable travel professionals are always available to offer first-rate service. We specialize in providing the ultimate assistance throughout your trip so you don&#38;#39;t have to worry about last minute itinerary adjustments or emergency issues. To secure your amazingly affordable first class seats and &#60;strong&#62;reduced business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, call us today, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be jetting to the U.K. in royal splendor.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3760</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><seo><description>business class airfare, first class flight to UK, best business class fares, business class cheap, business class cheap, cheap first class</description><keywords>best business class price to UK, business class tickets, discounts on first class, flight to United Kingdom</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>549a99d8569640f99b35527d149480a3.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class To London</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>53170c6f609246118b2a41cb01757fff.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Fare to UK</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>675e3c8e37434c87bc5f1080dc77749b.jpg</alias><content_id>13</content_id><title>First Class Discounted Fare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>14</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Vietnam</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Vietnam &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights. Save Up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-to-Vietnam</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Vietnam, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Vietnam. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;h2&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;font-size: 13px; line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Vietnam.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Ancient Cities and Pristine Beaches&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Dating back to the Paleolithic Age, Vietnam&#38;#39;s long history is told through its many palaces, ancient cities and natural resources. Like a misty movie set, Ha Long Bay&#38;#39;s deep aquamarine water is surrounded by a cove of rising monoliths. The bay holds abundant caves perfect for exploring and plenty of tourist attractions.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Travel to ancient town Hoi An for a glimpse of life in a 15th century trading port, and view the ornate Cao Dai temples in Tay Ninh, Da Lat and My Tho. History and cosmopolitan buildings intermingle in big cities Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi, where locals and visitors can marvel at the Presidential Palace and Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Lavish Luxury to Vietnam in Affordable Business Class Cabin&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Whether you&#38;#39;re traveling alone or with colleagues or family, your journey to Vietnam is more enjoyable in spacious first or &#60;strong&#62;business class&#60;/strong&#62;. As a premium traveler, you&#38;#39;ll receive pampering service from the moment you reach the airport. Appealing airport lounges provide a retreat from the airport masses and offer you gracious services and amenities designed to help you relax. In the air, your luxury cabin invites you to settle into the roomy leather seats, kick up your feet and let the accommodating attendants take care of you. You&#38;#39;ll dine on five-star quality meals, sip free-flowing beverages, access state-of-the-art entertainment systems and relish the fully-flat bedding. All of this and more is designed to create a space where you can make the most of your flight time.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;When you book with FlyFirst.com, you book with the confidence that you are receiving the very best available rates on &#60;strong&#62;first class seats and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Our experienced travel professionals are dedicated to finding the deepest discounts on all types of travel, including one-way trips, multi-city destinations, open-ended return tickets and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on published fares; sometimes, our first class seats and business class flights are as inexpensive as coach.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;On top of stellar discounts, we are committed to providing you with the ultimate in personalized service. Whether you have complicated travel requirements or need assistance rearranging plans in the middle of your trip, we are here to serve you. Call us now to secure your outstanding &#60;strong&#62;discount on first class seats or last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can be on your way to brilliant Vietnam.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4560</first_class_price><business_class_price>3340</business_class_price><seo><description>affordable business class to Vietnam, affordable first class, affordable business class tickets, business class cabin sale</description><keywords>cheap business class flight, last minute business class, airline tickets, business class deals to Vietnam</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>5b2d2f96aaad43e18c3b079cefb4cf0c.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Seats to Vietnam </title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>36529e695ce645ae96446337c7ac8506.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class To Vietnam</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>0d7d70e870134055afbd4668c9301815.jpg</alias><content_id>14</content_id><title>First Class Cheap to Vietnam</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>16</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Spain</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Spain &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save on Last Minute Travel</title><alias>Cheap-Last-Minute-Flights-to-Spain</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Spain, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Spain. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#38;#160;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to Spain.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Palaces, Paella and Mountain Peaks&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Warm people and an even-warmer climate beckons you to the lovely country of Spain. With ravishing cathedrals and palaces, there are plenty of cultural sites to explore in Spain&#38;#39;s many cities.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Famed Spanish artist Gaudi grandly designed nine of Barcelona&#38;#39;s magnificent structures, such as the Sagrada Familia, and should not be missed. Other fascinating sites in Barcelona include the Picasso Museum and the Catalan Gothic-styled Barcelona Cathedral.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In Madrid, visitors delight in the Plaza de Cibeles and the 18th century Royal Palace, the Spanish Royal Family&#38;#39;s official residence. The palace holds 3,418 rooms, some of which are open to the public.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The bustling coastal city of Valencia is the home of delectable paella and a cosmopolitan art scene. Revel in the artistry of the beautiful 15th century Silk Exchange building, then head to the city&#38;#39;s most iconic landmarks of Valencia Cathedral and its Miguelete Tower.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Dozens of other notable structures are spread throughout Spain, including the prehistoric Altamira Cave paintings in Cantabria, the ancient Roman Aqueduct of Segovia and Granada&#38;#39;s grand Alhambra. The massive Alhambra holds a 9th century citadel, Muslim palaces constructed in the 14th century and a 16th century palace built for Charles V.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Spain offers bountiful recreation at its many mountains, lakes and beaches. Burn off some of those late-night tapas calories by hiking or snowshoeing in the Pyrenees&#38;#39; Sant Maurici National Park, or kayaking near the warm beaches of San Sebasti&#38;aacute;n.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Sumptuous Seating to Spain&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Pamper yourself with the &#60;strong&#62;luxury&#60;/strong&#62; you deserve by selecting first or business class flights to Spain with help from FlyFirst.com. As a premium passenger, you&#38;#39;ll access exclusive airport lounges full of appealing services and high-end amenities. Expedited boarding and customs queues are frequently given to premium travelers, making your boarding and disembarking a pleasant, quick experience. On your flight, the pampering continues with five-star cuisine, over-sized leather seats, ample work spaces, privacy screens and bed turn-down service. You&#38;#39;ll land in Spain rested and keen to explore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our knowledgeable travel professionals find the very best deals available on premium flights to Spain and offer you superior service and a variety of travel options. One-way trips, multi-city destinations and last minute seats on &#60;strong&#62;cheap first and cheap business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; all receive our outstanding discounts of up to 70 percent. To secure your exceptional discounts on first class fares and &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;, call us today so that you can be on your way to sunny Spain in no time.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3890</first_class_price><business_class_price>2740</business_class_price><seo><description>business class flight, first class tickets, cheap tickets to Spain, cheap business flight, last minute discount for business class ticket</description><keywords>flight to Spain, business class flight, discounted first class, business class tickets discounts, best prices for business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>ec71aee4842646438599817d25380149.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fares to Spain</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>865443ed6734447aa1062a135f5349c1.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>First Class Last Minute to Spain</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>babd0ec0aca9486fa4539ed50ffcd174.jpg</alias><content_id>16</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Spain</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>17</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Qatar</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Qatar &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Ticket-to-Qatar</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Qatar, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Qatar. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;FlyFirst.com offers unparalleled discounts on first class fares and business class tickets to Singapore, saving you up to 70 percent off regular premium fares. With all that you will save on air travel to the Lion City, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty of funds to spend on enjoying Singapore&#38;#39;s exotic adventures.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Singapore.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Journey in style to the exotic land of Qatar with &#60;/span&#62;&#60;strong style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;affordable first class flights and discounted business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62; from FlyFirst.com. Nearly surrounded by the brilliant turquoise waters of the Persian Gulf, Qatar offers modern cities, a deeply rooted culture and one of the fastest growing economies in the world.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Capital city Doha offers a cross-cultural experience like no other. With the intensely blue bay as its backdrop, the city exudes modern achievements. Broad-laned roads curve along the coast, lined with palm trees and gleaming skyscrapers designed in a pleasing mix of contemporary glass and Moorish details.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once you take in Doha&#38;#39;s modern wonders, escape to the more iconic Middle East views of Khor al Udeid beach, where the tan-colored rolling sand dunes meet the Persian Gulf and offer plenty of relaxation and recreation. Head about 24 miles southwest of Doha to experience the eerie sounds of the Singing Sand Dunes.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Explore the region&#38;#39;s culture and history at Doha&#38;#39;s many museums, such as the Museum of Islamic Art. Sample wares and foods of all kinds at the old, traditional marketplace, Souq Waqif. Travel out of Doha to scout around the famed archaeological dig at Al Zubarah, where an old fort, a once-thriving village and an ancient mosque have been unearthed. End your day with a serene stroll along Doha&#38;#39;s Corniche promenade for an amazing sunset view of the Gulf.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Flights Await in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Begin your sojourn to world-class Qatar in the spacious elegance of first or business class. Your pampering experience begins even before you leave the ground, with exclusive access to privileged airport lounges. Have a bite to eat, mingle with fellow luxury passengers or just relax with spa and salon services at these airport oases. As you enter your first or business class cabin, you&#38;#39;ll be greeted by gracious attendants who are devoted to your every comfort. Meals designed by world-famous chefs, free-flowing drinks, abundant entertainment options and bed turn-down service are just some of the amenities you&#38;#39;ll enjoy on your premium flight. By the time you reach Doha International Airport, you&#38;#39;ll be relaxed and eager to experience all of Qatar&#38;#39;s delights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled savings of up to 70 percent on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, you&#38;#39;ll have plenty of funds left in your budget to truly explore Qatar. We are leaders in the &#60;strong&#62;luxury travel&#60;/strong&#62; industry, offering unmatched prices along with first-rate service. Our deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted fares&#60;/strong&#62; are available on all travel needs, including last minute flights, one-way tickets and multi-city trips. When you book your trip with FlyFirst.com, you can rest assured that you are getting the very best deal available on &#60;strong&#62;first class flights and business class fares to Qatar&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4580</first_class_price><business_class_price>3270</business_class_price><seo><description>discount first class, cheap business class to Qatar, cheap tickets first class, business class tickets, first class deals</description><keywords>last minute tickets, prices for flight to Qatar, business cabin, first cabin, business trip tickets, cheap flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b215541492824d2a82c5d58966f831f1.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Doha</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>6623ae6d0f3e4a108f320e66cc547d12.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>Last Minute Business class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>9ef7aeb30abd4970ab439d946e80bda7.jpg</alias><content_id>17</content_id><title>First Class Tickets To Qatar</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>18</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Italy</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Italy &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights. Save Up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-Italy</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Italy, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Italy. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Italy.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Ruins, Runways and Religion&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With a dozen renowned cities and even more small, charming villages, Italy offers a variety of locales and attractions to suit every interest. In the center of the country, Rome invites visitors to revel in ancient wonders such as the Colosseum and the Forum. Michaelangelo&#38;#39;s Piazza del Campidoglio is just a 15-minute stroll from the Colosseum and home to the magnificent basilica Santa Maria in Aracoeli, Palazzo Senatorio, Palazzo Nuovo and the Tabularium. Dozens of museums, fountains, statues and cathedrals are spread throughout Rome, offering plenty of activities for travelers.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;For world-class fashion shows and stellar shopping, trendsetters trek to Milan, the world&#38;#39;s celebrated fashion capital. While many visitors are occupied with the shopping in cosmopolitan Milan&#38;#39;s Fashion Quadrangle, others spend some time enjoying the city&#38;#39;s various historic sites. From the majestic white marble spires of the Gothic-era Duomo cathedral to the acclaimed performances at La Scala opera house, Milan is a perfect blend of modern culture and history.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Italy also offers countless delights for the senses. Drama, mystery and intrigue flourish at Carnivale in Venice. Elaborate costumes and intricate, surreal masks make the festival a unique experience in an already-enigmatic city. For a taste of the country&#38;#39;s famed vintages, head to Italy&#38;#39;s Tuscany region where the sun is warm, the hills are gentle and the locals are welcoming. Limoncello liqueur and dramatic seaside cliffs draw visitors to southern Italy&#38;#39;s Amalfi Coast, while abundant recreation takes travelers to Italy&#38;#39;s northern regions and the Italian Alps.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Travel Offers Pampering Comfort in&#38;#160;Cheap Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Every trip is better when it&#38;#39;s made in the posh style of first and &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Services and amenities are specifically designed to help you make the most of your flight time, from spacious work surfaces and electronic access to seats that convert to flat, plush beds. Even better, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy the services of &#60;strong&#62;exclusive airport lounges&#60;/strong&#62; before, between and after your flights.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent&#60;strong&#62; on first class flights to Italy&#60;/strong&#62; and receive spectacular service from our expert travel professionals. Whether you need affordable &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; on &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; or deeply discounted first class tickets on a multi-city trip, you can rest assured that you are receiving the very best possible deals. Call us today to access our stellar deals on first class seats and business class fares to intriguing Italy.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3760</first_class_price><business_class_price>2840</business_class_price><seo><description>business class travel, first class travel, business class discounts, first class discounts, cheap business class to Italy</description><keywords>economical first class seats, business class discounts, business class flight to Italy, first class, business class, deals on business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8c1714840a4b476fbe8f84c13b502b06.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>First Class Cheap to Italy</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>b6f6894b71324083b6f65c679bf6bd84.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class to Italy</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>456c501d363042f9ac72b78c879c647d.jpg</alias><content_id>18</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Fare to Italy</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>19</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Germany</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Germany &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-to-Germany</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Germany, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Germany. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Germany.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;At savings of up to 70 percent off regular fares, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy the luxury flight and still have room in your budget to fully explore the bountiful Deutschland.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Sculpted gardens and pristine streets create Germany&#38;#39;s crisp, clean atmosphere and welcome visitors to its many charms. Germany is filled with historic buildings resting side-by-side with glistening, modern structures. Trail through the country&#38;#39;s deep history with a trip to Berlin to view the 17th century Charlottenburg Palace, the awe-inspiring Berlin Cathedral, the art-filled Alte Nationalgalerie and the iconic Brandenburg Gate. Museum Island overflows with museums in a serene, picturesque setting, and don&#38;#39;t miss the red brick towers of Oberbaum Bridge, uniting two boroughs that were once separated by the Berlin Wall.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;The city&#38;#39;s newer structures are just a breathtaking as their historic counterparts. Gather at Potsdamer Platz to see some of Berlin&#38;#39;s newest towers and take in the night view of illuminated Fernsehturm Berlin, the tallest structure in Germany.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Frankfurt, Hamburg, Munich, Cologne offer countless opportunities to further revel in Germany&#38;#39;s varied history. You&#38;#39;ll also find abundant natural wonders and activities, such as world-class skiing near Munich and boating on Hamburg&#38;#39;s many waterways.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;For a comprehensive and magnificent tour of Germany&#38;#39;s history, take a cruise along the Rhine River, from Bingen to Koblenz. Nearly 30 castles, palaces, towers and fortresses loom over the river&#38;#39;s shores on towering cliffs and mountainsides, enhancing the majesty and grandeur of the medieval structures.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel In Comfort And Elegance&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Relax and relish the trip to Germany with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply &#60;strong&#62;discounted first and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Premium passengers enjoy exclusive entree to lavish airport lounges with bountiful and pampering high-end amenities, services and refreshments. Aboard your airplane, you&#38;#39;ll luxuriate in roomy seats, five-star cuisine, fully functional Internet and electronic outlets and white-glove service.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our experienced travel professionals are highly skilled at uncovering the &#60;strong&#62;very best deals on premium travel&#60;/strong&#62; and providing you with several travel options to best fit your schedule. Our industry-leading &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; of up to 70 percent are available on a variety of travel, including &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;, one-way trips, multi-city destinations and open-ended return tickets. On top of stellar &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62;, we offer unparalleled personalized service from the minute you call us to the time your final flight arrives home. To find out how much you can save on &#60;strong&#62;first class fares and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, simply call us today so that you can experience the ultimate Germany excursion.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3760</first_class_price><business_class_price>2730</business_class_price><seo><description>first class flight to Germany, business class tickets, discounted tickets, airline tickets discounts,business class sale</description><keywords>affordable business class fare, business class sale, discounted business class tickets to Germany, business class fare</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7980e76e8f24496b9fbd40fd9575d688.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Ticket To Germani</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>e2c4ec2577114fb5af4c1cd8c65f46cb.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Last Minute Flights to Germani</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>c539e265d35b4ed9a79d2c3e296c7c5d.jpg</alias><content_id>19</content_id><title>Cheap First Class Tickets to Germani</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>20</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>France</name><title>Cheap Business Class to France &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights. Save Up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-First-Class-Flights-to-France</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to France, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to France. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to France.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Make your flight to fabulous France in the luxury you deserve aboard FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply discounted first class seats and business class fares. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on these magnificent flights and have plenty of budget left over to enjoy the sights, cuisine and cultural delights of France.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;
    &#60;div&#62;Countless generations and noteworthy events created the stunning landscape and structures of France. From the Paleolithic cave paintings at Lascaux to the iconic Eiffel Tower in Paris, France is full of historic sites. For a sense of early France, don&#38;#39;t miss the Neolithic Carnac stones site in Brittany and the Roman Empire-era Maison Carr&#38;eacute;e in N&#38;icirc;mes. Walk through France&#38;#39;s rich history at the Ile-de-France region&#38;#39;s Palace of Versailles, Normandy&#38;#39;s Mont Saint-Michel and the Loire Valley&#38;#39;s Chateau de Chambord. In brilliant Paris, tour Basilique du Sacr&#38;eacute;-Coeur, the Louvre Museum and Notre-Dame de Reims.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Feast your senses on all of France&#38;#39;s delights, from high fashion to delectable cuisine. While in Paris, enjoy the fashion-forward shopping on apparel, perfumes and cosmetics along the Champs &#38;Eacute;lys&#38;eacute;es. Food and haute cuisine is a serious pursuit in France, whether you are enjoying an eclair or baguette at a sidewalk cafe or dining in some of France&#38;#39;s most prestigious Michelin-starred restaurants.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Treat Yourself to the Luxury of Cheap First Class and Business Class Flights&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;As a premium traveler, you are invited to enjoy exclusive airport lounges and all the pampering they include. Delicious meals, relaxing salon services, abundant entertainment and fully-equipped business centers are just the beginning of the numerous services offered at first class airport lounges. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll sink into plush leather seats that offer enough room to lounge, work, watch movies, play games and sleep. High-quality meals, bountiful champagne, ample storage and bed turn-down services all ensures that you arrive in France ready to explore the country&#38;#39;s wonders.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We offer incredible &#60;strong&#62;discounts&#60;/strong&#62; whether you are looking for &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;, one-way tickets or &#60;strong&#62;multi-city destination trips&#60;/strong&#62;. FlyFirst.com offers the highest level of service in the industry and some of the best prices on premium travel at up to 70 percent off regular rates. Our commitment to your needs last throughout your trip, so you never have to worry if you need to make sudden changes to your itinerary while you are traveling. Our expert travel professionals can help with your every travel need, so call us today to find out just how inexpensive your trip to France can be. In no time, you&#38;#39;ll be jetting off to lovely France in the luxury of &#60;strong&#62;first class seats or business class&#60;/strong&#62; cabins.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3940</first_class_price><business_class_price>2860</business_class_price><seo><description>flight to France, discounted flights, discounted airline tickets, first class discount</description><keywords>airline discounts, business class tickets, first class deals, cheap business class, first class to France</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>0aa6f243f9e54e42bb11a2395b1bb689.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>First Class Flight to Paris</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>ba9c6b9610c64dcfa96b01e9eb8cbaf3.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class Fare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>368b29424e02472298ca44d7aca63aff.jpg</alias><content_id>20</content_id><title>Cheap Tickets in Business Class France</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>21</country_id><continent_id>0</continent_id><name>South Africa</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights to South Africa. Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class.</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-South-Africa</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to South Africa, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to South Africa. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to South Africa.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Capes, Fossils and Safaris&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With more than 1,700 miles of coastline, South Africa is brimming with beaches, dramatic cliffs and outstanding views. At the southern end of South Africa, enjoy the Mediterranean climate while you bask in the views surrounding Cape Town&#38;#39;s exciting beaches. While in Cape Town, check out Table Mountain, the historic village at Simon&#38;#39;s Town and the infamous Cape of Good Hope.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Explore your own roots in South Africa&#38;#39;s prehistoric caves. The Cradle of Humankind is filled with archaeological sites where countless caves and lands overflow with hominin fossils. Sterkfontein, Coopers Cave and Gondolin Cave Kromdraai are just a few of the many areas to see human history unfold.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Tour the bushveld at the northern region of South Africa to reveal some of the world&#38;#39;s most fascinating wildlife. From lions and leopards to white rhinos and giraffes, the area is a nature lover&#38;#39;s dream. Some of the best areas to view South Africa&#38;#39;s diverse and abundant wildlife are Kruger National Park, Waterberg Biosphere Reserve and Mala Mala Game Reserve.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Cheap Business and First Class Luxury Travel&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Turn your long flight to South Africa into a refreshing respite aboard plush first class seats. You&#38;#39;ll have invitation-only access to some of the world&#38;#39;s most exclusive airport lounges. These high-end lounges teem with opulent amenities and relaxing services. Premium passengers often have access to expedited boarding and security queues, eliminating frustrating wait times. Aboard the plane, you&#38;#39;ll enter an oasis in the sky and sink into over-sized leather seats. Your attendant will even turn down your bed and add a cushioned mattress and fluffy pillows for your comfort. With all these services, you&#38;#39;ll arrive in South Africa rested and eager to tour the country&#38;#39;s bountiful sites.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We specialize in first-rate travel planning and stellar pricing. Our knowledgeable travel professionals are experts at unearthing the very &#60;strong&#62;best first class seat deals&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can travel in the luxury you deserve. Our unrivaled discounts of up to 70 percent are available for all travel types, including multi-city destinations and &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;. Even better, we are dedicated to serving you throughout your trip so there&#38;#39;s no need to worry if you need to make a sudden change to your itinerary in mid-trip. Call us today to secure your &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be relaxing in splendor.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>5240</first_class_price><business_class_price>3870</business_class_price><seo><description>business class cheap, discounted first class, luxury travel to South Africa,business class tciket</description><keywords>business, first, best travel deals, cheap business class to South Africa, cheap tickets, Cheap First Class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>1e576fa1e7ca470a8fcaf0af994702a6.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Fare to Africa</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>c0f5d9237a52417399dc9639886b5b2f.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Ticket to Africa</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>3d3b9ba1ae4c4e7cbf6a927583030185.jpg</alias><content_id>21</content_id><title>Cheap Firs Class To Africa</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>22</country_id><continent_id>3</continent_id><name>New Zealand</name><title>Cheap business class airfare and first class discount to New Zealand</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-to-New-Zealand</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to New Zealand, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to New Zealand. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to New Zeland.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Journey to the welcoming spirit, soft South Pacific trade winds and the vibrant Maori traditions of New Zealand. Your flight to gorgeous New Zealand can be just as amazing as your time on the islands when you fly in the glorious comfort of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s&#60;strong&#62; affordable first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Bungee Jumping, Geyser Spotting and Maori Traditions&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Nestled in the South Pacific seas southeast of Australia, New Zealand consists of two main islands and several smaller islands. Variety is the spice of New Zealand&#38;#39;s terrain, ranging for permanently frozen glaciers towering over the landscape to warm, pristine beaches. With that wide range of natural treasures, it&#38;#39;s no wonder that the country is known for its abundance of exciting activities, including mountain climbing, caving, wind surfing, kayaking and rafting. Unsurprisingly, New Zealand&#38;#39;s Queenstown is the birthplace of bungee jumping.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    While Auckland, Wellington and Christ Church are New Zealand&#38;#39;s largest cities, there are plenty of exciting adventures in the country&#38;#39;s smaller communities. Geothermal geysers and an authentic Maori village enliven Rotorua and Lamach Castle in Dunedin offers hours of entertainment for the whole family.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Exploring the vivid indigenous Maori culture is a must while you are in New Zealand. Whether you spend a day roaming the exhibits at national museum Te Papa Tongarewa or delighting in the rousing beat and intense colors of traditional Maori music and dance, the Maori culture is a triumph of spirit.&#38;#160;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;In the Lap of Luxury in Business Class Seat&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make the lengthy flight to New Zealand pleasurable aboard the luxury of first class and business class travel. The pampering begins even before you step foot on the plane, with &#60;strong&#62;first class airport lounges&#60;/strong&#62; featuring spa services, delectable meals and plush areas to relax, refresh and recharge. As you board your airplane, you&#38;#39;re welcomed into a serene space featuring spacious seats, ample work and storage areas and state-of-the-art entertainment systems. Your gracious flight attendants will serve you five-star meals, abundant beverages and turn down your bed when you want to sleep.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;br /&#62;
    With our exclusive services, you&#38;#39;ll access the deepest &#60;strong&#62;discounts on luxury airfare&#60;/strong&#62;, at up to 70 percent off regular rack rates. Whether you need &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; or a complicated &#60;strong&#62;multi-destination trip&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s unparalleled savings on premium travel apply. You&#38;#39;ll also receive our personalized customer service throughout your trip so that you don&#38;#39;t have to fret about any changes you might need to make while you are traveling. Enjoy these unrivaled savings on &#60;strong&#62;last minute business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can delight in all that gorgeous New Zealand offers.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4960</first_class_price><business_class_price>3780</business_class_price><seo><description>flight to New Zealand, business class ticket, least expensive business class</description><keywords>discount last minute business class, last minute flight to New Zealand, last minute travel deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6fb1c68200b04b67a855a6abd9d17278.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>LasT Minute Business Class Flight</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>806f9c4ac9154b3b89750a5ef96ab73d.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>First Class Deals</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>515ffd0cad4f447eaed5c89dd92c7619.jpg</alias><content_id>22</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Tickets</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>23</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Philippines</name><title>Affordable Business Class Tickets &#38; Discounted First Class to Philippines</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-To-Philippines</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Philippines, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Philipines. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Philippines.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Tropical rain forests and modern, bustling cities rest amiably side-by-side in the unique land that is the Philippines. Trek to the lush Philippine islands in heady luxury with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s&#60;strong&#62; affordable first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;reduced-fare business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. Our deep discounts save you as much as 70 percent on published fares, leaving you plenty of funds to fully experience the wonders held within the Philippines.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With more than 7,000 islands, the Philippines is a treasure trove of diversity. With a 67,000 year human history, it&#38;#39;s unsurprising that the country&#38;#39;s natural diversity is echoed in its many cultural influences, including colonial Spanish and Mexican, American, Malay and Japanese.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    That cultural variety results in bountiful attractions in big city Manila such as the oldest Chinatown in the world. Its cuisine also benefits from plentiful cultural influences, so don&#38;#39;t miss sampling the country&#38;#39;s distinctive cuisine.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Away from the city, explore the famed 2,000 year old rice terraces in Banaue to get a feel for the lifestyle of ancient Philippinos. In addition to its rich history and tradition, recreation is abundant here. In Batangas, scuba dive and wander the Taal Volcano and Taal heritage town; in Camarines Sur, laze on the black or white sand beaches and enjoy the coral reef&#38;#39;s colorful wildlife; and in Cagayan de Oro, thrill your adventurous nature while whitewater rafting.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Travel in Style in Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make the long journey in comfort with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s hugely &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class tickets &#60;/strong&#62;or &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll be pampered from start to finish with access to exclusive airport lounges and plush, spacious on-board seating. With plenty of room to spread out and work, dine or rest, your premium airline seat is designed to offer the ultimate in comfort and versatility. You&#38;#39;ll dine on meals created by world-famous chefs, sip free-flowing beverages and pass the time with state-of-the-art entertainment systems. As a premium traveler, your bed turn-down service includes a lush down comforter, fresh pajamas, fluffy pillows and mattress-topped beds. &#60;strong&#62;Flying in first or business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; creates a restful, productive oasis in the sky that delivers you to the Phillipines refreshed and ready to explore.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s expert professionals and dramatically reduced&#60;strong&#62; luxury flights&#60;/strong&#62; are just part of our industry-leading services. Whether you need &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62;, open-ended return tickets, multi-city destinations or one-way tickets, we provide the same outstanding discounts of up to&#60;strong&#62; 70 percent off regular airfares&#60;/strong&#62;. When you book with FlyFirst.com, you know that you are receiving the very best savings available. Call us today to secure your affordable and impressive &#60;strong&#62;first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; and service-filled &#60;strong&#62;business class flights&#60;/strong&#62; so that you can enjoy all the treasures found in the Philippines.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4260</first_class_price><business_class_price>3470</business_class_price><seo><description>business class, business class deals, first class seats, last minute flight to Philippines, discounted fare</description><keywords>cheap business class to Philippines, cheap first class tickets, discounted airline tickets, last minute business class</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6d55f91e84fc43489bfcaea78bd41d2b.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Flight</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>94441dc1e6f046a1903f29697918c445.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class Deals</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>98bd1855f95344bdbea53e0c539da477.jpg</alias><content_id>23</content_id><title>Business Class Airfare</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>24</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Russia</name><title>Best First Class Deals &#38; Business Class Tickets to Russia</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-to-Russia</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Russia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Russia. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Russia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;With premium travel discounts of up to 70 percent, your travel budget will have plenty left over to fully explore the rich culture, vibrant history and stunning architecture so renowned in the Russian Federation.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Travel to the mysterious and expansive land of Russia in the spacious luxury of economical first class deals and reduced-fare business class tickets from FlyFirst. With premium travel discounts of up to 70 percent, your travel budget will have plenty left over to fully explore the rich culture, vibrant history and stunning architecture so renowned in the Russian Federation.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Byzantine Architecture and Bold Skyscrapers&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With its varied history and expansion over the centuries, Russia was a melting pot as far back at the 10th century. The actual land encompassed by the Russian Federation is so vast that it stretches across nine time zones. With that immense size and voluminous history, Russia offers a tremendous variety of cultural attractions and architecture.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Big, contemporary city Moscow overflows with shining glass skyscrapers, evidence of one of the world&#38;#39;s fastest growing economies. In spite of its decidedly modern direction, Moscow retains some of its historic and beautiful buildings. From the imposing Kremlin to the colorful onion-shaped domes of St. Basil&#38;#39;s Cathedral, Moscow is a city to be relished.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Beautifully colorful St. Petersburg is the cultural center of Russia, with lively performing arts, culinary, history and architecture scenes. The Neva River winds its way through most of the town, providing a scenic foreground and backdrop for many of the city&#38;#39;s most brilliantly constructed buildings. St. Isaac&#38;#39;s Cathedral is known for its neoclassic facade and ornate dome plated in pure gold. Other lovely religious buildings to visit in St. Petersburg include Church of the Savior of Blood, Saints Peter and Paul Cathedral and Kazan Cathedral. Grand palaces and squares enhance the cultured ambiance of St. Petersburg. Expansive Palace Square is home to the glorious Winter Palace and the red granite Alexander Column and leads to the Admiralty Square and to The Hermitage, one of the world&#38;#39;s largest art museums.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Flights to a Scenic Country in First Class Seat&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make the lengthy journey to Russia enjoyable in the luxury of &#60;strong&#62;business and first class air travel&#60;/strong&#62;. The deluxe amenities and services begin before you even step onto the plane, with pampering airport lounges. Exclusive lounges often offer salon and spa services, entertainment areas, business centers and refreshments. Once you board your plane, you&#38;#39;ll dine on five-star meals and enjoy spacious, leather seats, entertainment systems and ample space to work, dine and sleep.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With FlyFirst&#38;#39;s top-of-the-line services, you&#38;#39;ll gain access to remarkable discounts on premium airfare, whether you need to make a sudden, last-minute business trip or a planned vacation. Enjoy FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s discounts up to 70 percent off rack rates, and receive stellar &#60;strong&#62;first class deals &#60;/strong&#62;and &#60;strong&#62;business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; to beautiful Russia.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3640</first_class_price><business_class_price>2890</business_class_price><seo><description>luxury business class, first class, business class travel to Russia, discounted flight business class,Last Minute flights</description><keywords>luxury first class, inexpensive business class, business class flight to Russia, last minute flight</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>cc22c4da763b4a1794786c013bc8b944.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Business Class Flight Discount</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>1637a596901e4eba892aac9bd37c0211.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Affordable First Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>45ab94e906a74220908468943f0fe3f5.jpg</alias><content_id>24</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>25</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>India</name><title>Cheap Business Class to India &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights. Save Up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-India</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to India, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to India. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flights to India.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color: rgb(169, 169, 169); line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Make the journey to the India in inexpensive opulence with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s deeply discounted business class seats and first class fares.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Trek to vibrant, exotic India in elegant luxury with&#60;strong&#62; affordable first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst.com. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on premium flights so that you can spend more of your travel budget enjoying the country&#38;#39;s vivid cultural landmarks and thrilling recreational attractions.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Diversity, Dillis and Tandoori&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Just as you would expect for a country that is the birthplace of four major religions, India is a melting pot of the East. Its awe-inspiring architecture is a testament to that diversity, from the Mughal architecture of Agra&#38;#39;s Taj Mahal and Delhi&#38;#39;s Red Fort to the stepped Dravidian architecture of Jagannath Temple in Odisha.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;In India, be sure to sample the country&#38;#39;s many flavors at open-air and street markets called dilli. In Delhi, spend some time at Dilli Haat, where you can taste the foods of several regions, including the tandoor-baked favorites of naan and skewered meats. Dilli Haat is abuzz with the sights and sounds of the local scene and is home to dozens of shops featuring elaborate fabrics, beads, local art and regional crafts.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Those looking for some Bollywood musical excitement, can head to India&#38;#39;s west coast city of Mumbai. While there, cruise along Marine Drive at dusk for spectacular views of the sun setting on the Arabian Sea, or boat over to Elephanta Island to marvel at the seven hand-dug Elephanta Caves and their elaborate carvings.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Once India&#38;#39;s cultural highlights are explored, head to the country&#38;#39;s northern border to take in the stunning views of the Himalayan Mountains. Travelers can journey to the lesser Himalaya ranges on the historic Darjeeling Himalayan Railway. Seasoned mountain climbers delight in the bounty of challenging trails, and sightseers savor the spectacular Himalayan views from the Darjeeling Ropeway cars.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxuriate in the Journey&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make your long sojourn to India pleasurable in the comfort of premium travel. You&#38;#39;ll be pampered from the time you enter the airport until the time your aircraft lands, and you&#38;#39;ll arrive in glorious India as rested as possible. Exclusive first and business class airport lounges offer refreshments, abundant services, bountiful entertainment options and fully equipped business centers. Those services continue on your flight and ensure that your lengthy journey is as productive as you need it to be.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;;

    &#60;div&#62;Known in the tourism industry for our outstanding travel professionals and unparalleled discounts, FlyFirst.com offers you top-of-the-line service. Our deep discounts are available on all types of travel, from &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; to multi-city trips. Call us today to save up to 70 percent on &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; to India so that you can begin to experience the magic and mystery of this Eastern land.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4640</first_class_price><business_class_price>3470</business_class_price><seo><description>best discounted business class, cheap flight, flight, business class ticket to India</description><keywords>business class seats, first class seats, last minute business class flight, last minute travel to India</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>6a8d5a947f9e403b845d0351dec10ffe.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Travel</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>eb50b70b6b5e414ea38c5d847f0f80cd.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>53ca62501da54739a66d01718536d394.jpg</alias><content_id>25</content_id><title>First Class Deals</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>26</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Korea</name><title>Best business class fares and cheapest first class tickets to Korea</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Korea</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Korea, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Korea. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.

    &#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Korea.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Travel to South Korea in the luxury you deserve with stunning &#60;strong&#62;first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;discounted business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on your airfare so that you can experience all of South Korea&#38;#39;s many adventures.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Retreat to the Land of the Morning Calm, where royal palaces, Buddhist temples and lush landscapes create a country that is at once welcoming and exotic. Travel to South Korea in the luxury you deserve with stunning &#60;strong&#62;first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;discounted business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; from FlyFirst. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on your airfare so that you can experience all of South Korea&#38;#39;s many adventures.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Towers, Temples and Thrills&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Modern and cosmopolitan, South Korea is known for its electronics, aerospace, biotechnology and robotics industries. With robust economies, the metropolitan flavors of Seoul, Incheon and Busan are created by seas of skyscrapers and advanced enterprises. Those bustling cities offer a wealth of opportunity and activities, from world-class shopping, bountiful fine dining and dozens of museums, theaters and theme parks.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    In addition to its man-made structures, South Korea brims with natural wonders, from semi-tropical Jeju-do Island and ecological treasure Suncheonman Bay to the Taebaek Mountains. The mountainous peninsula is ideal for thrill-seeker activities, including bungee jumping, whitewater rafting, kayaking, skiing, cycling and wind surfing.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With a long and storied history, South Korea holds some gorgeous remnants of its past. The Joseon Dynasty&#38;#39;s 14th century Five Grand Palaces in Seoul are perfect examples of brilliant Eastern architecture. Since Buddhism was introduced to Korea in the 4th century, a number of Buddhist relics are scattered throughout the country, from megalithic dolmens in Gochang to the Bulgaska temple at Mount Toham.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Awaits in Business &#38;amp; First Class Seat&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make your journey to the Land of the Morning Calm an equally tranquil experience aboard extravagant first and&#60;strong&#62; business class cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. Before you reach the airplane, you&#38;#39;ll be welcomed into special, exclusive airport lounges offering dining, cocktails, full-service business centers, refreshing showers and salon services, entertainment systems and inviting lounge areas. With all of the pampering that these airport lounges provide, you&#38;#39;ll never look at a lengthy layover as an irritation again. Reserved customs and boarding lines help you board your plane more quickly so that you can settle into your luscious leather seat and prepare for a &#60;strong&#62;luxury flight&#60;/strong&#62;. An oasis in the sky, your &#60;strong&#62;business and first class cabins&#60;/strong&#62; offer distinctive cuisine, comfortable bedding and ample room to work.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s personalized and expert travel services, you&#38;#39;ll receive deep discounts on premium flights of all kinds. Whether you require&#60;strong&#62; last minute business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;, open-ended return date tickets or an arduous multi-city itinerary, our skilled travel professionals offer the same great deals. The best part of all is that you&#38;#39;ll enjoy your flight time to gorgeous South Korea while saving up to 70 percent on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4480</first_class_price><business_class_price>3370</business_class_price><seo><description>best first class, first class ticket to Korea, inexpensive business class, first class discountes</description><keywords>travel to Korea, business class travel, first class travel, deals on business class flight, best first class deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>7b0cc7cac7eb44bf833b980398606043.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>8452917b93ff4d9eadee28c0b29e5bc7.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>First Class Discounts</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>1b87bf792e7a432b937df77f429599bd.jpg</alias><content_id>26</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>27</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Sweden</name><title>Savings on business class fares and first class deals to Sweden</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flights-To-Sweden</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Sweden, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Sweden. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Sweden.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel to the pristine Nordic country of Sweden, where historic palaces and gleaming glass buildings rest side-by-side. Make your way to welcoming Sweden in the lush comfort of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s discount &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save up to 70 percent on regular premium travel fares, leaving you thousands to better enjoy your Scandinavian adventure.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    A rich Viking history pervades Sweden, both in historic artifacts and in storytelling. While in Sweden, you can explore the exploits of these early Swedes at the Greece Runestones, Varangian Runestones and England Runestones. The Ingvar Runestones, now scattered throughout Sweden, commemorate the final expedition of Ingvar the Far-Traveled to Serkland. Traveling throughout the country to view the various runestones is a fantastic way to see the country, meet locals and discover Swedish history.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Stockholm is Sweden&#38;#39;s largest city and offers exciting experiences for travelers. From Old Town&#38;#39;s Royal Palace and Stockholm Cathedral to Parliament House and Stockholm City Hall, the historic architecture is breathtaking and welcoming.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Second largest city, Gothenburg, is an active, vibrant town. With its picturesque, bustling port, Gothenburg is both beautiful and cosmopolitan. It offers a buffet of cultural, artistic and community events, from famous music festivals to immense sporting tournaments. Movie buffs from around the world travel to the city for its G&#38;ouml;teborg International Film Festival, and tens of thousands of soccer players converge in Gothenburg each year for its Gothia Cup, the largest football/soccer tournament in the world.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Gothenburg is also home to two world-class institutions: Liseburg and Volvo. Named one of the top ten theme parks in the world by&#38;#160;&#60;em&#62;Forbes&#60;/em&#62;&#38;#160;magazine, Liseburg is home to exhilarating rides and roller coasters and a charming Christmas market. Slightly less adrenaline-inducing, Volvo offers a ride on The Blue Train through the company&#38;#39;s Torslanda factory to see how Volvos are manufactured.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Fit for a Monarch&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Flights to Sweden can be relaxing aboard the luscious style of first and business class cabins. Your luxurious trip begins at the airport with privileged entree to reserved airport lounges. First and business class lounges feature refreshing buffets and snacks, abundant entertainment, occasional spa and salon services and well-equipped business centers. Aboard your flight, you&#38;#39;ll revel in the personalized service offering five-star quality meals, free-flowing drinks, spacious and plush seats and amenity kits filled with today&#38;#39;s most exclusive skin care products.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;These luxuries can be yours to enjoy with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s amazing deals of up to 70 percent off regular fares. Whether you are flying at the &#60;strong&#62;last minute&#60;/strong&#62; or need deals on multi-city itineraries, FlyFirst.com has you covered. Call us today to secure your fabulous deals on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; to Sweden.&#60;/p&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3560</first_class_price><business_class_price>2670</business_class_price><seo><description>business class tickets to Sweden, business class discount, cheap business class to Sweden</description><keywords>savings on business class, travel deals, airline specials, special fares for business class, special fares for first class to Sweden</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>73b0c1ef0df045168abc585dd01c69ec.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Affordable Business Class Flights</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>45b94ac620704edb8d4cecde602e6432.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>3995fc168b7b437c9d02b7a4ce023220.jpg</alias><content_id>27</content_id><title>Discounted First Class flights</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>28</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Netherlands</name><title>Save thousands on first class deals and discounted business class tickets to Holland</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Netherlans</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Holland, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Netherlands. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;
    &#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Holland.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2 id=&#34;textpreview&#34;&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.2em;&#34;&#62;Windmills, Commerce and Peace&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Although many Westerners refer to the entire country of the Netherlands as Holland, Holland is actually a region within the Netherlands along the country&#38;#39;s North Sea Coast. Dozens of towns, large and small, offer plenty of attractions and activities, but Holland&#38;#39;s three largest cities are notable and distinct.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Amsterdam, the capital of the Netherlands, rests serenely in the North Holland region. Eight large, traditional windmills are sprinkled throughout Amsterdam, helping the large city retain its picturesque charm. Whether you are visiting Amsterdam for business or pleasure, there are plenty of must-see sights to include on your itinerary. Quaint Oude Kerk is the city&#38;#39;s oldest church, while the Church of St. Nicholas is a sprawling and impressive example of Neo-Renaissance and Neo-Baroque architecture. As testament to the city&#38;#39;s importance to fine art over the centuries, visitors can tour the Van Gogh Museum and honor the memory of Rembrandt at his statue.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Culture and commerce blend beautifully in Rotterdam, Holland&#38;#39;s second largest city. With one of the busiest ports in the world and a robust international commercial center, Rotterdam is a bustling hub for business. Its forward-thinking nature is evident in its remarkable Erasmus Bridge spanning the Meuse River, the Euromast observation tower and the funky, symbolic Cube Houses.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Known for its broad-minded attitudes and reputation for fairness, it&#38;#39;s fitting that the Netherlands is home to the most famous international political institution in The Hague. Its beautiful Peace Palace houses the International Court of Justice and the Permanent Court of Arbitration, and it frequently hosts special international events. The center of politics within its own nation, The Hague also holds gorgeous national government and royal buildings such as the Binnenhof, Knight&#38;#39;s Hall and the Royal Noordeinde Palace.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;World-class Flights for a World-Class Region in Affordable Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With all that Holland entails, making the long flight in comfort is a smart choice. Sumptuous &#60;strong&#62;first and business class &#60;/strong&#62;adventures begin at the airport with exclusive lounges and continue onto your flight. Culinary masterpieces, plush leather seats, bountiful storage and work spaces and pampering service make the trip enjoyable and restful.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;br /&#62;
    Our luxury &#60;strong&#62;travel discounts&#60;/strong&#62; are available for all travel needs, including one-way trips, &#60;strong&#62;last minute flights&#60;/strong&#62; and multi-city destinations. Call us today to get started on planning your dream trip to Holland, and soon you&#38;#39;ll be on your way to the beautiful region with satisfying &#60;strong&#62;savings on first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; reduced business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/div&#62;
    &#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3670</first_class_price><business_class_price>2840</business_class_price><seo><description>business class, first class, discounts on airline tickets, best price for business class, last minute flight</description><keywords>first class service to Holland, business, first, luxury travel, business class deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>8f2ace088c89421aadf38bdc582ef1de.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Business Class Flight Discounts</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>8ff4b8ef86354bb9be12aa3ab7d8bd19.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Affordable First Class Flight</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>8aed8ca0dbc94d1595a22c3764e9c6b2.jpg</alias><content_id>28</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Ticket</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>29</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Turkey</name><title>Huge savings on business and first class deals to Turkey. Save up to 70%</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Turkey</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Turkey, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Turkey. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.&#38;#160;
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Turkey.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on your premium flight so that you can better enjoy Turkey&#38;#39;s rich historical sites, impressive mountains and exuberant rivers.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make a memorable sojourn to the luscious land of Turkey in contented luxury with FlyFirst&#38;#39;s discount &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; business class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll save as much as 70 percent on your premium flight so that you can better enjoy Turkey&#38;#39;s rich historical sites, impressive mountains and exuberant rivers.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Turkey, on the Anatolian Peninsula, is one of the oldest settlements in the world and has the archaeological wonders to prove it. From the G&#38;ouml;bekli Tepe erected in 10,000 B.C.E. and the Neolithic &#38;Ccedil;atalh&#38;ouml;y&#38;uuml;k to the walls of Troy and the Lion Gate of Hattusa, the world&#38;#39;s ancient history plays out across the country.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The progression of Turkey&#38;#39;s history is evident in its many beautiful structures. The Byzantine Hagia Sophia is a gorgeous church-turned-mosque surrounded by manicured gardens, jetting fountains and impressive spires. Ottoman-era Selimiye Mosque in Edirne and Istanbul&#38;#39;s Baroque-style Dolmabah&#38;ccedil;e Palace and Ottoman Empire Topkapi Palace are sites not to be missed.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Culture, religion and adventure combine in the presence of imposing Mt. Ararat. A breathtaking site, Mt. Ararat is believed to be the home of Noah and is a challenging hike for skilled mountain climbers. Surrounded by the Black, Aegean and Mediterranean seas, Turkey offers plenty of water activities, from surfing and windsurfing to whitewater rafting and scuba diving. Exploration and hiking are abundant at the Cappadocians where the amazing Faery Chimneys rock formations and rock-cut temple emerge suddenly from the landscape.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Those looking for a more cosmopolitan experience head to modern Istanbul and Ankara, where skyscrapers dominate unique skylines. Dynamic business districts set busy paces for both cities, with vibrant performing arts, culinary and shopping scenes. Yet, along with this forward momentum, both cities maintain their reverence for ancient, historic and religious sites, such as Ankara Castle and the Temple of Augustus and Rome in Ankara and Istanbul&#38;#39;s Blue Mosque.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Treat Yourself to Luxury Travel in Cheap Business Class Flight&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;As a luxury passenger, you have exclusive access to amazing airport lounges. Begin your trip with the pampering amenities common at &#60;strong&#62;first and business class lounges&#60;/strong&#62;, such as relaxing spa services, abundant food, state-of-the-art entertainment and fully equipped business centers. On board your flight, you&#38;#39;ll appreciate over-sized leather seats, five-star meals, ample storage and gracious flight attendants. All these services ensures that you arrive in Turkey feeling refreshed and ready to explore the exotic, vivacious country.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;At FlyFirst.com the&#60;strong&#62; luxury of first and business class travel&#60;/strong&#62; is affordable, with &#60;strong&#62;discounts of up to 70 percent off published rates&#60;/strong&#62;. Our expert travel professionals offer outstanding service and the largest savings available. &#60;strong&#62;Call us today&#60;/strong&#62; to secure your economical &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;cut-rate business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; to the gorgeous Anatolia Peninsula and Turkey.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3940</first_class_price><business_class_price>2870</business_class_price><seo><description>last minute first class, last minute business class, last minute flight, last minute business class</description><keywords>flight to Turkey, business class flight, inexpensive business class tickets</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>b1cb027471b34b178f1b371f4cbca3b9.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>Business Class Deals</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>514f1bbed1594124a3c2d9a4690218ae.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>First Class Discounts </title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>ea21b1dfe07d41efb035d28e0730cece.jpg</alias><content_id>29</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Class Flight</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>30</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Egypt</name><title>Discounted Business &#38; First Class Flights to Egypt. Save up to 70% on Last Minute Business Class.</title><alias>Cheap-First-Class-Flight-to-Egypt</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Egypt, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Egypt. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Egypt.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;You&#38;#39;ll pay as little as 30 percent of regular luxury airfare while enjoying all of the full-price amenities and extravagant services of &#60;strong&#62;first and business class flights&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Both ancient and modern, Egypt is an economic and cultural leader in the region. Its long history, reaching back to the 10th millennium B.C., offers up plentiful and amazing ancient ruins. From the Giza pyramids and Great Sphinx to the ruins at Memphis, Karnak, the Valley of the Kings and Thebes, Egypt&#38;#39;s early treasures offer days of exploration and wonderment.&#38;#160;&#60;/span&#62;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    With the lovely Mediterranean on its northern borders, the azure Red Sea on its east, and the sweeping Nile River winding its way through the country, Egypt overflows with recreation and aquatic activities. Scuba diving and snorkeling along the Red Sea Riviera is particularly appealing since the area encompasses 250 coral reefs teeming with 1,000 colorful fish species.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Egypt&#38;#39;s largest cities offer their own distinctive appeal. Mega-metropolis Cairo manages to retain its exotic, historic ambiance with its abundance of medieval structures, old religious buildings and treasured landmarks. Known as the &#38;quot;city of a thousand minarets,&#38;quot; Islamic architecture is seen throughout Cairo in ornate mosques such as Al-Azhar Mosque, Al-Hakim Mosque and Lulua Mosque.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Immerse yourself in ancient Egyptian artifacts found in museums such as those at the medieval Saladin Citadel and the famed Museum of Egyptian Antiquities. Explore Egyptian art, food and crafts at the atmosphere-filled Khan el-Khalili, the ancient bazaar that dates back to 1382.&#38;#160;&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Creating and entirely different Egyptian experience, Alexandria&#38;#39;s Mediterranean and Hellenistic influences are evident. Tour the catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa, the ruins of an ancient Roman amphitheater and Pompey&#38;#39;s Pillar. Dedicated to Osiris and housing several Cleopatra artifacts, the Temple of Taposiris Magna is a fascinating site highlighting 3rd century art and architecture.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Fit for a Pharaoh, Travel in Discounted Business Class&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;Why travel to Egypt in cramped coach when you can enjoy the amenity-filled opulence of affordable first class? As a premium passenger, you&#38;#39;ll have access to exclusive airport lounges, expedited boarding queues and countless other time- and energy-saving services. In the air, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy fine dining, plush and spacious seating and state-of-the-art entertainment.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;line-height: 1.6em;&#34;&#62;At FlyFirst.com, premium travel is economical, with savings of up to 70 percent off published fares. Our travel professionals offer unmatched personalized service and the largest discounts around. FlyFirst Offers &#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business Class&#60;/strong&#62;. Call us now to plan your trip of a lifetime to Egypt with amazingly &#60;strong&#62;inexpensive first class flights and business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4270</first_class_price><business_class_price>3480</business_class_price><seo><description>affordable business class to Egypt, discounted first class, last minute, flight, travel, airline deals</description><keywords>savings on business class, first class flight, business class tickets to Egypt, best travel deals</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>063ea18bbaaf40c6b1dd5af40df18b24.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Cheap Last Minute Business Class To Egypt</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>9152f52c70ef4691847e75956ef32f17.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class to Egypt</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>df428a9f97f34d0aa04e8071cea7d172.jpg</alias><content_id>30</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>31</country_id><continent_id>1</continent_id><name>Belgium</name><title>Affordable Business Class Flights and First Class Tickets to Belgium</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-To-Belgium</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Belgium, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Belgium. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Belgium.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;With savings of nearly 70 percent, you&#38;#39;ll relish the journey as much as Belgium&#38;#39;s remarkable sights and rich cultural pursuits.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Travel to the land of pristine streets, welcoming locals and world-class chocolates aboard the inexpensive luxury of FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s &#60;strong&#62;discounted first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62;. With savings of nearly 70 percent, you&#38;#39;ll relish the journey as much as Belgium&#38;#39;s remarkable sights and rich cultural pursuits.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    The multi-lingual country of Belgium has a reputation for fine chocolates, a love of folklore, a dedication to fairness and mischievous, self-deprecating humor. The northern Flemish region of Belgium is Dutch-speaking, while the southern Wallonia region is French-speaking and a small region on the east speaks German. This blend of languages, nationalities and sensibilities gives Belgium its appealing ambiance.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    Belgium&#38;#39;s capital, Brussels, is a splendid blend of modern commerce, lively culture and gorgeous architecture. Its bustling Northern Quarter business district offers several high-rise towers and hectic streets, while outlying areas mix the modern with the historic. Those who want to shop or dine head to the 16th to 19th century Place du Grande Sablon, which now houses high-end chocolate, apparel and antique stores as well as fine restaurants. Stunning architecture can be found in the medieval Grand Palace and the Cathedral of Saints Michael and Gudula. Good humor and the history of the city&#38;#39;s water supply are found at the infamous Manneken Pis fountain. If you happen to be in town during a holiday season, be sure to drop by the fountain to see the statue&#38;#39;s special, humorous holiday attire.&#60;br /&#62;
    &#60;br /&#62;
    To the north of Brussels, Antwerp has one of Europe&#38;#39;s largest seaports. Brimming with Gothic architecture, Antwerp offers Cathedral of Our Lady; Grote Markt city square with its 16th century City Hall, Guild Houses and the towering Brabo Fountain as well as Het Steen, the only remaining medieval fortress from Antwerp&#38;#39;s early days as a fortified city. The home of artist Rubens, Antwerp entombed the artist in the ornate St. James&#38;#39; Church. Plenty of museums, zoos, parks and theaters are spread throughout the city, offering perfect entertainment options for business and pleasure travelers.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Luxury Travel for a Luxurious Country in Cheap Business Class Flights&#38;#160;&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;Make your journey to beautiful Belgium pleasurable by traveling in the comfort of&#60;strong&#62; first and business class airline cabins&#60;/strong&#62;. With outstanding discounts on FlyFirst.com &#60;strong&#62;business class seats&#60;/strong&#62; and&#60;strong&#62; first class deals&#60;/strong&#62;, you can revel in service-filled airport lounges, spacious airplane seating and delightful dishes at 70 percent less than published fares.&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;FlyFirst.com is dedicated to providing first-rate travel coordination and unrivaleld pricing. When you book with us, you know you are receiving the best deals available. Whether you have need complicated travel arrangements or just need great &#60;strong&#62;last minute deals&#60;/strong&#62;, FlyFirst.com offers &#60;strong&#62;stellar first class deals&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;cut-rate business class seats &#60;/strong&#62;to Belgium&#60;/p&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>3640</first_class_price><business_class_price>2680</business_class_price><seo><description>best business class, best first class, discounted tickets, best business class to Belgium, best travel deal, airplane tickets</description><keywords>first class deals, business class deal, business class price to Belgium, flight discounts, airline tickets sale</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>e5b263a0fc6142aaaba4cbec1d2e3a87.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Discounted Business Class Seats</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>2758d90daa364e53bef1f2adc2b9d175.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Economical First Class Airfare</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>dc1fca17d2bc47f791ac5855a6212233.jpg</alias><content_id>31</content_id><title>Discounted First Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>32</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Japan</name><title>Cheap Business Class to Japan &#38; Discounted First Class Tickets. Save Thousands on Last Minute Flights</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-To-Japan</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Japan, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Japan. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;div&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Japan.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Whether you are traveling to Japan for business or pleasure, we&#38;#39;ll save you up to 60 percent on posh&#60;strong&#62; business and first class seats&#60;/strong&#62; on some of the world&#38;#39;s most highly rated airlines. Best of all, our knowledgeable travel specialists will plan your flights to ensure you get the very best available deals to Japan without hassle or drama.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Experience the Tradition and Beauty of Japan&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our expert travel planning and&#60;strong&#62; luxury airfare deals to Japan&#60;/strong&#62; will leave you with plenty of time and money to explore the beauty of Japan. You can take in the majesty of Mt. Fuji, delight in the country&#38;#39;s colorful cherry blossoms or enjoy Japan&#38;#39;s rich cultural heritage. For business travelers, Japan&#38;#39;s industries have much to offer, from robust technology and automotive industries to machine tools and textiles. Boasting the globe&#38;#39;s third largest national economy, Japan&#38;#39;s business opportunities are bountiful. Business and pleasure travelers alike will appreciate the country&#38;#39;s sumptuous cuisine, time-saving bullet trains and brilliant scenery.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;The Joys of First and Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Traveling from USA to Japan can mean long, tiresome flights of about 14 hours. Take the pressure, worry and discomfort out of your flight arrangements by booking a &#60;strong&#62;discounted business or first class seat&#60;/strong&#62; to Japan. The 60 percent savings offered on luxury travel to Japan by FlyFirst makes the long journey affordable and enjoyable. As a business or first class passenger, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy the amenities and services of some of the world&#38;#39;s best airport lounges. In the lounges, you can expect extraordinary concierge services, complimentary meals, fully-equipped business facilities, plentiful entertainment options and relaxing services such as massages, beauty treatments and salon amenities. Once on your flight, you&#38;#39;ll be treated to complimentary beverages, meals inspired by the world&#38;#39;s greatest chefs, plush seating, bed turn-down service, personal video monitors and entertainment systems, privacy options and so much more. These incredible luxuries will help you arrive at your Japanese destination relaxed and able to enjoy the rest of your trip.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Exclusive FlyFirst Services &#38;amp; Cheap Business Class&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Our experienced travel specialists offer a full range of travel options and services, all with our renowned &#60;strong&#62;discounts on luxury trave&#60;/strong&#62;l. Need an open-ended return ticket,&#60;strong&#62; last minute flight&#60;/strong&#62; or multi-city itinerary? No problem, we can coordinate all those travel plans and still offer the best-priced luxury airline seats available. We specialize in &#60;strong&#62;cheap business class&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;first class flights&#60;/strong&#62; to Japan, so no travel request is too complicated for our talented travel specialists.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;We Can Plan Your Trip to Japan Today&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;We make it easy to get started on your upcoming trip to Japan. Simply call us toll-free to speak with one of our knowledgeable travel specialists, or complete our online travel form for a quick and free travel quote. We will begin working on your travel plans immediately, and we&#38;#39;ll have you on your way in no time.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4370</first_class_price><business_class_price>3640</business_class_price><seo><description>cheap business class, cheap last minute business class, cheap last minute ticket, business class fare, first class airfare</description><keywords>cheap flight to Japan, inexpensive business class flight, first class tickets, business class seats, first class seats</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>f8f7e7fe2088490dac8d24d96268dd32.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Cheap Business Class Flight</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>4aff056939f0422c927a417ee56894cd.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>First Class Deals</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>dcb05f6b271b43929630cb1f2858c648.jpg</alias><content_id>32</content_id><title>Last Minute First Class</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item><item><country_id>33</country_id><continent_id>2</continent_id><name>Malaysia</name><title>Discounted First Class &#38; Last Minute Business Class Seats to Malaysia</title><alias>Cheap-Business-Class-Flight-To-Malaysia</alias><summary>FlyFirst offers cheap Business Class flights to Malaysia, we specialize on last minute business class tickets, FlyFirst provides discounted First Class fares to Malaysia. Save Thousands on Business and First Class Tickets.Discount First &#38;amp; Business Class Airline Tickets. First Class &#38;amp; Business Class Travel Deals.
</summary><body>&#60;p&#62;&#60;strong&#62;Cheap Business &#38;amp; First Class Flight to Malaysia.&#38;#160; Save Thousands on Last Minute Business Class Tickets. Affordable Price for Business Class Seats. Call Us Now to Book &#38;amp; Save up to 70%&#60;/strong&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;p&#62;&#60;span style=&#34;color:#A9A9A9;&#34;&#62;Make your sojourn to the Malaysian center in sumptuous comfort with FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s terrifically&#60;strong&#62; reduced business class airfares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;discounted last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62;. You&#38;#39;ll pay less than half regular airfare for luxury travel that will deliver you to Malaysia rested and ready to explore.&#60;/span&#62;&#60;/p&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Diplomats, Financiers and Hindu Deities&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With its prospering financial markets, diplomatic missions and treasured landmarks, Malaysia is the sixth most popular world destination. For business travelers, the city is home to most foreign embassies, a burgeoning service sector and a growing hub of global Islamic financing. This showpiece of finance and economic progress is evident in the city&#38;#39;s many high-rise buildings and its iconic, record-setting Petronas Twin Towers. For a quick break between business meetings, the twin towers offer a stunning view of the city, as does the 1,381-foot Malaysia Tower spire.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Home to the Malaysian king&#38;#39;s official residence, Malaysia has a relatively short history that is best explored through its many buildings and open spaces. View the site where the country shed its British colonial flag in 1957 at Merdeka Square, or get a feel for the town&#38;#39;s pioneers at its Chinatown on Petaling Street. First-rate shopping, endless museums and an energetic nightlife bring extra entertainment to your exotic Malaysia voyage.&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Natural and religious wonders are located throughout the sprawling city. Delight in the Moorish architecture of Jamek Mosque, officially opened by the Sultan of Selangor in 1909. Explore the astonishing Batu Caves, guarded by an expansive shrine and a 140-foot tall gilded statue of the Hindu deity Murugan. Hindu drawings, statues and shrines are sprinkled throughout the site&#38;#39;s three main caves and many smaller caves. While on site, enjoy one of the 160 rock climbing routes among the caves and the surrounding mountainside.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;In the Lap of Luxury&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;Make the long-distance flight to Malaysia enjoyable aboard the comfort and style of first and &#60;strong&#62;business class air travel&#60;/strong&#62;. The deluxe services begin even before you embark on the plane, with extravagant airport lounges featuring salon and spa services, complimentary meals and comfortable lounge areas. Once you board your airplane, you&#38;#39;ll enjoy five-star meals, spacious seats, bed turn-down service, ample work space and services catered to your needs.&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;&#38;#160;&#60;/div&#62;

    &#60;h2&#62;Industry-Leading FlyFirst.com Services&#60;/h2&#62;

    &#60;div&#62;With FlyFirst.com&#38;#39;s exclusive services, you&#38;#39;ll have access to deep &#60;strong&#62;discounts on luxury airfare&#60;/strong&#62;, whether yours is a&#60;strong&#62; last-minute business trip&#60;/strong&#62; or a well-planned vacation. Enjoy up to 60 percent off published rates on &#60;strong&#62;business class fares&#60;/strong&#62; and &#60;strong&#62;last minute first class tickets&#60;/strong&#62; so you can relish all that the tropical Malaysia offers.&#60;/div&#62;
</body><capital_city>null</capital_city><first_class_price>4760</first_class_price><business_class_price>3680</business_class_price><seo><description>business class tickets, last minute deals, last minute travel, business class fare, business class airfare to Malaysia</description><keywords>last minute, first, business, airplane tickets, flight to Malaysia, fly business cheap</keywords></seo><images><image><alias>3de356012e034796983e50f0b729133d.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Last Minute Business Trip</title><queue>0</queue></image><image><alias>f6fb3bc42ad249d3b96342450c6f2feb.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>Discounted First Class Tickets</title><queue>1</queue></image><image><alias>a457c817935d4c46bb2e5ec1585c371b.jpg</alias><content_id>33</content_id><title>First Class Airfare to Asia</title><queue>2</queue></image></images></item></items>